<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Destination>

	<dest>
		<thumb>beginner</thumb>
		<image>beginner</image>
		<link>beginners-guide-on-how-to-charter-a-yacht</link>
		<title>Beginner's Guide On How To Charter A Yacht </title>
		<desc>Learn everything you need to know about yacht charters.</desc>
		<text>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;If you are looking to explore islands, experience breathtaking views, and travel in style, then the perfect vacation for you would be a yacht charter. When you charter a yacht, you get unlimited freedom to build your own itinerary, enjoy complete privacy, and get a taste of luxury.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A yacht is undoubtedly the epitome of wealth; with high quality, mansion-like interior and the ability to travel across seas, it's no surprise that all the wealthiest people own one. However, the ability to purchase a yacht outright is only accessible to a few people. This is where yacht charters come in. They allow us to get a taste of luxury for a few days without having to drop millions on a boat.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;P&gt;Chartering a yacht can seem like a daunting experience, and you might not know where to start. This is why we have compiled this thorough yacht charter guide that will tell you everything you need to know on how to charter a yacht, how to plan your itinerary, which yacht to choose, and more.&lt;/P&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;What is a Yacht Charter?&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;This is the practice of renting or chartering any kind of boat, whether a motorboat or a sailing one. You use it to travel to various destinations of your preference. Regardless of whether you are looking for the ideal family vacation spot or an island-hopping experience, a yacht charter gives you a safe, secure, and private environment to do all of that and more. With a yacht charter, you can build a personalized itinerary and do things your way, all the while enjoying utmost luxury.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Why Charter a Yacht?&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;P&gt;Yacht charters can provide you with a wonderful twist if you are bored of the same approach to your water-centered vacations. No matter the destination, yacht charters provide you with an unforgettable experience by letting you stay on a boat that resembles a five-star hotel and serves as an interesting mode of transportation. Here are the three main things you can enjoy when you charter a yacht:&lt;/P&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;ol class="bg-li"&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;</p>
			<p>A Customized Experience </p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A yacht charter experience comes with a complete crew, including a captain, cleaning staff, and chef. This means that they all can give you a completely personalized experience. For example, rather than relying on a pre-made menu, you can have the chef make something of your choice. Moreover, you can even stop wherever you want to enjoy views. All in all, it will provide you with an experience unlike any other.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Personal Freedom</p>
			<p>&lt;P&gt;One of the most significant reasons people go on yacht charter vacations is that they allow for personal freedom that cannot be compared to any other type of vacation. Even when comparing a yacht charter to a water-bound vacation like a cruise, yacht charter tops the list. This is because you get to decide where to go and when. You can visit different cities, diving spots, and ports according to your preference. It is all entirely up to you.&lt;/P&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Range of Excellent Amenities</p>
			<p>&lt;P&gt;Boats are typically considered a mode of transportation. However, that is not the case with yachts because they contain a wide range of amazing amenities. Depending on the cost and size of the yacht, you can enjoy features such as saunas, kitchens, hot tubs, steam rooms, swimming pools, and even a spa area.&lt;/P&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/ol&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Things to Consider when Chartering a Yacht&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;There are various types of yacht charters, and a number of variables impact the type you get. Some of these include your location, time of the year, and budget. For example, yacht charters tend to be much more affordable during the offseason. This is why you should keep all of these variables in mind before choosing a yacht charter for you.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;ol class="bg-li"&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Budget</p>
			<p>&lt;P&gt;This is perhaps the most important consideration when choosing a yacht charter. If you have a significantly large budget, you will not need to worry about the type of yacht and duration of the trip. However, if you don't want to break the bank on a yacht charter, you will have to consider these factors due to fuel costs.&lt;/P&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;P&gt;Typically, a weeklong yacht charter on a smaller yacht can cost around $10,000. However, a larger yacht, longer than 100-foot, and luxury yacht charters will range from $50,000 to $80,000. Superyachts cost even more, typically over $150,000. Other factors that may impact the total cost include taxes, service charges, and the cost of traveling to the place where you will begin your yacht charter.&lt;/P&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;The Type of Yacht Charter Experience</p>
			<p>&lt;P&gt;When choosing a yacht charter, you also have to decide whether to get one with an inclusive or exclusive expense. Inclusive yachts provide all amenities and services you would need to enjoy the trip. These are mostly included in luxury yacht charters, for example, crew members, food and drinks, planned itineraries, and more. Inclusive yacht charters tend to be more expensive but allow the guests to sit back and relax while everything is being done for them.&lt;/P&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;P&gt;On the other hand, some people prefer exclusive expense-based yacht charters because they are cheaper. They only charge you a base rate for the fuel costs, docking fees, captain and crew, and other amenities. You pay this lump sum amount at the beginning of the trip, after which you will likely not need to pay any additional fee.&lt;/P&gt; </p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Destination and Duration of the Trip</p>
			<p>&lt;P&gt;Since you will likely have to pay for fuel charges on top of the total cost for the yacht charter, where you are going will also impact the overall cost of the yacht charter trip. Those who plan to visit many destinations when they charter their yacht will need to spend much more than those going to one nearby destination. More than one destination also extends the duration of the trip, which will also impact the total cost and how much you will be spending. Hence, depending on your budget, you should plan your destination and duration accordingly.&lt;/P&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Size of the Yacht</p>
			<p>&lt;P&gt;Many people think that a larger yacht will always be the better option, but that is not true because it can lead to wasted space and money. Not only will a larger yacht cost more, but it will also accumulate a larger amount of fuel charges. Instead of doing that, it is recommended that you choose a luxury yacht charter that will give you a comfortable experience. For example, a reliable captain and an excellent chef are a much more worthwhile investment than a larger and longer yacht. You should only consider a larger yacht when you are hosting a party or wedding, but not when you are looking to travel to a destination.&lt;/P&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/ol&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Step By Step Guide on How to Charter a Yacht&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Now that you know about the main factors you should take under consideration when chartering a yacht, here's a thorough step-by-step guide on how to charter a yacht so you can plan all the details immaculately.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;ol class="bg-li"&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Decide Your Destination and Plan the Details in Advance</p>
			<p>&lt;P&gt;The first step in determining your yacht charter experience is to decide where to go. This entirely depends on your preferences, but some of the most popular yacht charter destinations include the Caribbean, Galapagos Islands, Alaska, Greece, and Italy. Once you decide on your destination, you should then plan out all of the details. Doing this in advance will not only help provide you with a comfortable yacht charter experience but will also let your broker know about the exact kind of yacht that would fit your preferences.&lt;/P&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;P&gt;Once you have decided the destination, you should also think about when to go since the ideal time to go will depend on the destination you choose or the other way round. The time will also impact the budget because off-season times typically result in lower costs.&lt;/P&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Determine Your Requirements</p>
			<p>&lt;P&gt;The key to crafting the perfect yacht charter experience is to determine all the requirements beforehand, including your budget, the number of guests, what amenities you require, whether you want an all-inclusive or exclusive expense yacht, and the size of your yacht.&lt;/P&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Look for the Perfect Yacht</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The next step in your yacht charter's guide is to start looking for the perfect yacht that fits your pre-determined requirements. When looking at specific yachts, you should also read all of the terms and conditions of each carefully, including their cancellation and payment terms. Note what amenities and features are included and excluded in the yacht and then finally review the agreement before signing it.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Once everything is clear and checked out by you, you can book the yacht and make all the necessary payments.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Plan Your Itinerary</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A luxury yacht charter, an all-inclusive one, and a superyacht will all give you a personalized itinerary. You can make changes to it, or you can plan your own itinerary yourself. You can work with the captain to tailor your itinerary, plan the routes, and create a customized experience. You should plan your itinerary with all the details, including where to dock the yacht, what activities to do, and dining options.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/ol&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt; </p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Final Words&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Your yacht charter will be an unforgettable trip unlike any other you have embarked on. This is why when it comes to how to charter a yacht; you should plan out each detail beforehand. Whether you are looking for the perfect family vacation or partying with your friends on a yacht, you can travel in style with a luxury yacht charter.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
		</text>
	</dest>

	<dest>
		<thumb>married</thumb>
		<image>married</image>
		<link>all-you-need-to-know-about-getting-married-on-a-yacht</link>
		<title>All You Need Know About Getting Married On A Yacht</title>
		<desc>Plan a wedding on the ocean.</desc>
		<text>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Whether you are considering a yacht or a superyacht, there are so many reasons why you should be saying, 'I do' on board a luxury boat with your close friends and family. Yacht weddings have been all the rage these days because of how they provide panoramic views of the ocean and make for an intimate gathering. Not to mention, they are perhaps the most romantic way to tie the knot. The dramatic sunset and sparkling blue waters make for the perfect setting for weddings.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;However, planning a wedding on a yacht can be slightly daunting. It requires plentiful planning and research beforehand. Moreover, there are several factors you need to keep in mind before committing to a nautical wedding on a yacht. This guide will walk you through everything you need to know about getting married on a yacht.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Reasons Why You Should Consider a Yacht Wedding&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;If you are still not convinced to have a wedding on a yacht, we're here to give you the five main reasons why you should consider otherwise. Here is why we love yacht weddings:&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;ol class="bg-li"&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;</p>
			<p>Stunning Views</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Depending on your location, you can expect to get breathtaking views and a stunning backdrop. Imagine saying your vows amidst the golden hour sunsets, blue sparkling ocean waters, and a nature-filled background. People consider beach weddings for the waterfront backdrop, but how about a wedding on this backdrop itself?&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;One-Stop Shopping </p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The most significant advantage of yacht weddings is the fact that you will not need to explore many options for your wedding. For example, most yachts are equipped with bars that have all kinds of drinks. Moreover, in some cases, captains can also legally perform wedding ceremonies. All in all, yacht weddings reduce the need for extra logistics. It really cannot get simpler to make your itinerary than with a yacht wedding&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Special Gift for Your Guests</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The unique experience of a yacht wedding gives your gifts a special gift that they will likely never forget. They can simply sit back, enjoy champagne, and dance or chat while marveling at the fantastic views.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Convenience</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;When you are getting married on a yacht, you can host the actual wedding ceremony onboard and reception there. This simplifies the wedding planning and experience, as well as becomes extremely convenient. You will not have to travel to multiple locations since everything will be under one roof.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Affordability</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Most yachts offer all-inclusive packages for weddings, which can include food and drinks, entertainment, tableware, catering, and everything related to wedding coordination. This makes planning simpler and more affordable.&lt;/p&gt; </p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/ol&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Yacht Wedding FAQs&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;If you are unfamiliar with the idea of yacht weddings, here are some answers to the most common questions regarding them.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;How Much Does it Cost to Have a Wedding on a Yacht?&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Renting a yacht is typically much cheaper than renting a wedding hall. Moreover, yachts also offer all-inclusive packages that lower the price compared to arranging and paying for all features and logistics for a typical wedding. Typically, a small yacht party with thirty guests can cost you around $1500. The price will increase when you include amenities, catering, wedding d&amp;eacute;cor, and more.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Is It Legal to Get Married on a Yacht?&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;For the most part, getting married on a yacht is legal. However, if you are cruising on international waters, that might not be the case. This is why it is recommended that you research the legal requirements of the area you are getting married in. You will also need to acquire a marriage license before the wedding ceremony.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Do Yachts Have Wedding Planners?&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Some yachts do provide wedding planners, event managers, and wedding coordinators. They can help plan the yacht wedding with you and ensure everything is on track before you board and set sail. They will also answer any questions you might have and provide guidance on having a wedding on a yacht. However, this largely depends on the type of yacht you get and whether they provide wedding planners.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;How to Plan a Wedding on a Yacht&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Now that you are aware of all the things to consider before deciding to tie the knot on board a yacht, here is how you can plan your wedding on a yacht:&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;ol class="bg-li"&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Choose Your Destination</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Likely, you have already decided which country to have your yacht wedding in. The next step is to determine the route you will take, whether or not you will stop at different spots throughout the trip, and whether you will have the ceremony or reception on the yacht or on land.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Choose Your Yacht</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;When choosing the right yacht for your wedding, you should consider its size and capacity to see how many guests can be accommodated onboard. Of course, you should also consider the budget and whether the cost fits it. You should also look at the space and whether it is enough for catering and partying.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Consider the Type of Decoration You Want</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Now that you have a yacht, the next step is to determine what kind of style of decoration you want. The decoration is essentially what will make the yacht look like it is hosting a wedding and not a party. Some people like to keep it simple with minimal decoration, while others go all out with floral decorations and a wedding aisle. The type of d&amp;eacute;cor you want largely depends on your budget, personal preferences, and the amount of space available.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Decide the Menu</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The next thing is to decide the menu. You should consider what type of catering to have at your yacht wedding, what kind of food to serve, and more. You can continue with the marine and sea theme and serve seafood or create a menu based on the local cuisine of the destination you have chosen.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Consider Entertainment Options</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Lastly, the most important aspect of any wedding is the entertainment. It is essential that you have a sound system and DJ, or a live wedding band, or dancers that will keep the party lively. Depending on the destination where you will host your yacht wedding, you can also hire local entertainers, such as dancers or performers.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/ol&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Yacht Wedding Tips&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Whether you are hosting a large yacht wedding or an intimate one, there are some tips that you need to keep in mind to make the experience special and fantastic for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;ol class="bg-li"&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Try Hosting Other Pre-Wedding Events on the Yacht</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;If you are not fully convinced to have a yacht wedding, perhaps it would be helpful to host other pre-wedding events before to see whether a wedding here would be right for you. Hosting a rehearsal dinner or bridal shower, or simply a party on a yacht will provide you with a feel of how a wedding would be. This would ultimately provide you with more clarity.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Prepare Beforehand for Possible Seasickness</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Although you will probably not be on unsteady waters, and your guests will likely have a view of the land most of the time, there is still a chance that someone might feel queasy and seasick. For such cases, it's best to equip your guests with knowledge on how to combat seasickness. You should also keep ginger candies, ginger ale, or ginger tea on board for anyone who might be feeling seasick.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Keep a Contingency Plan In Case of Bad Weather</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;One of the biggest drawbacks of hosting a yacht wedding is the uncertainty of bad weather. There is no way around it except to change the day or venue. For this reason, we recommend that you have a contingency plan in mind, such as moving your guests to the interior of the yacht.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Find Out About Wheelchair Accessibility Beforehand</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Another significant drawback of yachts is that they are typically not wheelchair accessible or friendly because they have winding staircases that lead to the upper deck or corridors that are too small for wheelchairs to fit in. Hence, if you have a guest in a wheelchair, it would be best to inquire about the yacht's wheelchair accessibility beforehand to prevent any issues or worries on the wedding day.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Determine Photo-Ops before the Wedding</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The main reason why people prefer to have a wedding on a yacht is because of the endless picturesque spots that give the perfect backdrop. It would be a good idea to work with your photographer beforehand to determine what areas maximize the breathtaking views from the yacht so that you have the best photos from your yacht wedding.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Add Necessary Information to Your Wedding Website Beforehand</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;If you are hosting a yacht wedding, it would be best to keep a wedding website or Facebook page for all of the guests that will include all the necessary information they should know about before attending the event. For example, the weather forecast on the wedding day, required dress code, whether guests should carry sunblock, and information on how to combat seasickness.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/ol&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h2&gt;Final Words&lt;/h2&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Getting married on a boat is definitely a unique and fantastic idea for couples who are on a budget and appreciate intimate settings. They not only give you a breathtaking 360 degrees view of the water and sunset but make for an unforgettable experience for you and your guests. Not to mention, planning a yacht wedding is also much easier than any other type of wedding. With the aforementioned tips and steps in this guide, you will be able to effortlessly pull off an incredible yacht wedding!&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			
		</text>
	</dest>

	<dest>
		<thumb>skippered</thumb>
		<image>skippered</image>
		<link>skippered-yacht-charters</link>
		<title>Skippered Yacht Charters</title>
		<desc>Everything you need to know about renting a crewed yacht.</desc>
		<text>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Picture this: You are on holiday, and you're lying on your yacht under the sun, sipping on wine, with no care in the world or worry about who is controlling the yacht. You can simply sit back and relax.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Yes, such vacations do exist. These are called skippered yacht charters or crewed yacht charters. They include traveling on your yacht to a destination with a skipper, captain, and other crew members such as hosts and chefs. Depending on the amount of people you hire on your yacht charter, you can let them handle everything for you.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;If you simply choose a skippered yacht charter, you get to travel with a skipper or captain who is a professional and controls the yacht. They also take care of the sailing for you. This means you can easily enjoy the yacht charter experience without worrying about anything else.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;You might still have questions regarding skippered yacht charters and what else is involved in this type of vacation. This guide will include all the details you need to know and answer all these questions, so you can decide for yourself whether a skippered yacht charter is for you or not.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;What Are Skippered Yacht Charters?&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A skipper is a qualified professional sailor whose job is to control the yacht and look after the sailing to make your vacation as enjoyable and relaxing as possible. They will be in charge of navigating the boat and taking you to your destination for the entire duration of your trip. You have the choice to rent a skippered yacht that will come with this professional crew. Some yachts come with a skipper and a captain; the captain controls the boat while the skipper handles the sailing. Otherwise, some yachts come with skippers who do everything.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Not only that, but skippers tend to have excellent knowledge of the destination they are taking you as well. If you want, they can teach you some sailing basics, give you inside knowledge and tips on sailing, and provide you with useful information about the destination you are going to. Skippers can provide you with hotel and food recommendations and give you inside knowledge on the best-hidden gems, which can prove to be a huge advantage. Your skippers know where the best dining spots are and can even make the bookings for you.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;How Does It Work? 150&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;You and your group will meet your skipper when you check in the yacht. They will likely tell you about the route they are taking, and you can discuss the details of your trip beforehand. After this, you can sit back and relax while they sail the boat. You can also go up to them and learn a few tricks on sailing, but for the most part, it entirely depends on your preference. Having someone control the boat means that you can sit back and enjoy your holiday. With a skipper, you even have free reign to swim off the back of the boat, snorkel, or simply sunbathe on the yacht.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The skipper will likely sail the yacht for three to four hours on average. However, how far you go and how long you sail primarily depends on your itinerary and destination. The skipper will dock the yacht in the evening at a port or harbor, wherein you can hop off and dine out or have dinner on the yacht.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Who Can Go on a Skippered Yacht Charter?&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Many people think hiring a skipper is quite expensive, but that is not the case. It is typically more affordable than you think. Anyone can go on a skippered yacht charter, but it is perfect for the following people:&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;ul&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Those who have no experience in sailing and don't know how to sail a yacht or are not comfortable with it&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;For larger yachts with more people because someone with professional knowledge is required in such cases&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;When the destination is far&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Those who want to explore, be out in the ocean and relax with family and friends&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Those who are visiting a destination for the first time and want to know more about its waters&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;New sailors who want to learn more about sailing from professionals&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/ul&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Things You Should Know&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Do you want to know more about what is involved in a skippered yacht charter? If you are considering getting a skippered yacht charter for your next vacation, here's what you should know:&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;ol class="bg-li"&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;</p>
			<p>You are Responsible for Your Skipper's Food and Accommodation</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;For the duration of your trip on the yacht with a skipper, you will need to make sure that they get private accommodation, food, and drinks. There should thus be enough space and food in the yacht for all the people on the yacht, including the crew and skipper. Many yachts have separate designated skipper rooms with their own entrance, which can be great in maintaining your privacy.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;</p>
			<p>Skippers Will Give You Privacy</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;If you are worried about your privacy with a skipper, you should not. The skippers are there to sail the yacht and provide you with guidance, all the while maintaining your privacy. Most skippers are only permitted to enter their own cabin and common areas on the yacht. You also don't have to take the skipper with you when you dine out unless you want to.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;</p>
			<p>Tipping Skippers</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Though tipping is not necessary, it is preferred and recommended when sailing with a skipper. It is recommended to give them 5% to 15% of the charter price as a tip.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;</p>
			<p>Catering and Cleaning Needs</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Your skipper is there to sail the yacht and give you guidance on where to go, and that is it. If you want additional services, such as preparing and serving food, keeping the yacht clean, and more, you will need to add more crew members. You can consider getting a hostess for these tasks because they will cook, clean, and serve for you.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/ol&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Difference between Bareboat, Skippered or Crewed Yacht Charter: Which to Choose?&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;You might still be confused about what exactly a skippered yacht charter includes and the difference between bareboat, skippered, and crewed yacht charter. Let's clear the confusion now.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A bareboat yacht charter is when you take your yacht out for a ride and vacation on your own without a crew, skipper, or captain. It's just you, your friends and family, and the ocean. You only hire the boat, and you handle the rest. The excellent thing about this type of arrangement is that you have complete independence and control over your itinerary. You also get all the privacy you want.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;However, with a bareboat yacht charter, you are quite literally responsible for everything. This means that you will need to find the ideal yacht, make your itinerary, and gather all the necessary provisions on your own. Not just that, but sailing the yacht, checking it for damages and issues, checking the anchor are all part of your responsibility. And in case of emergencies, you will be the one dealing with them. This can get challenging and stressful for some people, especially those with no prior experience of sailing.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, you will not need to worry about any such emergency situations with a skippered yacht charter. The skipper will be responsible for checking the yacht for damages, checking the anchor, and dealing with any problems or emergencies. You will leave the yacht in the hands of a qualified professional who will know about the yacht and destination so that they can provide you with guidance. The only con with them is that you might have a language barrier with them, or you may not be able to form a close bond with them. Otherwise, the best idea is to go for a skippered yacht charter.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A crewed yacht charter takes the skippered yacht charter one step further by including other crew members besides the skipper, such as chefs, hostesses, and captain. The crew can be a two-person team or a larger group depending on the size of the boat. Larger boats typically contain 30 crew members with engineers, mates, scuba divers, and more. Even if you have a small crew, you can enjoy several advantages since they will take care of everything for you. They will arrange your provisioning, safety, breakfast, lunch, and prepare drinks. All your needs are taken care of with a crewed yacht charter.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;However, the biggest disadvantage of a crewed yacht charter is the cost, which is considerably high. Not only will you need to pay for each crew member, but also for their food and gratuity cost. Paying for one person is high in itself, but it can be significantly expensive for two or more.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Therefore, choosing between a bareboat, skippered, or crewed yacht charter entirely depends on your budget, preferences, your level of experience in sailing, and the size of the yacht.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Final Words&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;You can find a skippered yacht charter at nearly any yacht provider. They will likely provide you with good yacht deals that come with a skipper. Having such a professional on-board can save you a ton of hassle in terms of maneuvering the yacht, routes, and knowing all the best spots and hidden treasures of your destination. They might be costly, but they are definitely worth it.&lt;/p&gt; </p>
		</text>
	</dest>

	<dest>
		<thumb>top-tips-to-charter-a-yacht</thumb>
		<image>top-tips-to-charter-a-yacht</image>
		<link>top-tips-to-charter-a-yacht</link>
		<title>Top Tips To Charter A Yacht</title>
		<desc>Get advice for your yachting vacation.</desc>
		<text>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;When you charter a yacht, it gives you and your family and friends a secure and pleasant vacation atmosphere, offering the utmost privacy and independence, unlike going on a cruise ship. This will be a one-of-a-kind trip if you prepare properly. Your food, your schedule, and everything should be tailored to make your stay as enjoyable as possible.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Here are a few of our top tips to charter a yacht.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p><br /></p>
			<p>&lt;ol class="bg-li"&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Obtaining Yacht Insurance</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The deposit and skipper liability insurance are the two most essential insurances for yacht rental. This is also a good idea for groups of friends or couples to prevent future conflicts. Another excellent precaution is a skipper&amp;rsquo;s travel costs cancelation insurance, which ensures that if the skipper or the entire charter crew are unable to arrive at the location, the travel expenses are not lost. The section on charter insurances has more comprehensive information on the topic.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Selecting the Right Yacht</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Choosing the appropriate luxury boat is critical to a successful charter. Your charter specialist will provide you with the finest options for yachts that meet your needs, suit your budget, and provide you with the degree of comfort you want, as well as provide guidance on the entire process. You need to plan your vacation location, dates, length, the number of cabins you&amp;rsquo;ll need, and the money you&amp;rsquo;ve set aside for the private yacht charter in order to make the best match.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Yachts are available to fit virtually every demand or budget. Suppose you&amp;rsquo;re traveling with a group of couples and splitting the bill equally. In that case, we can help you select a boat that best fits your lodging needs or yachts with a plethora of amenities if you&amp;rsquo;re looking for an active vacation where the yacht is the ultimate destination.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The total capacity of charter guests permitted by law on most manned charter boats is 12. Some mega yachts, on the other hand, include designated room for extra supernumeraries, including a nanny, nurse, security guard, trainer, or personal assistant.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Think about the Food</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;You should carry fresh vegetables and fruits as well as staples like pasta, bread, meat, milk, cheese, rice, and eggs for a sailing vacation. You can create virtually anything with these components. As a result, it would be fantastic if you could bring these materials on board.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;On a sailing vacation, you should always pack some food. It is the greatest choice since you will not constantly have to return to the country to eat. Nothing prevents you from preparing delicious meals right on your yacht.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Even better, prepare your meals ahead of time and pack everything you&amp;rsquo;ll need. You may keep the meal in the refrigerator and prepare it as needed. We recommend taking meat, cheese, milk, grains, and eggs in addition to the basics. You can capture fresh fish or shellfish if you&amp;rsquo;re skilled or fortunate enough. However, if all you want to do is relax and enjoy your vacation, you may have it for a reasonable price.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Make the Most of Your Boat&amp;rsquo;s Amenities</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;If you have the financial means, invest in a boat with lots of facilities to keep you amused at all times. If you&amp;rsquo;ve never tried a stand-up paddleboard or a jet ski, now would be the time to do it. When you rent a boat, it&amp;rsquo;s also a good idea to bear in mind that it is an excellent opportunity to acquire new talents.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;If you like to do nothing during your vacation, an hour in the Jacuzzi while being given your favorite drinks may just be your idea of paradise. Alternatively, make use of the yacht&amp;rsquo;s outstanding multi-media system, which offers the newest movies and music in high-resolution and sound in opulent settings.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Make Smart Packing Choices</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;You may live in your bikini or sarong, dress fancy to go out, wear simple tank tops and shorts to stay onshore to walk, cycle, or ride horses. The trick to packing properly for a charter trip is to not bring too much, to pack clothing that can be used multiple times, and to remember that you&amp;rsquo;ll be out on the water, so coats or warm scarves should be included on your list.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Consider the weather in the area where you want to go on your charter. If you&amp;rsquo;re planning to spend time in the sun, sea, or sand, be sure to bring appropriate clothing. Most restaurants on the beach will expect you to dress in 'smart casual,' but others may ask for more formal attire and footwear.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Most charter boats require passengers to roam around with bare feet inside the boat and wear boat shoes on the deck, so keeping your toes clean should be your top concern! High heels and firm soles are strictly forbidden. For onshore trips, you may want to bring a pair of shoes. Consider bringing rubber water shoes if you plan on exploring reefs and rocky islands.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to bring your travel papers, any prescription medicines, and chargers for any of your electronic gadgets.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Have Fun with Your Team</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;It is important to choose the proper individuals for your trip no matter the destination. A charter vacation is a once-in-a-lifetime experience that should run as well as possible. As a result, assembling the proper 'team' is akin to casting for a great movie. Imagine traveling on an Atlantic crossing; everyone must be a good match for such a journey in order for the vacation to be a memorable one.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Of course, there are those yacht crews who prefer to live in the present and plan their itineraries as haphazardly as possible. This isn&amp;rsquo;t an issue if the entire party is on the same spontaneous page. However, it may be a good idea to plan the routes ahead of time. Everyone will be able to agree on the specifics and will know what to anticipate during the boat charter.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s critical to address all of the crew members&amp;rsquo; unique preferences and no-nos while arranging the charter, as well as decide on a budget that works for everyone. Of course, the location and the appropriate boat type for the cruising region are also critical.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;If all participants of your yacht charter communicate their expectations before the trip, everyone&amp;rsquo;s interests will be taken into account. For example, one party member may like to do a lot of traveling and tour antique sites, while another may enjoy spending the whole day cruising or at anchor. There are some who are quite content to anchor at sea each night and cook for themselves, while others like to moor up in port every evening and go out to locate a pleasant restaurant. As a result, if everyone prepares ahead a bit, the appropriate compromises may be made, and peace can be assured.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;You may steer the charter boat yourself if you have adequate expertise. The second alternative is to hire a skipper who is available locally. In certain rare circumstances, such as when the seas are difficult to navigate, some providers hire a skilled skipper to guide the boat for the first few days till the charterer has gained enough confidence to take over. The benefit is that the captain will have extensive local knowledge and will be able to arrange all routes. A stewardess on a larger yacht might add even more to everyone&amp;rsquo;s full relaxation by handling shopping, cooking, and cleaning, as well as helping the captain during maneuvers.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/ol&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;In Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Preparing properly when you charter a yacht is necessary since it can ensure a successful vacation. You need to take care of some basic things in order to make sure that everyone is safe and happy on the entire vacation.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			
		</text>
	</dest>

	<dest>
		<thumb>how-to-plan-a-yacht-party</thumb>
		<image>how-to-plan-a-yacht-party</image>
		<link>how-to-plan-a-yacht-party</link>
		<title>How To Plan A Yacht Party</title>
		<desc>Tips for planning a party on a yacht.</desc>
		<text>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;When it comes to having a ball with friends, family, and other loved ones, nothing can beat having a yacht party! While there are many types of private parties, including birthday celebrations at home, intimate or extravagant cocktail nights, etc., it's safe to say that [partying in the middle of the sea on a private vessel has an undeniably charming appeal to it!&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;What's more is that everyone can throw a party in a hotel or arrange a private restaurant event, but not many people think of throwing a private yacht party. It isn't just an exclusive event for your loved ones, but it also gives you multiple opportunities to take exquisite, 'gram-worthy pictures.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;With that said, throwing a yacht party is no mean feat, and not everyone knows the effort and thought that goes into organizing a successful and memorable yacht party. You need the right tips for planning a yacht party to avoid party failures, such as a yacht that is too small to accommodate all your guests, a party date mix-up, lack of food, and more issues. With proper guidance, you can seamlessly plan the party so that you and your guests can head out to sea and enjoy the exquisite view and the fresh breeze.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;So, without any ado, let's take a look at nine tips for planning a yacht party!&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;9 Tips for Planning a Yacht Party&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Here are nine yacht rental party tips that you will need to throw the ideal yacht party:&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;ol class="bg-li"&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Plan a Few Weeks Ahead</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;When it comes to throwing a yacht party, you need to start the preparations at least a few weeks before the party date. Firstly, you should decide the kind of party you want to throw for your guests and choose a theme for it. For instance, you could celebrate a birthday on a yacht, throw an engagement party, or even host a swanky evening soiree for charity. As long as you have a clear vision of the type of party you want to throw, it will help you plan the other aspects of your yacht party seamlessly.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;You will also need to find the ideal date and time for your party. For instance, if it's a surprise birthday celebration, you would ideally want to surprise the person on the day of their birthday and at a time that would suit them the best.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Similarly, you will need to check with your prospective guests about their availability for any particular date you might have in mind for the sort of party that you throw. You certainly wouldn't want to throw a party where half of your guests' list wouldn't be able to show up because of prior commitments.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Choose a Party Theme</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Even though having a yacht party theme is not essential, having one will certainly add some much-needed pizzazz to your party! Choosing a theme can also help you select other aspects of the party, from the décor and food to the dress code. When selecting a theme for your yacht party, make sure that it is age-appropriate, easily created and followed on a yacht, and appropriate for the kind of party you have in mind. However, most importantly, it should be a theme that you and your guests will love.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Create a Party Checklist</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;When planning a yacht party, make sure to create a checklist of everything you will need to make your party a success. This list could include party food, décor, entertainment, cutlery, music, and more. Your checklist of items will certainly vary depending on the type of party you plan on throwing.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;For instance, if you're celebrating a birthday or wedding, make sure to include cake, candles, related cutlery, drinks, and other relevant items. Similarly, if it's a fourth of July party, you will need fireworks and relevant paraphernalia.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;So, list down everything you can think of and check with a few trusted friends to make sure that you do not forget something. If you're on a time crunch, make sure to create deadlines for arranging each item so that you have everything organized before the party.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Set a Budget</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Once you have created a checklist, decide on a budget that will work for you. If you're throwing the party with friends, make sure to choose a budget that everyone agrees with. This way, you will not put any unnecessary financial burden on your friends. Your budget for the party will certainly be determined by the yacht party rental you choose, the number of guests you invite, the variety and price of the food items you keep, entertainment options, décor, and more.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;You can start budgeting by allocating a rough cost to each aspect of the party. When arranging each party item, make sure to stay within your allocated budget. This way, when you're done arranging everything, you can make sure that your party doesn't cost you more than you can afford to spend.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Delegate Preparation Duties</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;One of the best tips for planning a yacht party is to not become a lone ranger! After all, organizing a yacht party by yourself can be time-consuming and tiresome. So, make sure to get a few friends and loved ones involved and delegate party prep duties to them. For instance, if you know someone who's great with food, hand over the food preps to them. Similarly, if you have an artist or creative individual in your midst, give them the task of decorating the yacht.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Depending on your budget, you can hire a professional event organizer for your yacht party. When choosing an event organizer, don't forget to read reviews and select someone who will respect your vision and turn it into a striking reality.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Make a Guest List </p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Your next step should be to make a guest list. Start by deciding whether you will invite a small group or a large group to your party. It will largely depend on your budget, the sort of party you want to throw, and your reason for organizing the party. For instance, if you're organizing a charity event, you would likely want to invite as many influential people as possible so that you can raise a lot of money for your cause. Alternatively, if you're throwing an intimate party or a small getaway brunch, you'd likely want to involve only the most relevant people or your closest friends. Once you have settled on the number of guests, you can send out your yacht party invitations. Make sure that your guests RSVP to the invite so that you can book a suitable yacht to accommodate them.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Find a Yacht That Suits Your Needs</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Once you have decided the number of guests, your budget, date, and more, start looking for a yacht party rental that will be suitable for your party. Make sure to find a decent yacht that is within your budget and can easily accommodate your guests. Create a criterion that you can follow when choosing the ideal yacht.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;For instance, do you want it to be a double-story vessel with an expansive deck? Do you want your chosen yacht rental to have a sound system? You can ask pertinent questions to the rental company to find a yacht that works best for you. Make sure to find one that you can rent for a minimum of four hours so that you can have a relaxing and fun time without worrying about the rental duration.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Plan Fun Party Activities</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Nothing screams a fun yacht party more than watersports! Depending on the theme of your party, you will need to arrange entertainment options and fun games for your guests. For instance, you can arrange floats, a karaoke system, snorkels, and more for your guests. If you're throwing a bachelorette party, you can arrange risqué games to make your party memorable. You can also bring a Bluetooth speaker to blast some music in the middle of nowhere! When arranging music, make sure to choose songs and playlists that suit the mood of the party.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Arrange Food &amp; Drinks</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Lastly, you will need to choose some killer food items and beverages for your party. You can choose to prepare homemade food and drinks for the party, depending on the number of guests you are inviting and your food choices. However, you can also order BBQ or hire caterers for the party. When arranging the food, make sure that it aligns with your overall theme and includes items that all your guests can have. For instance, if you have Muslim friends onboard, make sure to include Halal food options for them. Also, don't forget about the dietary restrictions and requirements of your guests. To be on the safe side, keep some vegan and vegetarian options as well.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/ol&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;The Bottom Line&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Throwing a yacht party is no joke! You need to be fully prepared to ensure that you don't come across any preventable issues and throw a party where your guests can have a grand time. The only way to throw a memorable yacht party is to prepare for it thoroughly and account for all the things that can go wrong. Follow the aforementioned tips for planning a yacht party that your guests will remember for ages to come!&lt;/p&gt;</p>
		</text>
	</dest>

	<dest>
		<thumb>guide-to-long-term-yacht-charter-in-the-caribbean</thumb>
		<image>guide-to-long-term-yacht-charter-in-the-caribbean</image>
		<link>guide-to-long-term-yacht-charter-in-the-caribbean</link>
		<title>Guide To Long Term Yacht Charter In The Carribean</title>
		<desc>How to have the tropical vacation of a lifetime.</desc>
		<text>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Have you ever been on vacation and wished you could stay there for longer and not come home?&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;With a long-term yacht charter, you can do exactly that. And what better place to spend a couple of weeks at than the Caribbean?&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The calm, serene, and sparkling blue waters of the Caribbean make for the perfect getaway on a yacht charter. Take your vacation to the next level by renting a yacht for a few weeks, cruising along these waters, and island hopping in the Caribbean. There is perhaps no other better vacation than this one. Live the dream by escaping your daily worries and catching a yacht in the majestic islands of the Caribbean.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The Caribbean is the best island yacht charter destination in the world since it holds nearly 700 islands. Of course, on a long-term yacht charter vacation, you will not be able to explore all these islands, but you will explore plenty that will leave you with an incredible time and indelible memories.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Whether you are vacationing with friends or family, a Caribbean yacht charter is a perfect haven for relaxation and adventure. This is why we have compiled this thorough guide that tells you everything you need to know about planning a long-term Caribbean yacht charter vacation.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Why Plan a Trip to the Caribbean?&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The Caribbean is the second most popular destination for luxury yacht charters, and we know exactly why. It is perhaps the best place to charter your yacht, whether on your own or with a crew. With its sparkling waters, warm glow of sunsets, best drinks, delicious cuisine, and a plethora of culture, there are so many reasons to visit this incredible place. No other island destination in the world offers as many advantages as The Caribbean does.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The Caribbean is filled with powder white pristine beaches and flora and fauna that hold a plethora of exotic birds, butterflies, and wildlife. Here, you can also discover outstanding diving spots that are perfect for snorkeling and swimming with the fish. Moreover, the culture of the Caribbean is also unlike any other because it is a vibrant mix of French, Danish, Dutch, Portuguese, and Spanish heritage. This not only results in absolutely delicious cuisine but also fantastic nightlife.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Whether you are looking for a romantic getaway, some solitude, thrilling adventure, or simply a fun time with friends and family, The Caribbean has it all.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h2&gt;Where to Go in the Caribbean?&lt;/h2&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The Caribbean is huge, and you have nearly 700 islands to choose from, which can get quite confusing. Typically, the Caribbean can be split into two main areas; the Greater Antilles and the Lesser Antilles. You can choose to island hope and travel within either of these. The Greater Antilles is comprised of popular destinations like the Dominican Republic, Jamaica, and Cuba, whereas the Lesser Antilles is home to famous destinations such as The British Virgin Islands, Barbuda, and Antigua.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;If you are torn between where to go or simply to wonder what the best destinations for a long term yacht charter in the Caribbean are, here is a list of our top picks:&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;ol class="bg-li"&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Antigua</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;If you are looking for some solitude and privacy, the ideal place for you to go to in the Caribbean is Antigua. With powdery white beaches, stunning coral reefs, and a myriad of beautiful bays, you can expect to have a relaxing time there. Besides lounging at the bays and beaches, some of the best activities are snorkeling in the sparkling blue waters here.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Barbados</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Barbados was under British rule till 1966, which is why you can expect to see an eclectic mix of British, Caribbean, and African culture here in the form of their cuisine and entertainment. Barbados offers its tourists a host of the best diving spots and beaches in the entire region. You can also explore the colonial town of Bridgetown or visit the mangrove forests to see exotic wildlife.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;The British Virgin Islands</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;If you are considering a long-term bareboat yacht charter experience in the Caribbean, we recommend going to the British Virgin Islands. Here, the water and winds are comparatively calmer and reliable. In fact, BVIs are often regarded as the best place for your first bareboat yacht charter because of their well-established sailing infrastructure and variety of yachts to choose from. They are also great for island hopping as you can visit Norman Island, Peter Island, Jost Van Dyke, and Anegada, to name a few.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Dominica</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;If you want to be blown away by stunning natural reserves, forests, and greenery, consider visiting Dominica. You will likely never get bored of its nature, free-flowing waterfalls, untouched forest, and stunning flora and fauna. Dominica is not just the youngest island in the Caribbean but also considered the "Nature Island." Besides being a natural haven, it is also ideal for adrenaline junkies because you can hike, trek, cycle, and raft.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Grenada</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;An island filled with mountains and rolling hills, Grenada is certainly one of the most picturesque islands in the Caribbean. It includes stunning waterfalls, beaches, bays, and mountain lakes. But that's not all; it is also host to fragrant spice trees and exotic plants and flowers. Grenada is also touted as one of the friendliest places in the region, which makes it an ideal destination on a long-term yacht charter.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Martinique</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Often regarded as the 'little bit of France in the Caribbean' is the ideal destination for a long-term yacht charter for those who enjoy French cuisine and culture. It is also great for bareboat yacht charters because of the excellent sailing infrastructure and plenty of yachts to choose from. You can hop from one island to the other or explore one end of the Martinique region to the other, exploring the many wonders offered by the island.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;St Lucia</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;This is certainly an adventure and thrill-seekers haven because it is filled with one of the best diving spots, rainforests, and the world's only drive-in volcanic crater. There are simply tons to explore on this wonderful island. The small and lush tropical gem is predominantly unknown, which means that you can enjoy privacy and solitude without having to worry about other tourists. With incredible natural reserves, a volcano, beach, colorful birds, and rainforests, what more could you ask for on your long-term yacht charter?&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/ol&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;How to Plan a Long Term Caribbean Yacht Charter&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Now that you have learned about the most popular destinations in the Caribbean region, it's time to discuss you can plan a long-term yacht charter there. Long-term yacht charters typically including renting and staying in a yacht for a couple of weeks or months. People tend to stay on the island while sailing the yacht to travel from one destination or the other. Others tend to rent larger yachts to stay in.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Moreover, you will also need to choose whether to get a bareboat, skippered, or crew yacht charter. A Bareboat involves no crew member, so you need to sail the yacht and look after it yourself. With a skippered yacht charter, you can explore the Caribbean with a local skipper who sails the boat for you and gives you guidance on where to go and how to plan your routes. Lastly, a crew yacht charter involves a captain, skipper, hostess, and chef who take care of all of your needs, so you have nothing to worry about.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The Caribbean is filled with sunshine all year round, and the daily temperature is primarily warm, so you don't have to worry about when to go. Most people tend to travel to the region during the driest seasons between December and April. The region is filled with tourists during Christmas and New Year time. Whenever you go, we recommend that you make all the necessary bookings well in advance.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The main Caribbean sailing season thus runs through November till July. The summer months are much warmer with sunshine but comparatively less crowded. If you plan to visit Cuba or the Bahamas, you must ensure that you are not traveling during the hurricane season. The rest of the destinations in this region are rarely ever hit with hurricanes.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The next step in planning your long-term Caribbean stay is to plan all the routes. You will need to take a flight to the region. After this, you can go to the yacht you have rented and start your vacation there. You will need to plan your route with a crew member or with the company you rent your yacht from to help you figure out what the best possible route around your destination is.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Lastly, plan your itinerary in advance before commencing your vacation. This will save you the hassle of deciding what to do later on. Since you will likely go for a longer time, you can easily make a list of a few spots you want to see and activities you want to do and then follow it over the course of your stay.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Final Words&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A long-term yacht charter to the Caribbean requires plentiful planning beforehand. Nonetheless, you will have a splendid time as you get acclimated to the region, explore the best and most stunning spots, and relax under the golden sun. Wherever in the Caribbean you go, you will likely be mesmerized by its beauty and the friendly locals. Don't forget to make your bookings and plan your itinerary before you leave.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
		</text>
	</dest>

	<dest>
		<thumb>how-to-plan-your-yacht-charter-min</thumb>
		<image>how-to-plan-your-yacht-charter</image>
		<link>how-to-plan-your-yacht-charter</link>
		<title>How To Plan Your Yacht Charter</title>
		<desc>Things to think about when chartering a yacht.</desc>
		<text>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Decide how many people will go on your yachting trip&lt;/strong&gt; - Most yacht charters have 6-12 friends and/or family members. There are various safety laws that make 12 the limit, no matter how big the yacht is.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When will you travel?&lt;/strong&gt; Many destinations are only available for the warmer half of the year, while others are available year-round. Your yacht charter broker will discuss the options with you.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What will be the duration of your trip?&lt;/strong&gt; Most charters are 5-10 days, and start and end at noon. So as not to feel stressed or rushed, many yachters arrive at the point of embarkation a day early.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where will you go on your vacation?&lt;/strong&gt; Each destination is known for certain features. Do you want white sandy beaches? Golf? Scuba diving or snorkeling? Fishing? Jungle adventures? History and culture? Delicious local cuisine? Your yacht charter broker will help you with all of this.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What size yacht do you need?&lt;/strong&gt; This will depend on several factors, such as how many people are in your party. And, do you want a pool or hot tub? A master suite on the main deck? A helipad (this will require a superyacht or megayacht)? Wifi? Do you need a tender (a small boat to take you to shore)?&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Should you buy trip insurance?&lt;/strong&gt; This covers your financial losses if your trip is cancelled. Also discuss other insurance options with your charter broker.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Visa requirements&lt;/strong&gt; - Each country has different regulations, depending on the nationality of each charter guest, so make sure to check on this ahead of time.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferences&lt;/strong&gt; - Prior to the trip, each member of your party will fill out a Preference Questionnaire to give the crew information about the food, drinks, and activities you like. You can be very specific ('no onions', vegan, 'lots of chocolate', etc.), and list any food allergies and brand preferences. Also, do you want the crew to dress in formal uniforms? How attentive do you want them to be?&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Make a checklist&lt;/strong&gt; - What are you going to bring on your trip? Use a duffle bag or collapsible bag. Check ahead about what shoes you should wear. Many yachts require you to go barefoot on deck, to protect the carpeting and flooring from getting marked. No high heels or shoes with dark soles. Remember to bring sun screen, a wind jacket, hats, and other personal travel items.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
		</text>
	</dest>

	<dest>
		<thumb>what-to-pack-for-a-yacht-charter</thumb>
		<image>what-to-pack-for-a-yacht-charter</image>
		<link>what-to-pack-for-a-yacht-charter</link>
		<title>What To Pack For A Yacht Charter</title>
		<desc>Pre-cruise preparation. Make sure you are properly prepared for your vacation.</desc>
		<text>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Kudos to you, my friend, if you re one of the few people who have perfected the art of quick and stress-free trip packing. For those who haven t, excitement for a much-anticipated vacation soon fades once a bare piece of baggage stares back at you. &lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, you ve decided to make the most of your vacation time. Packing for an adventurous island-hopping vacation is surprisingly simple when you have an excellently prepared checklist to guide you through the dreaded task. The tips below will help you prepare like a pro, whether it s your very first or the sixteenth time undocking for an amazing yacht charter trip.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Essentials to Pack for Yacht Vacation&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The following is a list of your fundamental necessities, which you should never leave home without:&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h4&gt;Documents for Travel&lt;/h4&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;It may seem obvious, but it has occurred to the greatest of us, so do remember to bring:&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;ul&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Your travel documents&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Proper identification documents&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Any other travel papers you ll need throughout your journey&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/ul&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Having cash on hand when boating is important. This will cover everything from airport taxis to fast purchases at any beachfront gift store and ensure you are prepared if paying via your credit card is not possible.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h4&gt;Clothing&lt;/h4&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Since it is so hot in tropical destinations like the Caribbean islands, you will spend much of your time onboard your own boat in a swimming suit. Swimwear with appropriate clothing over it is absolutely fine even when you go ashore – t-shirt, sundress, shorts, or tank tops. For maximum comfort, select items made of dry-fit cloth wherever feasible. If you intend to dine at one of the fine dining establishments, bring one or more clothes for going out, depending on your personalized cruise schedule.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Pack jackets, gloves, and other winter clothes if you re going on a cruise to a significantly colder area, such as Alaska.  For simpler cabin storage, pack light and use soft-sided baggage or a medium to large-sized duffel bag.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h4&gt;Shoes&lt;/h4&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Since you ll be walking about barefoot on board, some flip-flops or sandals are perfect for sliding on and off when you go ashore. If you plan on trekking, bring a pair of sneakers with you. For colder locations or trekking plans, sturdy, comfortable footwear are also a smart option.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h4&gt;Accessories&lt;/h4&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;As a general rule, it s best to leave the jewelry at home. Hats may be fashionable and provide sun protection, but keep the wind element and luggage “crushing” in mind when choosing a hat. A strap that can be adjusted is excellent.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Pack a good pair of sunglasses, ideally polarized, for better eye protection and viewing enjoyment. If you re prone to misplacing sunglasses, though, don t bring your most valuable pair. It is worthwhile to get a pair of sunglasses specifically for your charter trip.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h4&gt;Toiletries&lt;/h4&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Bring all of your personal belongings. Because the storage space in the bathroom is limited, we highly suggest bringing travel-sized toiletries or liquids. Larger goods, such as bug repellant and sunscreen, can be bought at your destination too.  Additionally, you will be able to avoid having to check your baggage.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h4&gt;Dry Bags&lt;/h4&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;It s a good idea to put small gadgets like cameras and mobile phones in dry bags before putting them in the backpack or beach tote before coming onshore.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Optional Objects to Pack for Your Yacht Vacation&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;While the following items aren t absolutely essential, it is still a good idea to take some of the following items to make your trip more enjoyable.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h4&gt;Playing Cards&lt;/h4&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The whole party may enjoy a normal deck of cards or a game of Cards Against Humanity. There will undoubtedly be plenty of laughter and good moments!&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h4&gt;Cup Cooler&lt;/h4&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;In the blazing heat, ice melts quickly. Furthermore, it is a precious and scarce charter resource. Your ice will stay frozen, and your drink will stay colder for longer in a stainless steel tumbler!&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h4&gt;Flag&lt;/h4&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Show off your local pride or a favorite sports team by hoisting a flag to add a unique flair to your rental boat.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h4&gt;Hammock&lt;/h4&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Install your own “hang out and chill” hammock to relax in throughout your relaxing Caribbean cruise trip.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h4&gt;Carabineers&lt;/h4&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;What other option do you have for securing your ultra-relaxing hammock? Carabineers may also be used to secure different things while on the move.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h4&gt;Star Finder&lt;/h4&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Use a star finder to bring out the inner astrologer in you and enjoy stargazing nights from the comfort of your own little paradise.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h4&gt;Lanterns That Inflate&lt;/h4&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;These inflatable solar-charged lanterns provide just the perfect amount of “mood lighting” ambience on the sea while you re in the middle of the sea, so kick back and relax. &lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h4&gt;GoPro&lt;/h4&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A GoPro is easy to use and allows you to record every memorable holiday moment above and below the sea.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h4&gt;Reliefband&lt;/h4&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;If you re prone to feeling “green” at sea, a chargeable Reliefband may help you feel better in minutes on the waves with no side effects.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h4&gt;Inflatable Rafts&lt;/h4&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Snorkeling equipment is often provided with the charter, and water toys like noodles, paddleboards, and kayaks may be rented upon arriving. An inflatable raft is a great bonus to have aboard. Once aboard, inflate it, attach it to the yacht s stern, grab your favorite boat drink, and relax while floating away from your worries!&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;What Should You NOT Pack for a Trip to the Caribbean?&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Learning what to pack for a yacht charter is just as essential as learning what not to pack. Overpacking non-essential things such as:&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;ul&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Cookware and utensils&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Use of a GPS and other navigational aids&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;First-aid kits (optional)&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;High-end or heritage jewelry&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Towels, linens, and pillows&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/ul&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pre-Cruise Preparation Tips&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;ol class="bg-li"&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Inspect The Boat s Condition</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;It doesn t matter which yacht you are going on the cruise with; make sure the boat is in proper working order before setting sail. This comprehensive tour covers the rudder, engine, valves, rigging, safety equipment, through-hulls, and more, allowing you to sail in complete safety.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Fill the fresh water and fuel tanks, as well as a jerrycan for the yacht s tender if it has an outboard engine, before leaving the dock; the readings must clearly show that they are full.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Also, make sure the battery is completely charged and that the gas bottles have enough fuel.&lt;/p&gt;    </p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Onboard Safety Equipment</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Depending on the type of cruising you re planning, such as a coastal or offshore vacation, you ll need to adhere to safety regulations and have a list of equipment required by law on board. &lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Set up netting on the lifelines if you are vacationing with kids on board, and bring life vests that are tailored to their size. A lifeline and harness attached to the boat are highly recommended if you plan to cruise alone or at night.&lt;/p&gt;    </p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;The Temperature</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A holiday on a boat, like any other travel, should be properly planned out. If you intend to visit new locations during your trip, read the nautical manuals even more thoroughly.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Check the maritime forecast online or ask the harbormaster, and bring local charts with you to map out your whole route ahead of time. Tides and current maps and any information from the Almanac or an updated coastline guide are also helpful.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;You ll also want to share your navigation plans with someone who will stay onshore, including stopovers, the destinations and the timeline of your stays&lt;/p&gt;    </p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Check on the Crew</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Make sure that everyone in the crew is in excellent health so that you can enjoy your vacation. Bring a new first-aid kit on board to respond to every potential injury such as cuts or burns, and make sure to bring sunscreen and other essentials for sunburns. At sea, the sun is dangerous, so it is best to avoid a sunstroke than to treat one.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Whatever the circumstances, seasickness may strike without notice, necessitating the use of a bucket that can be readily obtained from shore. Avoid circumstances when you are tired, hungry, cold, or thirsty at all costs.&lt;/p&gt;    </p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Onboard Comfort</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt; Most yachts are renowned for their classic styling and spacious interiors.  Multiple practical storage spaces are included inside the boats to make stashing and accessing your luggage and personal belongings in your staterooms a breeze.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;We recommend that you pack all of your personal belongings in soft-sided bags to save room after dumping them into the compartments onboard.&lt;/p&gt;    </p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;On-Board Comfort</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;There are numerous readily available storage spaces aboard where you can stock up on supplies. Ask every one of the crew members regarding their preferences before leaving the dock, and draw up a list of dishes ahead of time.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;You should not skip meals while at sea because you will be physically active all day and/or all night. You ll be exposed to the harsh sun and the sea salt that will dehydrate you. Make sure the whole crew has plenty of water, fresh vegetables and fruits, and foods with carbohydrates to keep up with their daily activities.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Ask the harbormaster to see what local supply stores and food stores are available at each dock. &lt;/p&gt;    </p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/ol&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;In Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Now that you know what to pack for a yacht charter, we hope that you enjoy your cruise vacation! Properly preparing for the vacation will reduce the risk of unsavory incidents and result in a successful, enjoyable trip.&lt;/p&gt; </p>
		</text>
	</dest>

	<dest>
		<thumb>how-yacht-charters-work</thumb>
		<image>how-yacht-charters-work</image>
		<link>how-yacht-charters-work</link>
		<title>How Yacht Charters Work</title>
		<desc>Frequently asked questions about yacht travel.</desc>
		<text>
			<p>&lt;h5&gt;Q. How is a yacht charter different than a yacht rental?&lt;/h5&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. They are similar, but a charter comes with a captain and crew to plan everything for you and cater to your every need. Kind of like being on a private cruise ship.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h5&gt;Q. Why use a charter broker?&lt;/h5&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. Yacht rentals and sale work like real estate, where the owner pays the brokerage fee. It costs nothing extra for you to use a charter broker. You get their many years of industry expertise for free, to help guide you and make your boating trip the best vacation possible. They act as your concierge, finding the best destination and perfect yacht for you, answering your questions, and handling all of the legal/tax/permit/regulation/logistics issues. All Yachts.com vacations are handled in partnership with Oceanscape Yachts, which has been providing yacht charters since 2013.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h5&gt;Q. How much does a yacht charter cost?&lt;/h5&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. The price usually works out to $5,000-$10,000 per person, which is the base price plus 55%-65% for a provision allowance which covers food and beverages, tipping the crew, fuel, customs, docking, marina fees, and other similar expenses.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h5&gt;Q. How do meals on the boat work?&lt;/h5&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. The yacht will have a personal chef, and you give them a list of your likes, dislikes, and food allergies. You can even customize things, like by catching your own fish and having the chef cook it, or have a picnic on a private secluded beach.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h5&gt;Q. How is payment handled?&lt;/h5&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. 30% is due when you book the trip, the balance is due 30 days before you leave.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h5&gt;Q. What recreational equipment does the boat have?&lt;/h5&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. Most yachts come with fishing and snorkeling gear. Some also come with jet skis, paddleboards, and tenders (small boats).&lt;/p&gt;</p>
		</text>
	</dest>

	<dest>
		<thumb>top-reasons-to-consider-a-vacation-on-a-yacht</thumb>
		<image>top-reasons-to-consider-a-vacation-on-a-yacht</image>
		<link>top-reasons-to-consider-a-vacation-on-a-yacht</link>
		<title>Top Reasons To Consider A Vacation On A Yacht</title>
		<desc>Why rent a yacht?</desc>
		<text>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you love the ocean, sunsets, secluded islands, luxury, privacy, freedom, and an endless supply of local delicacies on your vacations? Well, then you should opt for yacht charter holidays!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Even if you've never set foot aboard a boat or yacht, a yacht charter allows you to experience the wonders of the ocean and your travel destination in style. Moreover, you don't need to learn how to sail to enjoy a yacht holiday. After all, the yacht you book for your vacation will come with a captain (and a chef!) who will steer your vehicle wherever you want to go. A yacht vacation marries all the finest elements of holidays into one memorable experience.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;So, if you love the idea of an oceanfront holiday as much as we do, read on to discover what makes yacht holidays so memorable!&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Reasons to Enjoy Yacht Charter Holidays&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Here are ten reasons why yacht charter holidays are the best type of holidays you can take with your loved ones:&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;ol class="bg-li"&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;The Experience Is Truly Magical</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Yacht charter holidays offer a one-of-a-kind experience that you will remember for a lifetime. When renting a yacht, you will have the opportunity to drop anchor off an undeveloped, secluded isle with crystal-clear waters and fine sands, with no one in sight, except for you and your loved ones. You can enjoy the beautiful sunsets and sunrises, go for a swim, start a bonfire, and enjoy the sound of the waves lapping against your yacht. There's a beautiful sense of freedom and tranquility that you can experience on private yacht vacations, making it a must experience for all sea and island lovers.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;You Are In Charge</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Another wonderful reason to spend your holidays aboard a chartered yacht is that you have complete control over your itinerary. You will set the mood for your holiday and journey with complete assistance from the captain of your vessel. Unlike a cruise ship, you won't have to follow the itinerary of the company.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;You will have the freedom to go to shallow, remote, private bays and covers or explore yacht holiday hotspots, such as White Bay in the British Virgin Islands. Alternatively, you can enjoy a bit of both. It all depends on your and your loved ones' plans and whims. Moreover, depending on the length of your rental agreement, you can stay at one place however long you want and explore as many places as you want.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;No Hassle of Mass Tourism</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Charting yacht vacation rentals enables you to have exclusive access to all the remote islands and out-of-the-way gulfs you want to visit while escaping the less-than-relaxing atmosphere of mass tourism and the humdrum of big cruise ships and chain hotels. You also get to avoid the tourist crowds to have a relaxing time.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Additionally, when charting a yacht for your holiday, you don't have to worry about being left behind by your cruise ship as it leaves for the next island. It's especially useful for people who want to travel with their kids and explore all water sports and fun activities before sailing away.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;So, bid adieu to the world of traffic jams, repeated packing and unpacking, check-ins and check-outs, and the gut-wrenching feeling of leaving a heavenly island when all you want to do is take all its beauty in peacefully for the next few hours or days. With your rented yacht, you can visit national parks, explore private coves, snorkel in the shallow water, and discover beautiful hidden gems in the ocean at your convenience and schedule.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Free Sailing Lessons</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in sailing, a memorable yacht holiday is all you need to satisfy your interest. It's because when you rent a yacht, your captain may allow you to steer the vessel from time to time. However, if you plan to take ailing lessons from the captain, make sure to note that in your trip preferences, and rent a yacht whose captain will be willing to entertain your requests.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Moreover, you can also ask as many questions as you want regarding jibing, tacking, and sailing in general. It's a wonderful activity for kids as well. They will benefit from a casual sailing lesson, which will surely result in a memorable holiday for them. But remember that these lessons don't come with certifications and are just for fun.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Impressive Customized Service</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Yacht charter holidays are incredibly luxurious and offer customized services. Depending on your budget, you can have a dedicated, professional crew attending to your every need. You have a reliable captain, engineer, first mate, stewardess, chef, housekeeper, and deckhand managing every feature of the yacht and making your holiday as relaxing and enjoyable as possible.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;All of these people managing different aspects of your holiday is exceptionally helpful when you're traveling with infants or kids. Instead of making your holiday stressful and stretching you out thin, these people will take care of your multiple needs to ensure that you can have a fun, fulfilling time with your kids.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;The Benefit of Local Expertise</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;When you take some time off from work and go on a holiday, you want to have the time of your life. Ideally, you want to plan a holiday where you can have some much-needed fun and ample time to relax. Moreover, you want to ensure that your money is well spent. Renting yacht vacation rentals for your holiday will ensure all of that and offer you a lot more.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;When you book a yacht charter, you will have the assurance that the staff serving you, including the captain and chef, are the best in the business and have extensive knowledge about the destinations you plan to visit. You can expect nothing but the best from your captain, who will steer you to local destinations worth visiting. They will take you to the finest, most gorgeous islands and plan your itinerary keeping your wishes in mind while ensuring you have the best local experience.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Your Magical Floating Villa</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;When you're planning a private yacht vacation, you have the luxury of choosing the vessel you want to travel in with your loved ones. You get to decide who you want to travel with and what amenities you want. Depending on your budget, you can choose roomy staterooms with private en-suite facilities and an expansive saloon with a sofa, dining table, and the required media and entertainment facilities.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;You can also arrange for the right music, karaoke, food, water sports, and more amenities. Moreover, you can choose a yacht with a spacious deck and foyer, where all your loved ones can relax and have their own space. Essentially, you will have access to everything that you want in one place to make your holidays as wonderful as possible.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;A Unique Culinary Experience</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Charting a yacht for your holiday comes with the luxury of having access to a professional master chef who will cook everything you want them to. It's certainly an experience of a lifetime for all foodies. You get the opportunity to set your daily menus and request your favorite dishes.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;You will experience one-of-a-kind dining at sea under the twinkling stars in the middle of nowhere. Moreover, you can talk to your chef and make sure that they add the local cuisine to your menu. You can also ask them to teach you how to cook authentic local recipes or food you've always wanted to learn how to cook.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;An Affordable Luxury</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Contrary to popular opinion, yacht vacation rentals aren't too costly, especially when you consider all the amenities you get with them. Since the number of yacht lovers is growing worldwide and there is a continuous supply of different charter yachts, you can easily find yacht charters within your budget.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Plus, yachts come equipped with water toys, a bar, a lounge for cocktail hours, a nice, shady spot, and even a Jacuzzi. If you book the off-season, you can save a lot. Plus, make sure to do thorough research, and you will easily find a yacht that fits your budget while covering your needs and wishes.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;A Shared Sense of Togetherness</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Lastly, perhaps the best part about chartering a yacht for a holiday is that it allows you to have some much-needed private time with your loved ones, such as your kids, best friends, parents, or your partner. They are the perfect recipe for family togetherness and can help you make fantastic memories with the people you love.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;When you're enjoying the expansiveness of the universe in the middle of the sea with your favorite people, you tend to forget all about the daily struggles of life and enjoy some quality time with them. Depending on who you go with, you can enjoy watersports, swim with the dolphins, watch a movie under the stars, enjoy donut rides, or simply enjoy a beautiful sunset at the deck.  &lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/ol&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;The Bottom Line&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;When you charter a yacht for your holiday, you get to experience the world a little differently with the people you love. You don't have to rush through each holiday vacation and enjoy all sorts of water sports and the expansiveness of the ocean with your family or friends. You get to experience a relaxing holiday, away from other tourists, the way you want.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
		</text>
	</dest>

	<dest>
		<thumb>where-to-explore-on-a-yacht-in-greece</thumb>
		<image>where-to-explore-on-a-yacht-in-greece</image>
		<link>where-to-explore-on-a-yacht-in-greece</link>
		<title>Where To Explore On A Yacht In Greece</title>
		<desc>Tips on where to go on your Greek vacation.</desc>
		<text>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Greece's waters were designed to be visited by yacht. With dark pine trees mirrored off sparkling, blue seas and white beaches surrounding each coast, its complex shorelines conceal tremendous beauty behind every curve.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Thanks to hundreds of kilometers of pristine coasts, intimacy, and natural solitude are fundamental components of Greece's attractiveness. The temperate environment of the Eastern Mediterranean encourages yachting all year, with pleasant temperatures and splendid sunshine even in the fall months, all while maintaining the absolute safety that the Greek waters are renowned for. A cool summer wind permeates every one of the scores of charming islands and deserted islets to be explored, with a sweeping, clear sky. The combination of safe seas and a sense of isolation creates an unrivaled sailing experience.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;If you are wondering about destinations to explore on a yacht in Greece, we have outlined a handy list that you can look into for your yacht vacation.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Mykonos&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Mykonos is our overall winner since it offers the best of both worlds. It boasts the most beautiful beaches in Greece, with more than 20 stunning golden sand strips. These beaches appeal to a wide range of interests, including family beaches like Lia, fashionable beaches like Psarou, and calm beaches like AgiosSostis. Mykonos is located in the midst of the Aegean, making it quite easy to go either east or west if you want to later.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;When it comes to dining out, there are both inexpensive (try Bandana) and premium (Nobu) restaurants featuring food from all over the globe. Large yachts may anchor in two or three bays, most notably Psarou and Ornos. Of course, the islands are well-known for their nightlife and are considered one of the top party locations in the Mediterranean.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Rinia&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Rinia is a little island immediately south of Mykonos that caters to a certain market. It only has two or three tiny bays that large boats may utilize, but the bays are relatively deep, providing excellent weather protection. It offers the cleanest oceans in the world and a vast, wonderful sandy beach that is shallow for miles. Apart from a few old remains and the houses that farmers use when they visit by boat to care for their animals and land, there isn't much on the island.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Because there aren't any taverns or restaurants on the island, you may dine right on the beach in perfect privacy. Rinia is approximately 45 minutes by boat from Mykonos, so if you want a bit of a change, go to Rinia, rest, and enjoy the peace and quiet. You may immediately return to Mykonos if you get bored.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Koufonisia&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;This is really two islands located near Naxos and Mykonos. They have Rinia's calm and tranquil charm, yet there are just a few tiny hotels and tavernas. You can find some of the nicest coastlines in the Mediterranean on the upper island, as well as exquisite natural saltwater pools.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Finikas and FosFanari, two tiny rustic eateries, provide exclusively fresh fish obtained by local boats. Because there are just a few ferries and only two or three hotels, it is not extremely congested. If you want a beautiful sea to swim in, amazing beaches, plenty of fresh fish and lobsters, and relative seclusion, here is the place to go. A large harbor is available for boats up to 50 meters to anchor.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;The Cyclades&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The Cyclades are a very appealing sailing destination, owing to their close vicinity to Athens and the wide range of activities they offer. Greece's signature globally is the juxtaposition of their immaculate white dwellings by the deep blue color of the sea, not to forget the colors of its flag. Since the distance between the two islands is so short, a yachting vacation may involve a lot of ports and coves in a short amount of time. You could even cruise to a new island every day, but each one will need careful scrutiny.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Milos&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Further south, Milos provides stunning lunar vistas as well as dramatic beaches and coves accessible only by sail. It also contains one of the Mediterranean's biggest, virtually enclosed harbors, Adamas, which is safe in all types of weather and includes yacht-servicing facilities. If you visit Milos, the volcanic rock structures at Kleftiko just on the southern edge are a must-see.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;The Dodecanese Islands&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The ability to charter a boat locally makes cruising around distant Dodecanese simpler. The Meltemia, especially in the summer, makes sailing a particularly appealing choice for skilled sailors since the waters are unrestricted. However, don't expect to arrive in one day. Almost all of the islands have airports, making travel from Athens simple.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Apart from Kastellorizo, these islands, like the Cyclades, are very near to one another, allowing you to explore a new one every day. Please remember that every island has much to offer to justify a longer visit. This group has a lot to offer, from Rhodes, the chain's hub, to the little islands of Arki, Lipsi, and Agathonisi. Leros, Kos, and, of course, Rhodes all have wonderful marinas that can accommodate boats of all sizes.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Sporades&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The densely forested Sporades islands are fantastic for yachting. The greenest of the three islands, Skiathos, Skopelos, and Alonissos, is a toss-up. Its ‘brother' Skyros, to the south, is pine-wooded and rugged, with the white Hora on a barren peninsula seen from miles away and a modern harbor. The distance between the islands is quite short, and you can easily visit all of them, as well as their smaller deserted cousins within the Sporades Marine Park.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Crete&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Crete, the biggest of all Greek islands off the coast of Africa, is a fantastic sailing destination with enough to see and do. Unwind onboard and be mesmerized by the magnificent and dramatic hues of the water as you dock in secret coves and hidden beaches. When on land, see various snow-capped mountains, Minoan historical sites, green valleys, and beautiful beaches, dine at wonderful waterfront restaurants, and make lifelong memories.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Thassos&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Thassos is a lovely and peaceful island that is ideal for one full-day sailing adventure. See dolphins in Panagia, a preserved marine environment that is part of the Natura 2000 network on the southern shore, or view the spectacular rock formations and sea near Giola, farther east. Swim at Aliki and interact with Greek locals at Archodissa, a modest bar providing wonderful meals. Then proceed north to Paradise Beach along the shore. The lush islet called NisidaKinira is ideal for a quick exploring stop or a relaxing night at the little harbor of Thassos town's main port.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Ionian Islands&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Begin your voyage in the shimmering Ionian Sea by stocking up on provisions at Zakynthos' harbor before touring tiny beaches and pausing by small harbors for lunch or supper. Don't miss the Blue Caves or the famed Navagio Beach, both of which can only be reached by boat. Then go north to the stunning island of Kefalonia, which requires a minimum of two days to really appreciate. aThe friendly Ithaca and the satellite islands around it await you next, followed by the magnificent Lefkada – don't hurry to the next destination and take time to enjoy its numerous wonderful beaches. Before arriving in Corfu, stop in at Paxi and Antipaxi, which are known for their beautiful beaches and quiet coves.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Chios&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Chios is located on the eastern Aegean Sea, near Turkey. It's the fifth-largest of the islands around Greece, and it lacks the abundance of excellent sandy beaches seen on the top three. There are still beautiful locations to swim, including the Karfas and Maura Volia, and the water is very clean if a little cooler than usual due to its location within a stream of cold waters.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Instead, you'll discover wonderful medieval towns, as well as the castle and excellent museums, as well as the UNESCO World Heritage Site of Nea Moni, a Byzantine monastery founded in the 11th century. This island has a lot of history, so if you prefer historical civilizations, monasteries, and medieval towns, come here, rent a scooter, and have a look about.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Chios has a large airport, so you may ship the yacht ahead and fly in. There are very few international tourists on the island, but there are a lot of Greek visitors. Since there aren't as many high-end visitors or large yachts arriving, the cuisine is extremely fresh, and lobster is significantly cheaper than on Mykonos. Finally, you can even combine the tour with a charter flight to Turkey.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Vouliagmeni &lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Although it is not technically an island, we are putting it on the list since it has lately gained a lot of popularity recently. Vouliagmeni is a small beach town 13 miles south of Athens. If you reside in Athens, this is the best area to swim since the water is pure. Mooring in the harbor with a breathtaking view of the biggest hotel south of Athens, Astir Palace Hotel.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;This also has some of Greece's most costly real estate, making it very exclusive, and so many boats stop here for a few days before or after visiting Athens. If you have business in Athens, a helipad on top of the Astir Palace Hotel allows you to travel from the boat to the city every day. It's as though you're on an island rather than in a major city. It offers a beautiful sandy beach with excellent restaurants, particularly, and you may utilize all of the amenities.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;We hope now you have some idea of where to explore on a yacht in Greece! Have fun on your next cruise on the beautiful waters of Greece.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
		</text>
	</dest>

	<dest>
		<thumb>top-destinations-in-the-mediterranean-for-yacht-vacations</thumb>
		<image>top-destinations-in-the-mediterranean-for-yacht-vacations</image>
		<link>top-destinations-in-the-mediterranean-for-yacht-vacations</link>
		<title>Top Destinations In The Mediterranean For Yacht Vacations</title>
		<desc>Trying to decide where to go on your vacation?</desc>
		<text>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Is the Mediterranean calling you? Well, we are here to help you plan the finest yacht vacation this summer. We've compiled a list of standout itineraries and hand-picked choices of the top destinations in the Mediterranean for yacht vacations. &lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The Mediterranean has endless popular superyacht destinations, making it quite the treasure trove to visit, from the beautiful coastlines of Italy to the golden, sunny beaches of Balearics. It might be difficult to know where to start when planning a yacht charter trip in the Mediterranean, which is why we are here to help!&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;With the support of brokers and sailing experts, we've compiled this list of the top destinations in the Mediterranean for yacht vacations. Let's take a closer look now.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Ionian Islands&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The Ionian Islands comprise of seven major Greek islands as well as several smaller islets. Each island stretches 50 miles south to north along Greece's west coast and has its own distinct appeal for charter passengers. Corfu is the biggest of the Ionian Islands, as well as a quite popular tourist destination. You can immerse yourself in the traditional culture of Zante Island or feel the charm of the Blue Grotto and Smugglers Cover in Zakynthos.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Sardinia&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Sardinia is a blend of fashionable beach clubs, elegant shops, rich history, and natural beauty, making it one of the most spectacular Mediterranean yacht destinations. With a shoreline of secret coves and beautiful beaches, this yachting hideaway offers some of the greatest diving, snorkeling, and watersports. Celebrities promenade in luxury along the Porto Cervo beachfront, delivering a wonderful combination of elegance and beauty to the towns all along the Costa Smeralda. You can find some of the most enthralling anchorages in northern Sardinia.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Cala Granara in the Maddalenas, for example, has a bay in a wonderfully remote spot for superyachts to moor. Cala di Luna, set within a rocky promontory, is a beach connoisseur's dream, with spectacular snorkeling and adjacent ancient ruins for culture-lovers to investigate.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Sardinia's cuisine is hearty, tasty, and made with real Italian flare; local restaurants take pleasure in the availability of fresh ingredients from both land and sea -a fantastic source of inspiration for your yacht's chef to create unique, delicious meals on board.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Corsica&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The picturesque French island of Corsica, located near Sardinia and often visited as part of the same voyage, boasts some of the most stunning mountain landscapes in the Mediterranean.There are offshore anchorages and marina berthing to fully take in the environment, which is untamed and wild- yet unspoiled by man in parts. It has a French influence and is stunningly distinctive. The ports of Bonifacio and Calvi are known for their old town beauty and romance, while Lavezzi and Palombaggia are known for their stunning beaches and natural beauty. Corsica is a wonderful endpoint or stopover destination because of its strategic location between France and Italy.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Sicily&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;With a long summer season, getting a yacht charter in Sicily allows you to enjoy a fantastic cultural experience while sampling the wonderful local cuisine. The superb sailing areas in this Italian island are studded with breathtaking scenery, including beautiful towns, black sand beaches, and towering volcanoes, all of which are best enjoyed by boat.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Palermo, Sicily's dynamic capital city and old harbor, is a perfect start or end location for a yacht charter vacation in Sicily, overlooking the spectacular Monte Pellegrino. To the east, hilltop Taormina exudes flair, with terraced cafés offering breathtaking views over the gorgeous Isola Bella beach, which is flanked by the majestic Mount Etna. The seven beautiful Aeolian Islands, located to the north, are home to a variety of attractions. Visit Lipari for lively eateries, visit desolate Volcano for hot springs, and sail by active Stromboli for a light display of flowing lava at a safe distance from the yacht. &lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Malta&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Malta is a lesser-known yacht charter location, yet it is a wonderful Mediterranean jewel with a rich history. The Mediterranean sun will accompany you on your cruise to Malta, where charming harbors and ancient ruins nestle beside the stunning beaches and bays that are carved into the shoreline, only a short journey from Sicily. Gozo and Comino, two of the Maltese archipelago's 21 inhabited islands, provide some of the most isolated anchorages as well as some of the greatest watersports and diving spots. There are red sand beaches, rocky inlets, and crystal-clear seas that you can find here.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;The French Rivera&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The Southern region of France is one of the most renowned yacht charter locations in the world. Chartering a boat on the French Riviera gives you the opportunity to have an ultimate luxury lifestyle, from the lively clubs on the beaches of St Tropez to the subtle grandeur of Monaco's casino culture. From the luxury of your own charter boat, see perched medieval villages, take in the Mediterranean sun, and savor gastronomic delights.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Dive into crystal blue seas off the isolated Porquerolles, which are dotted with hidden coves, from your yacht's swim platform. Further up the coast, the lovely sheltered anchorages of Villefranche-sur-Mer and Cap Ferrat are always popular, while anchoring off at the Cap d'Antibes to get a delicious lunch at the Hotel du Cap-Eden-Roc is a trendy option too. Make use of the watersports equipment before arriving in Antibes to wander the charming cobblestone streets, dine at Michelin-starred restaurants in Cannes, or dance all night in vibrant Juan Les Pins. &lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;The Balearics&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The Balearic Islands are a collection of four Spanish islands that each have their own distinct personality, and a yacht charter is an ideal opportunity to see everything these sailing grounds have to offer.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Mallorca is home to the ancient city of Palma, as well as hilltop communities, hidden coves, and lush mountaintops. There are several scenic sites where you may take in breathtaking views before dining at one of the many good restaurants onshore. Menorca's whitewashed beaches are ideal for mountain biking and kayaking in the sea. The island is known for its hidden jewels, such as the sandy CalaMacarelleta and its breathtaking seafood at waterfront restaurants. Formentera, Formentera's younger sister, is dotted with peaceful anchorages, ideal for a relaxing Balearic sailing adventure and sunset cocktails on the deck.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The white beaches and rocky coves of Ibiza invite you to rest throughout the day, but after the sun sets, be ready to dance with the finest as world-class DJs throw amazing parties in Ibiza Town. Spend the day sailing around EsVedra, a rocky island protrusion with a magnetic pull, and finish off at the Blue Marlin for a taste of Balearic sounds. Of course, you'd be remiss if you didn't include Beso Beach on your list; the beach bar and restaurant is a true Ibizan institution located only a short distance from the SesIlletes in Formentera. Nothing but pleasant feelings and cool audiences are to be expected.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Croatia and Montenegro &lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Croatia has been one of the top destinations in the Mediterranean for yacht vacations and tourist destinations in recent years, thanks to its 1,200 islands.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Despite the popularity of locations like Dubrovnik, Split, and Hvar, it seems peaceful and remote from the deck of a luxury boat, with just 50 of its islands inhabited. On charter, it gives enough room for individuals wanting solitude and adventure.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The beautiful natural landscape is riddled with remains of a stormy past throughout its various islands, but since there is a lot to see, sticking to a charter schedule may be tough. Many people will take the time to explore Montenegro on the same vacation, which starts or ends at the Bay of Kotor and is known for its stunning natural beauty.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;The Turquoise Coast of Turkey&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Despite the current concerns about sailing safety in the Eastern Mediterranean, Turkey continues to provide some of the most beautiful cruising areas for yacht charters. It has more coastline to explore compared to other Mediterranean nations and a cultural blend of Western and Eastern customs. The Turquoise Coast is named after the adjoining blue-green colors of its sea and the horizon. It is widely recognized for its beautiful beaches and breathtaking mountain scenery. Guests can enjoy Fethiye's lively port, Marmaris' bustling town, and Lüdeniz's protected lagoon.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;During your journey, you should stop at Lebessos Winery. This restaurant, housed in a 400-year-old stone hamlet in the Kayakoy town (that has been abandoned since 1923), is Fethiye's gourmet dining leader. The venue receives bonus points for its cab service, which eliminates the need to schedule a shuttle.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The native food is traditional and wonderfully prepared; try the levissi chicken with spicy yogurt, soft lamb kleftiko, or honey-drenched figs. In addition, the restaurant has a wine cellar where you may experience Turkish wines.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;The Amalfi Coast &lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The Amalfi Coast, located just south of ancient Naples and embellished with technicolor cities, perched villages, and interesting isles, provides unlimited choices for a stunning boat charter itinerary. Sorrento remains popular due to a network of elegant stores and sophisticated bars, while the CliffsidePositano exemplifies a wealthy resort town with breathtaking views on land and at sea.  The region's namesake, Amalfi, is steeped in romanticism and known for its great beaches and lemon production. Cruise farther away to relax in the hot springs on the little island of Ischia, while vistas towards the towering cliffs of Capri are indeed a joy to see from a boat.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Eat traditional food prepared with fresh flavors and local products ripened and sweetened by the sun, a highlight of a yacht vacation in Italy. Naples, the birthplace of pizza, is the ideal location to sample the famous margherita. The Amalfi Coast is known for its lemons, which may be found in cooling gelatos and, obviously, the wonderfully sweet native limoncello.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;In Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;When exploring the top destinations in the Mediterranean for yacht vacations, you should make a list of all the places you want to hit and go for it. There may not be another chance to explore the beautiful paradise points of the areas around the Mediterranean, so make the most of it!&lt;/p&gt;</p>
		</text>
	</dest>

	<dest>
		<thumb>best-places-to-visit-on-an-italy-yacht-charter</thumb>
		<image>best-places-to-visit-on-an-italy-yacht-charter</image>
		<link>best-places-to-visit-on-an-italy-yacht-charter</link>
		<title>Best Places To Visit On An Italy Yacht Charter</title>
		<desc>Learn the secrets of an Italian vacation.</desc>
		<text>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A yacht charter vacation is certainly one of the finest, most luxurious, and enjoyable ways to enjoy the breathtaking islands, beaches, cities, and villages in any country, and Italy is no exception. The European country boasts mesmerizing landscapes, such as sandy beaches, volcanoes, hills, verdant planes, and many varied, culturally rich islands. If you take a yacht charter in Italy to explore all the varied locations, you will be able to move freely, at your convenience, and explore your favorite beaches at a pace that suits you and your loved ones.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;So, without any ado, let's take a look at the best places you can visit in Italy on a yacht charter!&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h2&gt;The Best Places to Visit with a Yacht Charter in Italy&lt;/h2&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Here are the best islands, cities, and coasts you must visit in Italy on your yacht charter vacation:&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Sardinia&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Sardinia is a paradise-like picture-perfect coastline that lies in the middle of the Mediterranean Sea. About 12 miles south of Corsica, Sardinia is home to many spectacular islands and beaches of the Archipelago of La Maddalena. You can explore castle and fort ruins, stunning churches, and magnificent galleries and museums.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;With more than sixty islands, rocks, and islets, you can also find many sandy beaches with clear shining seas. These unspoiled and utterly beautiful spots are excellent for yachting and sailing. Southern Sardinia has shallow beaches, excellent water sports conditions, and hot weather. Moreover, many nearby cities house Michelin-starred eateries to fulfill your fine dining dreams.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Northern Sardinia has Porto Cervo, a seaside resort known as a superyacht and chartered yachts hub. It features many eateries and shops for you to explore and have a fun time. It houses an eclectic mix of fishing villages, beautiful villas, and high-end boutiques. You will witness the spectacular pink granite coastline, dazzling, pristine beaches, and sheltered anchorage and coves when exploring Sardinia.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Sicily&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Sicily is the largest island in the Mediterranean Sea and is also the country's biggest island. Not only is Sicily blessed with an expansive landscape, but it also has some pretty diverse landforms, such as the dynamic volcanic and mountainous scenery, the flowering meadows, and the beautiful crystal blue seas. The beaches offer many water sports and partying opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;What makes Sicily stand out as one of the most culturally diverse places in Italy is that it has been invaded numerous times over the years by the Greeks, Romans, Arabs, Phoenicians Spaniards, and Normans due to its strategic location. Each of these occupants left behind their cultural influences that have given Sicily its blended yet distinctive culture and architecture. The UNESCO World Heritage Sites and city streets of Palermo, the capital of Sicily, are a must-visit for all yacht travelers.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;The Aeolian Islands&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The Aeolian Islands - Vulcano, Lipari, Stromboli, Panarea, Alicudi, and Filicudi - are in the middle of the Tyrrhenian Sea, about fifteen miles from the coast of Sicilia. They feature volatile mountains and stunning back beaches made from volcanic soil. With your yacht charter in Italy, you can explore the island archipelagos at your own pace. The Aeolian Islands will also offer many scenic spots where you can moor the yacht overnight.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Even though the Aeolian Islands are quite dramatic, they are not as well-known as Sicily or the Gulf of Maples, making them the ideal vacation spot for families looking for a less touristy spot. The dramatic beaches and islands have towering cliffs, striking volcanoes, fertile fields, and fallen Roman-Greco temple statues. You can take your yacht to a quiet beach and snorkel or have a relaxing night under the starry sky.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The ports of the islands feature charming eateries and bars. Meanwhile, the interiors have contrasting landscapes, crystal clear water bays, active volcanoes, simple white-painted houses, isolated reefs, and archaeological sites that are dramatic and beautiful.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;The Gulf of Naples&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Naples is one of the most renowned and oldest inhabited sites in the world. It features many modern and ancient treasures. The Gulf of Naples houses Sorrento, a picturesque town with a narrow ravine flowing through its historical landscape. The town features numerous old shops selling local Sorrento lemon liqueur, ceramics, and lacework. It also houses many striking hotels that offer an enticing combination of five-star service and quaint old-world charm.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;You can unwind in Sorrento's serene parks, enjoy some gelato ice cream, and stroll the streets while having local food. You can also find pretty souvenirs made with fine wooden marquetry boxes. Meanwhile, Naples is steeped in history and offers delicious culinary delights. You have to see the art of San Lorenzo Maggiore and the veiled figures of Museo Cappella Sansevero.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, the Gulf of Naples also includes the idyllic Capri, known for its luxurious shopping opportunities. When you visit Capri, you can find unique shops that carry everything from pottery and accessories to shoes and fabrics. The town also houses many deluxe restaurants, the Gardens of Augustus, and elegant caf's. The lesser-known town of Ischia is known for its immaculate landscaped gardens, a magnificent Aragonese castle, and relaxing thermal spas.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Amalfi Coast &lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;If you're looking for some truly unique landscapes, you must visit the Amalfi Coast on your yacht charter in Italy. Rocky cliffs with winding and twisting roads, secluded bays, and small villages offer a beautiful view of the clear blue ocean. Moreover, the coast also boasts verdant Mediterranean flora that colors the slopes of the adjoining cliffs and hills. The coast also houses world-renowned towns, such as Ravello, Amalfi, and Positano.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;When traveling to the Amalfi Coast, you will have the opportunity to visit Pompeii, a striking archaeological site of a thriving Roman town that became a victim of the Mount Vesuvius volcanic eruption in AD79. Since the whole town was covered with 25 meters deep ash, blocking air and moisture, it ensured the preservation of the town relics. These relics reflect the remarkable intricacies of daily life in the old days.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Moreover, you can enjoy authentic Italian coffee at one of the many quaint caf's in Positano. You must also visit the Church of Santa Maria Assunta before you head to other islands. If you want to explore beautiful beaches and find shaded coves for water sports, you can visit the hotspots, such as Spiaggia di Tordigliano.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Venice &amp; the Adriatic Sea&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;How can one not include Venice in the list of places you must visit in Italy on your yacht charter? After all, it's a beautiful and world-renowned city with incredible architectural attractions listed as UNESCO World Heritage Sites. You can take part in the annual carnival and take the famous gondola ride on the Grand Canal. You can also shop for genuine Vatican souvenirs, such as hand-blown Murano glass. Visit historic sites like the Palazzo Ducale and Basilica di San Marco.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, the Adriatic Sea is a striking destination you can choose to begin or end your charter vacation. You can cruise to the impressively beautiful Istrian peninsula and the Dalmatian coast, where the islands feature breathtaking, untouched beaches with shallow and clear water. You can also find plenty of scuba diving sites around the area.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;The Italian Riviera&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;When traveling on a yacht in Italy, you must take your yacht charter to the Italian Riviera. It features many notable attractions, such as San Basilio, the Russian Orthodox Church in Sanremo. The waterfront features varied eateries that offer an outdoor setting and sunbathing areas, where you can take in the verdant vegetation that borders the pale sandy beaches and vibrant blue seas.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;If you love medieval architecture, you will certainly love the enchanting La Pinga. You must also visit the museums that line the La Spezia, a city with a comprehensive maritime history that it displays in its Technical Naval Museum. You can also marvel at St. George's Castle, which offers panoramic views of the sea and features the Archaeological Museum. For art lovers, the Amedeo Lia Museum features some beautiful art as it is established on the site of an old convent.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The Italian Riviera also houses a small port town known as Portofino. It's a quaint town that features Museo del Parco sculptures and a 16thcentury castle and museum known as Castello Brown. You will also find well-known luxury international brands that you can shop from to find gifts for your loved ones back home.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;You can also visit the Cinque Terre villages that are UNESCO World Heritage Sites. These villages offer stunning views of colorful shops and houses that you can enjoy from your charter yacht. You can also traverse them on foot and shop in the small boutiques or grab a bite from the local caf's. You can also cruise to one of the bays accessible by water for a fun-filled afternoon of snorkeling and swimming.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Tuscany&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Tuscany boasts pristine wilderness and a mesmerizing coastline. Since most of the coast is only accessible by sea, it offers you some privacy for sunbathing during the day and partying under the stars. You can swim and snorkel among the colorful fish for hours or be at peace with nature on Capraia. You can also go to Elba to enjoy hiking along the trails that offer views of the oldest ruins on the island.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Now that you know about all the breathtaking coasts, villages, and cities you can visit on a yacht charter in Italy, make sure to include them on your itinerary. These places offer a comprehensive Italian experience, with delicious local food, specialty drinks, souvenirs, archeological sites, diverse landscapes, and so much more.&lt;/p&gt; </p>
			
		</text>
	</dest>

	<dest>
		<thumb>yacht-care-and-maintenance-tips</thumb>
		<image>yacht-care-and-maintenance-tips</image>
		<link>yacht-care-and-maintenance-tips</link>
		<title>Yacht Care &amp; Maintenance Tips</title>
		<desc>Increase the lifespan of your boat.</desc>
		<text>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;If you live near a major body of water, a yacht is your passport to a vacation filled with excitement and adventure. On the wide sea, a boat results in freedom. It may bring you outside at moments in the year where you may not other consider being outside on the sea. &lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;p&gt;That is why, to maintain a boat and ensure that it is operating for a long time to come, adequate boat maintenance is required. Under moderate to heavy usage, all boats suffer a battering. Depending on the kind of waters and weather circumstances, they may be exposed to various hazards that threaten to collapse or ground them on the shore if proper precautions are not taken.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;p&gt;Boat maintenance, thankfully, is simple with a little knowledge and experience. Knowing the kind of repairs and maintenance your yacht needs and how to care for it can go a long way in ensuring a longer lifespan for your boat.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;p&gt;Let's take a closer look at some yacht care and maintenance tips. &lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;ol class="bg-li"&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;li&gt;Using Fiberglass Reconditioner</p>
			<p>	&lt;p&gt;During typical usage, fiberglass hulls may take a battering. Most issues arise over time when many impacts and debris repeatedly strike the same spot, eroding the hull's integrity. Cleaning may help remove some wear and tear or buildup, but we have found that fiberglass reconditioners go much farther.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;p&gt;This is referred to as a fiberglass reconditioning compound, and it can usually eliminate some of the oxidation stains and watermarks that may damage the boat's hull over time. Many compounds additionally cover the hull with a protective layer that deflects water and oil during regular operation.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;p&gt;To safeguard the boat during the season, follow this step in your pre-season yacht maintenance program.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;li&gt;Make Use of Marine Cleaning Supplies</p>
			<p>	&lt;p&gt;Your yacht will appear gleaming and new after a thorough cleaning. More significantly, it will preserve the hull in excellent condition for a much longer period of time. This is particularly true in the case of boats that are utilized in saline water.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;p&gt;When it's time to wash the boat, make sure you use the right cleaning agents that won't harm the surfaces. These treatments are often intended to remove common dirt and germs that accumulate over time. Some goods will be designed expressly for usage with specific kinds of water.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;li&gt;Batteries Should Be Cleaned and Checked</p>
			<p>	&lt;p&gt;Even if you aren't using your batteries, they will deteriorate over time. Regular entropy causes power drains and leaks. If you neglect these concerns, you might end yourself stranded on the open sea with no lights or electricity.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;p&gt;A battery check should be carried out at least once per season as part of routine boat maintenance. A voltage meter may be used to detect how much charge is remaining in batteries. Determine how much charge the batteries typically consume during a particular season ahead of time. Replace batteries that are going low to be safe.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;p&gt;Examine all connections to your batteries as well. Clean these connections to ensure that the power gets to where it's required the most.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;li&gt;Make Use of Fresh Water</p>
			<p>	&lt;p&gt;Typical boat maintenance during the regular season includes cleaning the boat down following one or two trips on the water. This will aid in the removal of usual grime and muck accumulation while also simplifying off-season cleaning.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;p&gt;Whenever you're cleaning the boat, be certain to use freshwater. For most surfaces, spray the boat with the hose. As a spot cleaner, utilize fresh water from the tap in a bucket with cleaning soap to wash away any problematic places.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;p&gt;Make sure the water you use is of good quality. Most tap water is safe to drink, but be careful of contaminants and minerals that might harm the surface of your boat.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;li&gt;Examine the Electrical Lines</p>
			<p>	&lt;p&gt;Electrical wires on a yacht, like batteries, may deteriorate with time. Physical injury, as well as dirt and filth, are typical reasons. You should inspect these lines on a regular basis and make any and all required replacements or repairs.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;p&gt;When anything fails to operate or switch on during a typical boat operation, the electrical wires are likely faulty. Anything that isn't regulated by mechanical systems is prone to failure. Cleaning power cables is an excellent approach to prevent these problems, but all wires ultimately need to be replaced.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;p&gt;Another instrument for inspecting the condition of these cables is a voltmeter.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;li&gt;Inspect Frequently</p>
			<p>	&lt;p&gt;It's easy to believe that your boat will work flawlessly every time you bring it out on the lake. Most individuals make that assertion after purchasing a new boat or doing routine maintenance or upgrades on it. Regrettably, difficulties might arise at any moment.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;p&gt;It's a good idea to start examining your boat on a regular basis. Some checks should be performed on a more regular basis than others. For example, before taking your boat out, you may quickly examine the hull for apparent concerns. Every time you use it, you should do this.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;p&gt;Checking the wiring, engine, pumps, fluids, and controls should be done at least once per season before operating the yacht. An inspection can help you determine what sort of yacht maintenance is necessary while also preventing severe problems from arising.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;li&gt;Clean Your Windows with A Window Cleaner</p>
			<p>	&lt;p&gt;If the windows get excessively filthy, a decent window cleaner may help a lot. Cleaning windows that are directly in the spray line as the yacht passes through the water should be on the yacht maintenance checklist. The majority of the windows at the bow and waterline will fall into this category.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;p&gt;If you wish to stay loyal to the boat's demands, specialty cleaners are available. Certain window home cleaners work for some folks, but their effectiveness is hit or miss. If you're unsure, a little trial and error can help you figure out what actually works for you and the boat.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;li&gt;Examine the Bilge Pumps</p>
			<p>	&lt;p&gt;If your boat sinks, boat upkeep is meaningless. Bilge pumps are normally provided to pump the water out of the boat's interior to prevent the boat from sinking. These pumps might help save lives in bad weather or severe seas.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;p&gt;Bilges, like any other form of pump, need regular maintenance. Electrical and mechanical systems have a high failure rate. Debris and items, in particular, may become stuck in a pump's internal workings, thus stopping the flow of water.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;p&gt;Before using the pump for the season, make sure it's in good working condition by testing it. An electrical problem might be indicated by a failure to startup or function correctly. A mechanical problem might be indicated by strange sounds or an absence of pumping motion. Before putting the boat out, you may have to fix a defective component or replace the complete unit in both circumstances.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;li&gt;Hire Professionals After High Seasonal Use</p>
			<p>	&lt;p&gt;Unless you are a skilled mechanic or have decades of boat care knowledge, there's a strong chance you'll need to hire a proper professional to inspect and repair your boat at some point. This is especially true with regard to repairing and upgrading the boat's more complicated inner workings, such as its engines.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;p&gt;Professional technicians are typically able to identify problems before they become big difficulties. They'll also assist you in protecting the yacht during the off-season and fine-tuning your normal boat maintenance to meet the demands of your boat.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;p&gt;Feel free to browse around for alternative mechanic choices when it is time for major repair or update. Consider the experience and the services they provide, as well as the fees they charge. While it's tempting to choose the costliest mechanic, it's not always essential or even advisable.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;li&gt;Winterize</p>
			<p>	&lt;p&gt;During the off-season, most boats sustain a great deal of damage. Yachts like the spring and summer seasons since there isn't any ice, snow, or extreme cold to harm them. Depending on the area, you may need to find out ways to winterize your boat to keep it safe from extreme weather conditions.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;p&gt;To keep their boats for the winter, some customers choose indoor storage or climate-controlled docks. If you're changing to a private dock for the winter, these alternatives normally entail monthly fees or a lump sum payment. If you generally keep the boat on your own property, commercial solutions such as tarps and backyard buildings may be available.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;li&gt;Yacht Maintenance</p>
			<p>	&lt;p&gt;If done regularly and properly, proper yacht maintenance will keep the boat healthy and happy for many years. The most common stumbling block is simply finding the drive to do the essential maintenance on the boat.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;p&gt;There's no better time than the present to establish your own regimen. Summer is coming rapidly. As a result, most individuals will be getting ready for summer aquatic activities in no time. Get a head start on that upkeep!&lt;/p&gt;                        </p>
			<p>	&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>	&lt;/ol&gt;</p>
		</text>
	</dest>

	<dest>
		<thumb>Boat-Jokes-min</thumb>
		<image>Boat-Jokes</image>
		<link>boat-jokes</link>
		<title>Boat Jokes</title>
		<desc>Yacht humor.</desc>
		<text>
		<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. What did the pirate say when he turned 80?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. “Aye matey”&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. What detergent do sailors use?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. Tide.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. Why did the admiral decide against buying a new hat?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. He was worried about cap-sizing!&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A pirate walks into a bar with a little ship’s wheel in the front of his pants.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The bartender says, “Hey, why you got a ship’s wheel in your trousers?”&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The pirate replies “I don’t know, but it’s driving me nuts!”&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. Why are portholes in boats round?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. So the water doesn’t hit the sailors square in the face!&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A slice of apple pie is $2.50 in Jamaica and $3.00 in the Bahamas.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;These are the pie rates of the Caribbean.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. Why can’t you tickle a sailor?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. Because they’re nautical-ish.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Two wind turbines sit in the ocean. One turns to the other and asks, “What music do you listen to?”&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The second one says. “I’m a massive heavy metal fan.”&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. Why did the hippie drown in the ocean?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. He was too far out.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A lost hiker is on one side of a raging river when he sees a Buddhist monk on the other side.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;There are no bridges. He has no boat. He shouts out to the monk on the opposite bank. “How do I get to the other side?”&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The Buddhist monk shouts back: “You are on the other side.”&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. How much does it cost a pirate to get his ears pierced?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. A Buck-an-ear.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Two Italian guys, Tony and Marco, go fishing on a boat&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Suddenly, Tony spots an old WWII bomb floating towards them.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Marco screams “Tony! Look! It’s a mine!”&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Tony, scared, replies “Okay okay Marco, you can a have it!”&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A very nervous first time crew member says to the skipper, “Do boats like this sink very often?”&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;“Not too often,” replied the skipper. “Usually it’s only the once.”&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. Why didn’t the sailors play cards?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. Because the captain was standing on the deck.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. What happens if you throw a Finnish sailor overboard?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. Helsinki.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Guy at the Marina: “So which of these boats is the one I won in the dice game?”&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;“Yacht C,” the attendant says.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;“No. Craps!”&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. What kind of fish is made from just two sodium atoms?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. 2 Na&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. Why don’t pirates drive on mountain roads?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. ‘Scurvy.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A man walks into a seafood store carrying a trout under his arm.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;“Do you make fish cakes?” he asked.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;“Yes, we do,” replied the fishmonger.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;“Great,” said the man, “It’s his birthday.”&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. How do you get two whales in a car?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. Start in England and drive west.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;I told my girlfriend that I had a crush on Beyoncé.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;And she said to me “Whatever floats your boat”.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;And I replied “No, that’s Buoyancy.”&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. How does the ocean floor stay up-to-date on the news?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. By following current events.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A boat carrying red paint crashed into a boat carrying blue paint and the crew were marooned.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. If you have 5 cats on a boat and and 1 jumps off, how many cats are left in the boat?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. None, they were copycats.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;My wife is nervous about having to talk to strangers on a cruise we are about to take.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;I said, “Don’t worry. We are all in the same boat.”&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. Where did Captain Hook buy his hook&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. At a second hand store.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;I saw a sailor with a big bushy beautiful beard today.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Was it a navel beard?&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;No, his beard was on his chin.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. What is the deepest part of the ocean?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. The bottom.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Give a man a fish and he will eat for a day.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Teach him how to fish and he will sit in a boat and drink beer all day.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. Do you guys want to know what I put in the wooden box I made and threw in the ocean?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. Never mind, it’s a sea-crate.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. What causes some boats to become party boats?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. Pier pressure.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. What is a ghost pirate’s favorite kind of tea?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. Boo tea.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. How do you make a boat feel better?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. Give it some vitamin sea.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. Why does the Norwegian navy have barcodes on the side of their ships?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. So that when the ships come back into port they can Scandinavian!&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;My wife has just sailed to the Caribbean.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Jamaica?&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;No, she wanted to!&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. Why do oars fall in love?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. Because they’re row-mantic.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. When is a sailor not a sailor?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. When he’s aboard.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Two people are out sailing when suddenly a hand appears in the sea.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;“What’s this?” asked the skipper, “It looks as if someone is drowning!”&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;“No,” explained his crew, “It’s just a little wave.”&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. What’s big and blue and if it fell out of a tree would kill you?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. The Pacific Ocean.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. Where do sick boats go?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. To the dock.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. What keeps the ocean from leaking out?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. The seals.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. Where do ghosts like to go sailing?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. Lake Eerie.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A pirate goes to see his doctor and asks him to look at the spots on his arm.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The doctor examines them and says, “Nothing to worry about, they’re benign.”&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The pirate says, “No Doc, there be eleven. I counted them before I came here.”&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. Why are pirates so bad at learning alphabets?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. Because they always get stuck at C.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. Where do zombies like to go sailing?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. The Dead Sea.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. Why is pirating addictive?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. Once you lose your first hand, you get hooked.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Pretend you are on a boat surrounded by sharks. How do you survive?&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;You stop pretending.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. Why did the viking buy an old boat ?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. He couldn’t a fjord a new one&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. What lies at the bottom of the ocean and twitches?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. A nervous wreck.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. What did the pirate say when his wooden leg got stuck in the freezer?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. Shiver me timbers.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. How can you cut an ocean in two?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. With a sea-saw.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. What do you call a boat full of buddies?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. A friend-ship.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Boating Riddle:&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. 3 men are in a boat with 4 cigarettes but no lighter, what do they do?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. Throw 1 cigarette overboard and the boat becomes a cigarette lighter.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Knock, knock.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Who’s there?&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Canoe.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Canoe, who?&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Canoe answer the door, please?&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. Why don’t pirates shower before they walk the plank?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. They’ll just wash up on the shore later.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. Which type of vegetable is banned on ships?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. Leeks.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. What type of sailors blow their nose a lot?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. The anchor chiefs.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. Why don’t you ever see a pirate cry?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. Because when they do, it’s a private tear.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. How do you communicate with a fish?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. Drop it a line.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. H20 is water, but what is H204?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. It’s for boating, of course.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. Why do scuba divers always flip backwards when jumping from a boat in water?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. Because if they flip forward they would still be in the boat.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A dentist opened an office on a boat.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;What was the boat’s name?&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The Tooth Ferry&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. What kind of grades did the pirate get in school?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. High Cs.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. What’s a pirate’s favorite letter?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. P, because without it they’re irate.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;I spent my children’s college fund on a boat…I’m going to call it the scholarship.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. What’s the world’s most efficient bilge pump?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. A scared man with a bucket.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. When do you know you are getting a good deal on a boat?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. When there’s a sail on it.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. What kind of boat do sailors learn their trade on?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. An apprenticeship.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. What did the sand say when the tide came back in?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A. Long time, no sea!&lt;/p&gt;</p>
		</text>
	</dest>

	<dest>
		<thumb>Boat-Puns-min</thumb>
		<image>Boat-Puns</image>
		<link>boat-puns</link>
		<title>Boat Puns</title>
		<desc>I entered my 10 best yacht puns in the Blue Ocean Almonds humor competition. I didn&#8217;t win; it was nuts. No pun in ten did.</desc>
		<text>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A pirate ship is assailing vessel.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;My anchor rope started talking to me, so I asked if it was a person now. "I'm a frayed knot," it replied.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;I started a successful boat building business in the attic of my house. Sails are going through the roof!&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;While driving to work, robbers jumped into my car and stole everything. They were pirates of the car I be in.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Two cruise ships were in the harbor. "I'm empty. Where is everyone?" said one. "I haven't got a crew," said the second.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;I was saddened to learn that my cousin was run over by a boat in Venice today. I sent his family my gondolances.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Cleopatra fell out of her boat but wouldn't admit she was wet. She was in denial.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;I met a pilot once who said he actually wanted to be a sailor. He was in the wrong craft.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;I used to have a fear of boats, but that ship has sailed.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;If you ever need to fit two of every animal on a boat, I Noah guy.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A sailor eating alphabet soup found the seven Cs.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Why are sailors so indecisive? Because they're always far from shore.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;When the captain's ship ran aground he couldn't fathom why.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;My friend was late for our sailing trip. When she arrived, it was a-boat time.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;I'm not one for buoyancy, but you know, whatever floats your boat.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;"I like the rear of the ship," Bill said sternly.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A rock band's yacht moored then fell over sideways. It liked to dock and roll.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;I crashed my rowing boat. I suffered a broken scull.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;I'd like to have a party on my boat, it is always a great sail-abration.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Leaving boating school is sad, I hated saying bye to my piers.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A ship's captain is a sails manager.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Do swimming instructors get immersed in their work?&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Making a boat out of stone would be a hardship.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;3.14% of Sailors are Pi Rates.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A luxury yacht sank and a passenger was holding on to a floating piano. All of a sudden, someone floats by sitting atop a floating cello and asks: " May I accompany you?"&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The admiral's motto was, 'Do it schooner rather than later!'&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;I won the rowing championship, canoe believe it?&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Other boats always think that a canal boat is pushy. He just keeps barging in on them.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;I recently bought a boat for a friend. I was pier pressured.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Seven days without swimming makes one weak.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;We weren't planning to go sailing, but we decided to seas the day.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;My friend has an unhealthy obsession with ocean life. I told her to sea kelp.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A car ferry sailed past. "That's a ferry impressive boat," shouted the captain.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Before my operation, the anaesthesiologist asked if I wanted to be knocked out via gas or boat paddle. It was an ether/oar situation.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A brother and sister were arguing about oars in their boat. They were having a row.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;There's a big paddle sale at the boat store. It's quite an oar deal.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The cast of "Friends" got stuck at sea in a boat, but thankfully nothing happened. Because Lisa Kudrow and David was a good Schwimmer&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;This ship keeps banging into rocks. It's cruising for a bruising.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;I got a new saltwater boat. I use it for saline.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A kid put a tied-up piece of rope on a sailor's wrist. "Knot on my watch!" the sailor shouted. "That's knot funny."&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;I got my friend a row boat, but I'd better a-skiff she wants it.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;I named my boat Relation. Now I can tell people…I have a Relationship.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;I bought a sail for my boat on Amazon the other day. Today it dawned on me that it's not the right size, so I tried to cancel the order. They said it's too late. That sail has shipped.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;We had a party on our boat the other day. It was a sail-abration.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The canoe was annoyed the paddle fell over the side. Getting it back would be an oar-deal.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;When the bottom of a cargo ship got a hole, it had one hull of a problem.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;I only laugh at boating puns…I'm not a fan of dry humor.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;If your boat gets sick, I know a great dock. It's pier-reviewed.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A rope asked if it was getting a Christmas present. "Depends if you're knotty or nice," the sailor replied.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A canoe asked a tug whether he'd been to the Atlantic. "Oh, no," he replied. "I wouldn't go there. I have very Pacific tastes."&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A man kept walking round the harbor sticking poles on the boats. He was the harbor mast-er.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
		</text>
	</dest>

	<dest>
		<thumb>Funny-Boat-Names-min</thumb>
		<image>Funny-Boat-Names</image>
		<link>funny-boat-names</link>
		<title>Funny Boat Names</title>
		<desc>Boat owners can sometimes be very silly.</desc>
		<text>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Barely A Wake&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Sea-E-O&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Moor Bills&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Sails Call&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Kids' Inheritance&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Lure Me&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Aboat Time&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;LunaSea&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Knot Hers&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;For Sail By Owner&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Gypsea&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Campbell's Sloop&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Fish Limo&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Moor Often Than Knot&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Keel Over&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Miss Conduct&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Little Knotty&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;One Too Many&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Feeling Nauti&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Ships n' Giggles&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Doctor's Orders&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;On The Rocks&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Fear Knot&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Devocean&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Yachts of Fun&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Reel Magic&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Elegantly Wasted&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Bouy Oh Bouy&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Knot For Sail&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Miss B. Haven&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Caught in the Moment&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Reel Time&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Nice Aft&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Playbouy&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Sea For Two&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Reelax&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;In a Meeting&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Tuition&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;After Berth&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Seazure&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Keep'n It Reel&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The Codfather&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Island Time&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Pier Pressure&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;It's-A-Moray&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Reel Estate&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Seas The Moment&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Sea U Late Oar&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Companion Ship&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Vitamin Sea&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Knot Paid IV&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Passing Wind&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Best of Boat Worlds&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Current Sea&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Yacht Sea&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Sea Duction&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Grounds For Divorce&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Why Knot?&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Beeracuda&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Reel Therapy&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Fuelish Behavior&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Sea Me&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Friendship&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Liquid Asset&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Knot 2 Bad&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Berth Control&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Goin' Broke&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Bouys and Gills&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A Wave From It All&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Favorite Mistake&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Weather Oar Knot&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Between The Sheets&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Gone With The Wind&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Unfathomable&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Buoyoncé&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Dock Holiday&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Seas The Day&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;2nd Wind&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Bow Movement&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Waterfront Bar&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;It's 5 O'clock Somewhere&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Sea Ya&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Fishful Thinkin'&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Nauti By Nature&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Empty Pocket&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Crabby&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;AquaHolic&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;In Decent Seas&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Sea Señor&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Holy Mackerel&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;ARRR Boat&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Aquasition&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Liquid Pleasure&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Unsinkable II&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;She Got The House&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Seaclusion&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Knot Shore&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Hydro Therapy&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Freudian Sloop&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Fish &amp; Chicks&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Breakin Wind&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Court A Sea&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Seaductress&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Ship Happens&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Prawnto&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Nautibuoy&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Unortho-Docks&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Cool Whip&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Sail La Vie&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Latitude Adjustment&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Ship For Brains&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Bad To The Bow&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The Court Ship&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;This Side Up&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Reel Easy&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Deck-A-Dence&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;CrewZen&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Sea-Duced&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Semper Fish&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Changes in L'Attitudes&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Nacho Boat&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Anchor Management&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Sea Nile&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;DotCalm&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Ship Faced&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Water You Lookin' At?&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A Frayed Knot&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Unreel&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Marlin Monroe&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Hook &amp; Ladder&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Fantasea&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Divorce Sail&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Ta-Keel-La&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Forward My Calls&lt;/p&gt;</p>
		</text>
	</dest>

	<dest>
		<thumb>the-top-10-yachting-destinations</thumb>
		<image>the-top-10-yachting-destinations</image>
		<link>the-top-10-yachting-destinations</link>
		<title>The Top 10 Yachting Destinations</title>
		<desc>Figure out whare to go on your yachting vacation.</desc>
		<text>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Picture this: the sun is beating down on you as a fresh breeze ruffles your hair. You lean back and enjoy the gentle rocking motion of your yacht in one of the world's most beautiful sailing destinations. Doesn't that sound amazing?&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;You can have that experience and more when you know where to go. After all, you didn't buy your yacht to take it on a local trip once a year. Be adventurous and get out there! Enjoy the experience of sailing around the world.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;To help you plan your next dream yachting trip, here are the top ten yachting destinations. Visit these to find the beauty, relaxation, and fun you've been craving.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;ol class="bg-li"&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;The French Riviera, France</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;If you're looking for some beautiful buildings and are an architecture fan, the French Riviera has gorgeous towns lining its coast. The bright colors and bustling life complement its subtle vintage feel.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;If you're feeling adventurous, you can even make your way to the beautiful, natural health retreat nearby: Monaco. You can also stop by the coast for one of its many lively festivals throughout the year.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;If you want to avoid the rainy weather, you should sail here from late spring to early fall.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Norwegian Fjords</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;If you want to travel through a breath-taking natural landscape, you should consider the Norwegian Fjords. This area, formed by glaciers, is full of peaceful blue and green waters. You can also view the quaint, rustic villages nearby and stop in for lunch.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;If you're wanting sunshine, June through August is the best time to travel here. If you're wanting to catch a glimpse of the Northern lights, you should sail here between October and March.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;The Dalmatian Coast, Croatia</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The Dalmatian Coast is speckled with stretching, sandy beaches and dotted with islands just waiting to be explored. Get out and swim, or enjoy the carved rock cliff sides decorated with lush greenery.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Get the best of both worlds with nature on all sides and ancient architecture abutting the shore. If you want to enjoy the experience without the crowds, plan your trip here in May, September, or October, to avoid the tourist season but still have warmer weather.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;The Greek Coastline and Islands</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Between the Sporades islands, off the east coast, and sailing near the beauty of Santorini, there's lots to love about Greece! The lush, green plant life and hidden coves on the islands lend their beauty and provide a sense of adventure as you travel through the many islands.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;When closer to the mainland, you can see the picturesque cliffside with restaurants and buildings rising out of it. Like Croatia, you should plan to visit in May, September, or October to avoid the crowds.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;The Amalfi Coast, Italy</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Sail the shores of Italy and experience a historical, architectural wonder. Mountains and cliffs stretch over blue waters, spread with greenery and buildings old and new. Stop by one of the many small towns to enjoy the atmosphere and food, or swim at one of its beaches.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Walk the cobbled streets and smell the sea air while enjoying a glass of wine or a short shopping spree. The best time to visit is in Spring and Fall, as the temperatures will be more moderate and the crowds will be gone.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Alor Archipelago, Indonesia</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;This gorgeous group of islands has it all: marine life, natural, untouched beauty, and warm, sunny weather. Indonesia has about 17,500 islands to explore, and these are some of the best. You can go diving and see the ocean life up close, including coral reefs.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;There are hiking spots and locations where you can watch exotic animals from a distance. To avoid the currents and rain, the best time to visit is from April to August.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;The Maldives</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The Maldives has been known for its stunning geography for a long time. Made of 1,100 islands, it covers a wide expanse of the Indian Ocean and offers recreation along with its relaxing scenery.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;You can watch dolphins playing and jumping out of the water or dive down deep to see ocean life, including sharks and whales. Additionally, jet skiing and other water activities are allowed here, on the beautiful sea in the sunshine. It's best to visit during the dry season, between November and April.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;The Galapagos Islands</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;If you're interested in biodiversity and a stunning, South American getaway, the Galapagos Islands are a great destination for your next yachting trip. Get up close and personal with amazing animal life such as sea lions and giant tortoises.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The hot, rainy season that starts in December can be the best time to break out your yacht, as the ocean is the smoothest for sailing. Starting in January, there are fewer tourists, and you'll have the place to yourself! Enjoy snorkeling, diving, hiking, kayaking, or surfing in one of the most amazing natural locations in the world.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;The Antarctic Gateway</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;If you are a more adventurous sailor, you may want to visit the Antarctic Gateway, where the rough Drake passage takes skill to navigate even on a good day. Once you get past the rough passage, where cold and warm water meet and rough winds have beat against many boats, you'll see the natural glacial beauty of the Antarctic.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;As you pass by Chile and Argentina on your way there, however, you'll see natural ice formations and national parks, scenic mountains against the cold waters, and many small port towns where you can stop and refuel with some delicious South American cuisine. February is one of the warmest months for this area, and you can still see some whales in March.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;li&gt;Queensland, Australia</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Queensland, Australia may not be the first place you think of to go yachting, but it's one of the most rewarding. From Moreton Bay, a popular spot for diving and swimming, to Whitsundays, which includes the well-known Hamilton Island, there are endless places to explore and recreate in the warmth of Australia's southern coast.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;It's also home to the Great Sandy Strait, a picturesque destination with clear water that allows you to see the wildlife, including whales, dolphins, sea turtles, and dugongs, a manatee-like animal. The best time to visit this area is January through March for the warmest weather and the calmest ocean.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/li&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/ol&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;br&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h3&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Hopefully, you've learned about some great options for your next sailing adventure that were provided for us by Lana from &lt;a href="https://www.crowdsourcedexplorer.com/"&gt;CrowdsourcedExplorer.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Be sure to &lt;a href="http://crowdsourcedexplorer.com/"&gt;get tips from locals&lt;/a&gt; before you go! You want to know all the most beautiful and fun spots to visit, and locals often know about things the tour guides won't tell you.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
		</text>
	</dest>

	<dest>
		<thumb>sold</thumb>
		<image>sold</image>
		<link>should-i-use-a-yacht-broker</link>
		<title>Should I Use A Yacht Broker?</title>
		<desc>Boat brokers usually charge a 10% commission. The question is, should you pay this fee, or sell it yourself? </desc>
		<text>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Boat brokers usually charge a 10% commission. The question is, should you pay this fee, or sell it yourself?&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Unlike with real estate, where most houses are sold via the MLS system, there is no one central listing site for boats. Buyers find boats through all types of methods. You can do a “For Sale By Owner” listing, where you post your listing on as many sites as you can, but it will cost you hundreds of dollars and take a lot of time and effort. Brokers pay a fixed monthly fee to each site and then can add an unlimited number of listings, many times using an automated system, so it is easy for them to promote your boat on all of the top boating marketplaces.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;For listings on Yachts.com, I have tried advertising yachts for sale on these types of sites, and currently pay over $500/month to do this, but I have not found the response to be that great. For lower-priced boats though, people tell me Craigslist and Facebook marketplace generates a lot of buyers.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;One advantage a broker has is they can get your boat listed in YachtWorld.com, which is the biggest site for this sort of thing and is for brokers only. A broker can also co-broke your listing, which means other brokers throughout the country will also try to find a buyer for your boat.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The biggest advantage of a broker is that they can market your boat both nationally and locally. Their brokerage already is getting new potential buyers every day looking for a boat like yours.  They also can promote it in the same geographic area where your boat is located, and help the buyer through the sale process so everything goes smoothly.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;If you are not in a rush and have the time to deal with it, it is worth trying to sell your boat on your own. But for the typical seller, I would recommend using a broker, as that way it has a much higher chance of getting sold.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
		</text>
	</dest>

	<dest>
		<thumb>self-driving-boat-version-1</thumb>
		<image>none</image>
		<link>self-driving-boat-version-1</link>
		<title>Self-Driving Boat - Version #1</title>
		<desc>Watch the video of the first test of our autonomous boat.</desc>
		<text>
			<p>&lt;div class="text-center w-100"&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;video playsinline controls loop&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;source src="../videos/self-driving-boat.mp4" poster="/images/thumbnail/self-driving-thumb.webp" type="video/mp4" /&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/video&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/div&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The video above is the first test of our autonomous boat (as described in our previous article posting about &lt;a href="https://yachts.com/articles/self-driving-boats.php" target="_blank"&gt;self-driving boats&lt;/a&gt;). Keep in mind it took James Dyson 5,127 tries to invent his revolutionary vacuum cleaner, and Thomas Edison made over 1,000 unsuccessful attempts at inventing the light bulb before it finally worked. So we are just getting started.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The model boat in the video is made entirely using a 3D printer. This demo version does not yet have the self-driving part; instead it is remote controlled. Being able to control it remotely is the first step to adding the autonomous part. The next version will carry a cell phone, which will control the boat and allow the user to remotely log in to enter a destination for the boat to go to.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The body of the boat is made of PLA white plastic and was printed on an Anet A8+ 3D printer in one single print. The model itself was designed with Python and OpenSCAD by my programmer (Peter Chervenski) in a Jupyter notebook. He initially modeled only the motor cases and the propellers to ensure a perfect fit and also to measure how much current the motor draws with the propeller on. With that info, he selected two LM317 regulators for each motor (adjusted to output 12V), one 7805 regulator for the NodeMCU, and two TIP31C MOSFET transistors used as relays.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;He then built a crude model of the electronics on a breadboard and once it worked, soldered the components on a PCB board to make it permanent. The next step was programming the NodeMCU using a computer over the USB port. The program simply turns on/off two pins on the NodeMCU in response to the command it receives over Bluetooth.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;For the remote control part, he wrote an Android app in Java which shows 3 buttons "left", "right" and "both". Touching a button turns on the motor, and lifting the finger from the button turns the motor off. Finally, he added an on/off switch for the whole thing, installed and glued the battery box to the body, then the PCB board, connected all wires and it was done.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;One of the biggest problems with all of this is that weeks worth of work can be ruined by putting the boat in the water and having the electronics get wet. For the boat you see in our video, duct tape was used in an effort to reduce the probability water would get inside. But that did not work very well (plus a piece of the duct tape got caught in the propellers, making noise) so we need to find a better solution.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Our next version of the boat will actually drive itself, and hopefully not sink.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
		</text>
	</dest>

	<dest>
		<thumb>fractional-yacht-ownership</thumb>
		<image>fractional-yacht-ownership</image>
		<link>fractional-yacht-ownership</link>
		<title>Fractional Yacht Ownership</title>
		<desc>Fractional Yacht Ownership Similar is where members share a fleet of boats.</desc>
		<text>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Similar to my recent post about &lt;a href="https://yachts.com/articles/boat-clubs.php" target="_blank"&gt;Boat Clubs&lt;/a&gt;, where members share a fleet of boats, fractional yacht ownership allows you to you share one specific boat with other owners. It is very much like how a timeshare works in real estate.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;One of the main benefits of yacht sharing is that, like with a boat club, everything is handled for you. You don't need to pay for marina fees or insurance, and you don't do any maintenance. It is like renting a car, you just show up and drive.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Some companies, such as &lt;a href="https://sailtime.com/"&gt;SailTime&lt;/a&gt;, let you choose to be either a "Member" or an "Owner". As a Member, you get to share usage of a specific sailboat for a monthly fee.  As an Owner, have a partial share of the yacht, and the company will manage it for you by renting it out for charters, giving you a return on your investment and allowing you also to use the boat yourself. &lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Some other yacht co-ownership companies include:&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sunsailyachtownership.com/"&gt;Sunsail&lt;/a&gt; (also see &lt;a href="https://www.mooringsyachtownership.com/"&gt;The Moorings&lt;/a&gt; which is related)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.dreamyachtcharter.com/yacht-ownership/management-programs/"&gt;Dream Yacht Charter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="https://boatequity.com/"&gt;Boat Equity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="http://monocleyachts.com/"&gt;Monocle Yachts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.avyachts.com/"&gt;AV Yachts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.smartyacht.net/"&gt;Smart Yacht&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="https://seanetco.com/"&gt;Seanet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.flexisail.com/"&gt;FlexiSail&lt;/a&gt;  (UK)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="https://purelatitude.com/"&gt;Pure Latitude&lt;/a&gt;  (UK)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.fairviewsailing.co.uk/Boat-Club/"&gt;Fairview Sailing&lt;/a&gt;  (UK)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="https://virgincharteryachts.com/"&gt;Virgin Charter Yachts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="https://miy-yacht.net/"&gt;MIY Yacht&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.azureultra.com/en/fractional-yacht-ownership/"&gt;Azure Ultra&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="https://ownertimecharters.com/"&gt;Owner Time Charters&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="https://one4yacht.com/"&gt;One 4 Yacht&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Also, these 2 luxury yacht charter companies do not offer fractional ownership, but do have membership programs:  &lt;a href="https://www.yachtlife.com/membership"&gt;Yachtlife&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://me160.isrefer.com/go/Premium/impulse/"&gt;Oceanscape Yachts&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
		</text>
	</dest>

	<dest>
		<thumb>self-driven2</thumb>
		<image>self-driven2</image>
		<link>self-driving-boats</link>
		<title>Self-Driving Boats</title>
		<desc>Autonomous navigation uses AI to drive the boat. Like a Tesla.</desc>
		<text>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;As I wrote about in a recent &lt;a href="https://yachts.com/articles/electric-boats.php" target="_blank"&gt;article&lt;/a&gt;, electric boats are growing in popularity, as they are silent, energy efficient,, and have zero pollution.  But what makes a Tesla car special is not just that is electric, it is that it can drive itself. Although there are not any boats available to general public that do this, there are a bunch of new companies working on it.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Autonomous navigation (in a Tesla or boat) all comes down to using artificial intelligence, which is a good fit for electric vehicles. Now that electric boats have gained some acceptance, the self-driving part is more easily achievable. An example is &lt;a href="https://roboat.org/"&gt;Roboat&lt;/a&gt; (shown in the photo above), which operates in the canals of Amsterdam with no captain or crew.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;One advantage of self-driving vessels is they can be up to 80% smaller, making them cheaper to build, easier to navigate, and less expensive to power. They don't need space for the typical human amenities such as bathrooms, decks, pilothouses, bunks, and kitchens.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Owning a self-driving boat is not just about saving money, it is also about safety.  Ship collisions account for over 1/3 of all maritime accidents, with most of these being caused by human error. Autonomous marine systems never get tired, providing obstacle detection and collision avoidance 24/7.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Using AI does not necessarily mean a human isn't involved. A captain can use this advanced technology to get critical alerts and make more well-informed decisions to prevent accidents.  All of this is especially useful on cargo ships, which account for 90% of global trade.   &lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;div class="caption-image"&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;img src="/images/pages/self-driven3.webp" alt="Self-Driving Boats" class="img-fluid w-100"&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/div&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The image above is from &lt;a href="https://sea-machines.com/"&gt;Sea Machines&lt;/a&gt;, which offers a system that allows a cargo ship to be piloted remotely from a PC. You can even set up a command center to control a fleet of ships.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Other companies developing autonomous boats include &lt;a href="https://www.sea-kit.com/"&gt;SEA-KIT&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://zeabuz.com/"&gt;ZeaBuzz&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.seabubbles.com/"&gt;SeaBubbles&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.metalsharkboats.com/autonomous-vessels/"&gt;Metal Shark&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.rolls-royce.com/products-and-services/defence/naval/advanced-technology/artificial-chief-engineer.aspx"&gt;Rolls Royce&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.buffautomation.com/"&gt;Buffalo Automation&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.artemistechnologies.co.uk/"&gt;Artemis Technologies&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.ibm.com/cloud/automation/mayflower-autonomous-ship"&gt;IBM,&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.liquid-robotics.com/"&gt;Liquid Robotics&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.sailbuoy.no/"&gt;SailBouy&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.saildrone.com/"&gt;Saildrone&lt;/a&gt;,  &lt;a href="https://www.unleash-future-boats.com/"&gt;Unleash Future Boats&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.kongsberg.com/maritime/products/marine-robotics/autonomous-surface-vehicles/"&gt;KONGSBERG&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.l3harris.com/all-capabilities/asview-control-system"&gt;L3Harris&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://openoceanrobotics.com/force12xplorer/"&gt;Open Ocean Robotics&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.orca-ai.io/"&gt;Orca AI&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Soon, you will be able to add Yachts.com to that list. Yes, that is right, we are working on developing our own self-driving boat. So far we are only at the model stage, see below:&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;div class="caption-image"&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;img src="/images/pages/self-driven4.webp" alt="Self-Driving Boats" class="img-fluid w-100"&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/div&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The prototype shown in this photo does not float, as it is much easier to test things out of the water. It uses an Android phone as a brain, a GPS sensor, 3D printed parts, and Python for programming. The phone acts as a server, allowing us to go to a private web page, enter the GPS coordinates for a destination, and have the “boat” automatically go there.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The main problem with this design is that, of course, it is not a boat. A boat needs to deal with moving in water and protecting the electronics from getting wet. And if it gets stuck, we either have to start all over and build a new one, or potentially drown swimming out to retrieve it.  But once we make a little more progress, here’s our potential design: &lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;div class="caption-image"&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;img src="/images/pages/self-driven5.webp" alt="Self-Driving Boats" class="img-fluid w-100"&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;/div&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;This high-tech preview has probably whipped you into a frenzy, wondering how you can get your hands on our marvelous nautical creation. Because we would be overwhelmed with business, and want to focus on research and development, we are not taking any pre-orders (sorry to disappoint you).  But, stay tuned to our site to see the next version, launching in a few weeks.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
		</text>
	</dest>

	<dest>
		<thumb>boat-clubs</thumb>
		<image>boat-clubs</image>
		<link>boat-clubs</link>
		<title>Boat Clubs</title>
		<desc>A boat club offers unlimited access to a fleet of boats for a flat monthly membership fee.</desc>
		<text>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;A boat club offers unlimited access to a fleet of boats for a flat monthly membership fee.  No need to worry about all the costs and hassles associated with owning a boat; the boat club does it all for you: maintenance, slip fees, seasonal hauling and storage, insurance, cleaning, and more. You get the convenience of simply going to the marina and heading out on the water.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The cost of joining a boat club varies by location, but a rough estimate might be that you would pay a $5,000 initiation fee and then $400/month. This gives you the ability to use their boats in your local marina, and also the boats at all their other locations.  Many boat clubs also have member-only social gatherings, making it a good way to meet other boaters.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Don't get a boat club confused with a yacht club (sometimes known as a "sailing club"). A yacht club is like an exclusive country club, with a clubhouse and an attached bar/care/restaurant where members socialize. Yacht clubs also host regattas and races. Unlike a boat club, they are not in the business of rental/sharing boats.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;There are several drawbacks to using a boat club instead of buying your own boat. Many clubs only allow you to take the boats out from 9am to 5pm, and not all boats allow fishing. It also can be hard to get reservations at peak times (weekends and holidays).&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Some of the largest boat clubs include::&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.freedomboatclub.com/"&gt;Freedom Boat Club&lt;/a&gt; - Over 285 locations in the USA, Canada, and France.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://carefreeboats.com/"&gt;Carefree Boat Club&lt;/a&gt; - Around 100 locations in the USA, Canada, British Virgin Islands, Panama, and Philippines.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://yourboatclub.com/"&gt;Your Boat Club&lt;/a&gt; -Minnesota, Illinois, and Wisconsin.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://sovereignboatclub.com/"&gt;Sovereign Boat Club&lt;/a&gt; - Florida only.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dreamboatclub.com/"&gt;Dream Boat Club&lt;/a&gt; -France, Sweden, UK, and Spain.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://nauticalboatclub.com/"&gt;Nautical Boat Club&lt;/a&gt; - Georgia, South Carolina, Tennessee, Texas, and Wisconsin.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://destinationboatclubs.com/"&gt;Destination Boat Clubs&lt;/a&gt; - Florida only.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://sailtime.com/membership/plus/"&gt;Sailtime&lt;/a&gt; - 35 locations across the United States.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;With many of these companies, each location is an independent franchise, so the level of service can vary greatly. Make sure to look up reviews for your specific location before joining.  &lt;/p&gt;             </p>
		</text>
	</dest>

	<dest>
		<thumb>electric-boats</thumb>
		<image>electric-boats</image>
		<link>electric-boats</link>
		<title>Electric Boats</title>
		<desc>There are several new companies that want to become the Tesla of the ocean.</desc>
		<text>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;There are several new companies that want to become the Tesla of the ocean. Electric boats are growing in popularity because they eliminate the harmful pollution and noise of conventional fossil-fuel motors, allowing you to enjoy the sounds of nature and the water. In addition to helping prevent climate change, you also save on maintenance because there are fewer moving parts, and no winterization is needed. Potential customers can either buy a new electric boat, like the one shown in the photo above from &lt;a href="https://voltaireyachts.com/"&gt;Voltaire&lt;/a&gt; (also check out their competitors such as &lt;a href="https://silent-yachts.com/"&gt;Silent-Yachts&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.zinboats.com/"&gt;Zinboats&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://candela.com/"&gt;Candela&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.xshore.com/"&gt;X Shore&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://arcboats.com/"&gt;ArcBoats&lt;/a&gt;) or go with a company such as &lt;a href="https://www.torqeedo.com/"&gt;Torqeedo&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://oceanvolt.com/"&gt;Oceanvolt&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.purewatercraft.com/"&gt;Pure Watercraft&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href="https://www.stealthelectricoutboards.com/"&gt;Stealth Electric Outboards&lt;/a&gt; that offers electric outboard motors to convert your existing boat. To help keep Boston Harbor clean, there is even a company named &lt;a href="https://www.electricboatsboston.com/"&gt;Boston Electric Boats&lt;/a&gt; that rents out only electric boats.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Another advantage is that electric engines are around 75% cheaper to run, in terms of the cost of the electricity vs the gasoline. And like with a Tesla, they have almost instant acceleration, which is something many boaters appreciate, while the complete absence of oil residue, toxic fumes, and noise pollution is something the marine life will appreciate.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Many electric boats are built for slowly driving around a harbor or lake, while others such as the Zin Boat can go up to 35mph, with a range of 80-100 miles (powered by a BMW i3 battery, it recharges using a 110V or a 220V plug, making life much easier). Sailboats can also be a good fit for an electric motor, as it is only needed for short durations, like when there is no wind, or for heading into the harbor or marina. And in Norway and Finland, electric ferries have been successfully running for several years.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;The first electric boat was built by German inventor Moritz von Jacobi in 1839 in Russia. It had a top speed of 3 miles per hour, was 24 feet in length, and carried 14 passengers. From the 1880s to the 1920s electric boats became popular but were eventually replaced by gas-powered motors. The recent resurgence is due to dramatic advances in battery technology and solar power, as well as the growing concern about global warming. Just like with the electric car market, adoption has started off slow due to high prices and limited availability, but sales are projected to reach $10 billion by 2026.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Another advantage of electric boats is that they can much more easily be autonomously controlled, as compared to a standard boat. This means, like with a Tesla, it can use artificial intelligence to be 'self-driving'. We will explore that topic further in our next article.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
		</text>
	</dest>

	<dest>
		<thumb>yachts-dotcom-theme-song</thumb>
		<image>none</image>
		<link>yachts-dotcom-theme-song</link>
		<title>Yachts.com Theme Song</title>
		<desc>To commemorate the launch of Yachts.com, I wrote a fun theme song for the site.</desc>
		<text>
			
			<p>&lt;style&gt;.caption-image{padding-top:56.25%;}.caption-image>iframe{position:absolute;left:0;top:0;width:100%;height:100%;}&lt;/style&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;div class="caption-image"&gt;&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/yF9ujfwWiyM" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;To commemorate the launch of Yachts.com, I wrote a theme song for the site.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Lyrics and melody by &lt;a href="https://mcericb.com/"&gt;Eric Borgos&lt;/a&gt;, vocals by&lt;a href="https://www.fiverr.com/ninthent/"&gt; IntrovertDAME&lt;/a&gt;, music video by Eric Borgos and &lt;a href="https://www.fiverr.com/enoproductions"&gt;Eno Productions&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Lyrics:&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h2&gt;VERSE 1&lt;/h2&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Boats they come&lt;br /&gt; in all shapes and sizes&lt;br /&gt; wealth and power&lt;br /&gt; a yacht symbolizes&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Ride them in bays&lt;br /&gt; ride 'em in oceans&lt;br /&gt; give the common people&lt;br /&gt; jealous emotions&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Wind in your hair&lt;br /&gt; the smell of success&lt;br /&gt; life on the water&lt;br /&gt; without worry and stress&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;So go call your banker&lt;br /&gt; lawyer or trust&lt;br /&gt; we only live once&lt;br /&gt; then all turn to dust&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h2&gt;CHORUS&lt;/h2&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Yachts.com&lt;br /&gt; Yachts.com&lt;br /&gt; Yachts.com&lt;br /&gt; Ya Ya Yachts&lt;br /&gt; Dot Com&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h2&gt;VERSE 2&lt;/h2&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Some rich folk buy islands&lt;br /&gt; or fly into space&lt;br /&gt; toilets of gold&lt;br /&gt; and sports cars to race&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;but on journeys nautical&lt;br /&gt; they're missing out&lt;br /&gt; the sun and the seas, ya&lt;br /&gt; that's what life's about&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Caviar, wine&lt;br /&gt; everything lux&lt;br /&gt; no better way&lt;br /&gt; to spend all your bucks&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;So make the champagne flow&lt;br /&gt; turn the music loud&lt;br /&gt; and party it up&lt;br /&gt; with the billionaire crowd&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;h2&gt;CHORUS&lt;/h2&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Yachts.com&lt;br /&gt; Yachts.com&lt;br /&gt; Yachts.com&lt;br /&gt; Yachts.com&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Yachts.com&lt;br /&gt; Yachts.com&lt;br /&gt; Yachts.com&lt;br /&gt; Ya Ya Yachts.com&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Yachts.com&lt;br /&gt; Yachts.com&lt;br /&gt; Buy a yacht&lt;br /&gt; For your dad and mom&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Yachts.com&lt;/p&gt;</p>
		</text>
	</dest>

	<dest>
		<thumb>tcs</thumb>
		<image>none</image>
		<link>the-crazy-story-of-the-100000-yacht</link>
		<title>The Crazy Story of the $100,000 Yacht</title>
		<desc>The wild, real-life adventures of YouTuber Airrack as he wins a yacht, drops it in Logan Paul's swimming pool, and drives it to Mr Beast's private island. </desc>
		<text>
			<p>&lt;style&gt;.caption-image{padding-top:56.25%;}.caption-image>iframe{position:absolute;left:0;top:0;width:100%;height:100%;}&lt;/style&gt;</p>
			<p>In the series of 4 real-life videos below from YouTuber Airrack (Eric Decker), he gets chased by a bounty hunter to win a $100,000 yacht, drops the yacht in Logan Paul’s pool, then drives the yacht to Mr. Beast’s private island in the Bahamas:</p>
			<p>&lt;div class="caption-image"&gt;&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/gTpGSgxBbzM" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;div class="caption-image"&gt;&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/VdfMIfAvzqA" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;div class="caption-image"&gt;&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZkKRdC4QLoo" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;div class="caption-image"&gt;&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/k2e9838HxQ4" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</p>
		</text>
	</dest>

	<dest>
		<thumb>sleep</thumb>
		<image>sleep</image>
		<link>sleep-afloats</link>
		<title>Sleep Afloats - Dockside Boat Rentals</title>
		<desc>Instead of going to a hotel or Airbnb for your next vacation, sleep aboard a yacht or houseboat. Relax on the water, enjoy the oceanfront views, and get away from it all.</desc>
		<text>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;Instead of going to a hotel or Airbnb for your next vacation, sleep aboard a yacht or houseboat. Relax on the water, enjoy the oceanfront views, and get away from it all. This is not charter tour where you go sightseeing; the boat stays on the dock the whole time. Known as “Boat Bed and Breakfasts”, “Sleep Afloats”, “Houseboat Rentals”, “Boat BnBs”, and “Sleep Aboards”, some available rentals include:&lt;/p&gt;</p>
			<p>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sleepafloat.com" target="_blank"&gt;SleepAfloat&lt;/a&gt; (Boston and Philadelphia)&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.bedandbreakfastafloat.com" target="_blank"&gt;Bed and Breakfast Afloat&lt;/a&gt; (Boston)&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.boatbnb.com" target="_blank"&gt;Boatbnb&lt;/a&gt; (San Diego, CA)&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.bedsonboard.com" target="_blank"&gt;Bedsonboard&lt;/a&gt; (Mostly in England but has some US listings)&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sleep-aboard.com" target="_blank"&gt;Sleep Aboard&lt;/a&gt; (Rhode Island and Boston)&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.yachtsuites.net" target="_blank"&gt;Yacht Suites&lt;/a&gt; (Redwood City, CA) &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://boatandbed.com" target="_blank"&gt;Dockside Boat &amp; Bed&lt;/a&gt; (Long Beach, CA)&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://boatelonthewater.com" target="_blank"&gt;Boatel On The Water&lt;/a&gt; (CA)&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.businessinsider.com/best-boat-airbnbs#desert-houseboat-with-pool-in-joshua-tree-california-3" target="_blank"&gt;Airbnb&lt;/a&gt; (Worldwide)&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.getmyboat.com/boat-rental/houseboat-overnight/" target="_blank"&gt;GetMyBoat.com&lt;/a&gt; (Worldwide)&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://americanhouseboatrentals.com" target="_blank"&gt;American Houseboat Rentals&lt;/a&gt; (On 30 lakes nationwide)&lt;/p&gt;                    </p>
		</text>
	</dest>
</Destination>