<?xml version="1.0"?>
<countries>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Fiji</country>
		<image>Fiji</image>
		<place>Fiji</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>This is a South Pacific archipelago of more than 300 exotic islands that boasts beautiful coral reefs with clear lagoons, rugged landscapes, and majestic beaches that are lined with palm trees.</p>
			<p>Most Fijian islands are not open for tourism because of how remote they are, which presents the ultimate opportunity for adventure for yacht owners and charterers.</p>
			<p>A Fiji yacht charter is indeed the most ideal way to explore this archipelago that offers such a beautiful mix of tropical surroundings, a creative fusion of cultures, and the much-needed thrill that most travelers seek, making it a wonderful yachting destination. Whether you are looking for a romantic getaway, an adventure with friends, or a peaceful family vacation, Fiji caters to all types of trips.</p>
			<p>Some of the most noticeable features and characteristics of this island country have to be its swaying palm trees, white sandy beaches, and clear blue waters.</p>
			<p>One thing that has made Fiji such a desired yachting spot is how each island has a unique identity and brings its own distinctive attractions and cultures. The collection of as many as 300 islands create a literal boating mecca, many of which are waiting to be explored and cruised.</p>
			<p>Some of the most-visited spots in Fiji are the Mamanuca Islands and Yasawa Islands that offer you a chance to visit Fijian villages and explore their way of life. You can further head north to the northern called Vanua Levu, where you are likely going to be lucky enough to witness a marine spectacle.</p>
			<p>If you are looking to experience a memorable and adventurous charter vacation, Fiji should definitely be on your list because it offers a unique feel of paradise. More than that, the kind of serenity, natural beauty, and seclusion found here is almost unparalleled to anywhere else.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>fiji</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Fiji</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Croatia</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Croatia</country>
		<image>Croatia</image>
		<place>Croatia</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>With spectacular beaches, clear waters, and a glorious coastline, it's no wonder why Croatia is one of the best yacht charter destinations in the world.</p>
			<p>Located in Central and Southeast Europe, Croatia offers you an exotic yachting playground with a number of harbors, islands, and picturesque seaside villages to explore.</p>
			<p>A yacht charter in Croatia is just the right way to explore its stunning Dalmatian Coast, which is home to a plethora of striking islands. You will also find walled fortress cities and quaint villages there that are surrounded by beautiful lavender fields and olive groves. The Adriatic coastline will further blow you away as it is nothing short of a breathtaking landscape. A tranquil, blue-green sea surrounds forested mountains and peaceful islands here which makes this whole place a truly must-visit sight.</p>
			<p>Croatia has long been a hot destination for not only travel enthusiasts, but also charterers and yacht owners. A luxury charter yacht vacation offers a fantastic escape as you go over its crystal clear waters, pristine islands and coastal villages.</p>
			<p>When yachting in Croatia, Split is the ideal place to start which is Croatia's second-largest city and has some of its most famous islands just a short cruise away such as the islands of Brac, Kor?ula and Hvar. This city and its surrounding areas both proudly boast some of Croatia's largest marinas that are home to most of the yachts.</p>
			<p>The best time to go on a yacht trip in Croatia is September-October when the sea is warm and serene, the summer crowds have vanished, and the weather is just perfect.</p>
			<p>With Croatia's unique beauty and what all it has to offer to you, you will find picture-worthy spots at every turn while on your yacht, giving you endless opportunities to capture the little details of this breathtaking region.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>croatia</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Croatia</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Galapagos Islands</country>
		<image>Galapagos-Islands</image>
		<place>Galapagos Islands</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>When it comes to visiting and exploring the Galapagos Islands in the Pacific Ocean, the best way to experience it is through a private yacht, and there are no two ways about it.</p>
			<p>This volcanic archipelago is known for its magnificent volcanic formations, crystal clear blue waters, exotic marine life, and beautifully colored sandy beaches.</p>
			<p>The Galapagos Islands are often referred to as a naturalist's dream considering all the natural beauty and picturesque views it has to offer. One of the biggest focal attraction points of these islands is its extraordinary biodiversity that thrives with the kind of landscapes and wildlife that you've probably never seen elsewhere in the world.</p>
			<p>Did you know that the Galapagos Islands have been given the title 'Living Laboratory' because of how they are home to such a unique and beautiful array of species, some of which aren't found anywhere in the world.</p>
			<p>Some of the main ports in the Galapagos Islands for a luxury yacht charter vacation include Santiago, Santa Cruz, Genovesa, San Cristobal Santa Fe, and Espanola. The ideal time to plan a yachting trip to these islands is between January and June, during which the weather is super warm, and the waters are incredibly serene.</p>
			<p>Most vacationers opt for a private crewed yacht charter when visiting the Galapagos Islands because they get to experience its beauty and the fabulous natural life without any interference or interruptions. Regardless of that, a luxury charter to the Galapagos Islands promises breathtaking landscapes and backdrops, fascinating land and bird inhabitants, volcanic formations, and incredible marine life, including dolphins, sharks, sea turtles, sea lions, and marine iguanas.</p>
			<p>Needless to say, a yacht trip to these islands will be a one-of-a-kind experience that will probably last in your mind forever!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>galapagos-islands</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Galapagos Islands</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>Alaska</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Alaska</image>
		<place>Alaska</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>An untouched paradise and a wonderful gem of the world, Alaska brings you diverse exotic wildlife, gigantic glaciers, massive landscapes, and gorgeous mountains and forests.</p>
			<p>Located towards North America's northwest corner, this state is truly one of the best and must-visit luxury yacht destinations in the whole world. You may have already traveled Alaska by air, but this time around, you must consider an Alaskan charter vacation which will be an experience unlike any other.</p>
			<p>One of Alaska's most wonderful characteristics is its idyllic stillness which is perfect for a yachting experience because you can easily set your own pace and explore different spots for as long as you want. Some must-have experiences on your charter definitely include cruising past beautiful icebergs, whale watching between Ketchikan and Glacier Bay, and listening to the unique sounds of a glacier calving.</p>
			<p>When cruising in Alaska, you must begin with Juneau, which is the capital of this state and is reachable only through a seaplane or a boat. This town is located in the southeast region and is thriving with character and beauty. One of the most popular glaciers in Juneau is the Mendenhall Glacier, where you will get to see stunning ice formations that have been transforming the very landscape for thousands of years.</p>
			<p>Your next stop could very well be Tenakee Springs in Tlingit roots, an area that is mainly visited for its hot mineral springs. The best part is you can indulge in a number of water activities here such as kayaking, fishing, and whale watching, among many others.</p>
			<p>Simply put, a yacht charter vacation to Alaska will bring you an unparalleled cruising experience, and your journey will be full of discovery and exploration.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>alaska</link2>
		<areas>Anchorage, Seward, Homer, Whittier, Sterling, Halibut Cove, Wasilla, Skwentna, Cooper Landing, Willow, Kenai, Butte, Soldotna, Palmer, and Ninilchik.</areas>
		<criteria>Alaska, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Bahamas</country>
		<image>Bahamas</image>	
		<place>Bahamas</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>The gorgeous islands of the Bahamas have long been one of the most popular destinations among travelers, owing to the country's beautiful weather, white sand beaches, historic spots, and more than 700 picturesque islands.</p>
			<p>When it comes to tropical traveling, the Bahamas is an absolute staple, and as the saying goes,'it's better in the Bahamas!'</p>
			<p>It lies southwest of Florida, peacefully resting within the Lucayan Archipelago, and is undoubtedly one of the most desirable destinations for charterers, yacht owners, and luxury charter yacht guests alike.</p>
			<p>The Bahamas are one of those year-round travel spots with 700 islands and cays, each of which has its own unique personality and different activities to offer. While these islands are perfect for resort vacations and commercial cruise ships, a yacht charter is a whole other territory that allows you to explore the sleepy seaside settlements and hidden gems of the islands at a beautifully slow pace.</p>
			<p>A Bahamas yacht charter trip should definitely kick-start with Nassau, the largest city of the Bahamas and also its capital. This bustling commercial center is home to the Atlantis Paradise Island Resort, where the marina easily berths yachts that are up to 240 feet (73m) long. It is home to an array of natural harbors and stunning secluded beaches that have hundreds of miles of clear blue waters.</p>
			<p>This tropical perfection provides yacht charter guests a chance to experience unparalleled escapism and breathtaking views of its sun-kissed pink sands.</p>
			<p>With 100,000 square miles of ocean providing home to over 700 majestic islands, it can be quite tough to figure out where to go in the Bahamas. But, a great option is to head south to the Exumas, which is an archipelago of almost 365 spectacular islands, all scattered across a tranquil, clear blue sea.</p>
			<p>Needless to say, a private yacht charter in the Bahamas is one of the must-have experiences ever!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>bahamas</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Bahamas</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Thailand</country>
		<image>Thailand</image>	
		<place>Thailand</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Looking for the absolute best vacation that provides the perfect combination of cultural immersion, scenic views, and an incredibly relaxing time?</p>
			<p>With clear blue waters, unique and delicious cuisine, and a lively ambiance, it's no surprise that Thailand is one of the world's most popular vacation destinations.</p>
			<p>Located on the South East side of Asia, you can enjoy delicious Thai street food by the beach while exploring the several islands there. Soak in all the beauty Thailand has to offer by chartering a yacht through Phuket and visiting all the famous adjoining islands to it. From there, you can visit the world heritage site 'Phang Nga Bay,' best known as the James Bond Island where the infamous movie was filmed.</p>
			<p>Another one of tourists' favorite vacation destinations happens to be the Phi Phi islands that done stunning and picturesque spots to bathe in the sun and enjoy the unique Thai cuisine. These islands also have absolutely clear and blue options that done a myriad of various types of sea life and coral reef, offering you one of a kind snorkeling and diving experience.</p>
			<p>But that's not all; you can also learn about the Thai culture and Buddhist religion as you are likely to see one or two monks descending from their sunset prayers. Hence, the country is a fantastic destination for those looking to appeal to their visual senses and increase their knowledge simultaneously.</p>
			<p>Besides the picturesque beach, ancient ruins, and ornate temples, you can also explore their opulent royal palaces that have been around for decades. Thailand has so much to offer that it will definitely make you want to keep coming back.</p>
			<p>If you want to feed the adventurer wanderlust in you, then book your yacht trip to the beautiful and mesmerizing region now!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>thailand</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Thailand</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Sicily</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Italy</country>
		<image>Sicily</image>	
		<place>Sicily</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>One of the largest Mediterranean islands, Sicily is an ideal vacation destination as it offers you the chance to learn about its rich history spanning over centuries, explore exotic locations, and indulge in incredible cuisines.</p>
			<p>Located at the 'toe' of Italy's 'boot,' this mesmerizing island is the place to visit for a myriad of reasons. It offers breathtaking views of the three seas surrounding the island, provides unique architecture, with an ever-so-friendly and authentic Italian ambiance. Though a major chunk of this island comprises mountains and hills, you can alternatively visit the seven islands that make up the Aeolians on your yacht endeavors. The Aeolian Islands are not to miss when you charter your yacht in Sicily.</p>
			<p>While you visit Sicily, you can also see its major tourist spots, including Mount Etna, Stromboli volcanoes, and various cliffs. Moreover, you can also expect to tantalize your taste buds with Sicily's fresh produce and wine. Don't forget to try their seafood as well when you're there.</p>
			<p>If you are looking for a luxury chart yacht vacation, look no further than Sicily. This is also the place where you can find Europe's biggest fashion designers and richest celebrities relaxing. After all, this is where big names like Dolce and Gabbana and Vincenzo Bellini hailed from. Sicily is a popular retreat for the rich and famous.</p>
			<p>Start your luxurious chart yacht vacation through Sicily and Aeolian islands from Portorosa, Palermo, or Capo d'Orlando, and then sail west to the clear coastlines and scenic beaches of the Egadi Islands. Then, end your vacation with a retreat in the Aeolian Islands.</p>
			<p>Needless to say, by charting your yacht through Sicily, you will return with an unforgettable experience and feel relaxed and rejuvenated!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>sicily</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Sicily, Italy</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Costa Rica</country>
		<image>Costa-Rica</image>	
		<place>Costa Rica</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Costa Rica, the popular Central American country, is the perfect representation of the saying, good things come in small packages!</p>
			<p>It might be a small country, but it has so much to offer and is simply extraordinary in its truest sense.</p>
			<p>This country is located in Central America, and it is peacefully nestled between the Pacific Ocean and the Caribbean Sea. It is literally brimming with extensive stretches of beach, hidden gushing waterfalls, and thriving jungle life. The spectacular beauty and natural wonders of this country certainly call for a Costa Rican luxury yacht charter where you will find an ideal mix of adventure, radiating sun, beaches, warm weather, serene waters, and culture in its 51,000 square kilometers.</p>
			<p>Costa Rica's strategic location between the sea and ocean is what makes it such a fantastic spot and location for yacht charterers. It is quite a literal haven for luxury yacht charter holidays featuring azure waters, picturesque landscapes, and dormant volcanoes.</p>
			<p>Most beach getaways in Costa Rica are quite laidback and peaceful, with the exception of Playas del Coco, which is the perfect starting point for your luxury yacht charter vacation. It is the ultimate party destination, so if you wish to kick-start your cruise trip with a bang, this is the way to do it!</p>
			<p>With a rich coast, fascinating biodiversity, exotic food, and picturesque views every step along the way, a Costa Rican yacht charter is going to be the highlight of all your vacation to this day!		</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>costa-rica</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Costa Rica</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>New England</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>New-England</image>	
		<place>New England</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>If you are looking to get away from the hustle and bustle of your city, one of the best and most relaxing getaways you can consider spending is in New England.</p>
			<p>Located in the Northeastern region of the United States, this charming yacht destination is the place to go if you want to learn more about colonial history and witness one-of-a-kind lush forests, sand dunes, tranquil bays, ambient ports, and much more.</p>
			<p>During your time chartering through New England, you can visit the quaint villages and explore all the prestigious universities located there that have taken over global dominance.</p>
			<p>New England is one of those places that make you want to keep coming back for more because there is so much to see and do. You can start off your yacht chartering tour from Newport and sail towards the sandy shores and lush green hills of Block Island for some downtime by the sea. Then, visit the ever so picturesque vineyards and orchards before reaching Cape Cod, one of the most popular islands with peaceful villages.</p>
			<p>There are also various swimming and kayaking spots in New England that beg to be explored. You can find them while chartering through the Elizabeth Islands. There, you will also feel as if you have traveled back in time if you go to the outskirts of the island and visit the colonial Cuttyhunk.</p>
			<p>Lastly, many yacht charters also include visiting the fancy Hamptons, where the affluent spend their retreats. The place is dotted with old stone and shingle buildings and designer shops, providing an air of glamour.</p>
			<p>While the summers may be the best time to visit New England, you can also explore the islands during fall time, when you can witness the changing colors of the maple leaves, all bringing about a plethora of colors.</p>
			<p>There is so much that New England has to offer, especially to yacht charters, which makes it the place to be for an unforgettable experience!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>new-england</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>New England, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Balearic Islands</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Spain</country>
		<image>Balearic-Islands</image>	
		<place>Balearic Islands</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>If you are looking for the perfect island-hopping trip, look no further than the Balearic Islands. With clear blue oceans, cool breezes, amazing nightlife, delicious cuisines, quaint towns, and so much history, what more could you want?</p>
			<p>It offers a plethora of opportunities to visit one island to another, and the sandy beaches will leave you with a guaranteed tan!</p>
			<p>The Balearic Islands are one of the best gems Spain has to offer. Visiting these islands will be the perfect yacht charter experience because they happen to be a short distance from other adjoining islands and beautiful coastal towns.</p>
			<p>For example, on your Balearic Islands yacht charting endeavors, you can park your yacht at the docks of Ibiza, Mallorca, and Menorca. Ibiza happens to be the best place for any party-goer as it is dotted with clubs, and the nights are lit up with them.</p>
			<p>In Mallorca, you cannot just tantalize your taste buds with delicious food but also visit natural places seldom explored by man. These include Mallorca's caves and hidden bays that will surely win your heart. The white strips of sand will provide you with scenic views you may have never seen before.</p>
			<p>Moreover, you can sail further into the tiny beach of Cala Hort, where you can witness the charming view of the spectacular three Dragon Islands. This place feels absolutely magical, with a twilight atmosphere and sweeping vistas.</p>
			<p>When you go to Menorca, you can park your yacht at the famous Port Mahon and then travel back in time by visiting the many ancient fortresses and buildings. While you are there, don't forget to swim and dive into the clear waters of Cala Macarelleta.</p>
			<p>Visit this sunny corner of Spain by chartering your yacht from Barcelona. With beautiful vistas, unforgettable nightlife, and hidden natural gems, this is a must-have experience for anyone!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>balearic-islands</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Balearic Islands, Spain</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Santorini</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Greece</country>
		<image>Santorini</image>	
		<place>Santorini</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<P>With beautiful multi-colored beaches, hilltop towns, breathtaking sunsets, and picturesque backgrounds, Santorini is undoubtedly one of the most popular and must-visit islands in Greece. It is often described as idyllic, spectacular, and exquisite, but it is so much more than that.</P>
			<P>This Greek island calls for an amazing luxury Greek yacht charter vacation where the gushing topaz blue sea will simply blow you away. Whether you wish to cruise from one beach to the other or from its wineries to the lighthouse, a yacht is the right way to go about it.</P>
			<P>Santorini is a small Greek island spanning an area of about 76.19 km² and is located in the Cyclades in the Aegean Sea. It is the main island in the Cyclades archipelago and also boasts the title of the 'Black Pearl' of the Aegean Sea.</P>
			<P>Once you find yourself somewhere in the middle of this gorgeous island in a yacht, you probably won't ever feel like leaving from there. A yacht charter vacation to this island will take you over Santorini's iconic beaches and also let you explore the surrounding top sights and islands.</P>
			<P>You can even stop for fun-filled water activities like snorkeling, swimming, and sunbathing, and once you are back on the yacht, you can look forward to indulging in delicious meals and other luxurious amenities offered by the yacht.</P>
			<P>Santorini Island is steeped in history and was basically formed from volcanic ruins, which is one of the many reasons why it's such a popular travel destination among people from all over the world. It is one of the world's most magnificent natural sights, and there aren't enough reasons for you to explore the island on a yacht and take in all its wonderful beauty. A yacht is the best way indeed to sightsee this remarkable archipelago!		</P>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>santorini</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Santorini, Greece</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>French Riviera</state>
		<country>France</country>
		<image>French-Riviera</image>	
		<place>French Riviera</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Fancy a summer in the South of France?</p>
			<p>There's no better way to explore that area than with a yacht charter. Sail through the French Riviera that truly comes alive during the summertime and is lit up with concerts, festivals, and so much more. But that's not all; the French Riviera lets you experience the true essence of fine dining as you can hop off and visit the several high-class restaurants.</p>
			<p>Besides the mounds of entertainment and delicious cuisine, French Riviera offers you the chance to relax and unwind at one of the most scenic beaches in the world at Saint Tropez. The quaint town surrounding the beach and harbor is worth exploring since you can find gorgeous architectural sights and music. The night comes alive at Saint Tropez with clubs and exclusive parties that will truly make your time there worth remembering.</p>
			<p>On your yacht charter through the French Riviera, Cannes is a must-visit. Just a short walk from the port, you can delve into the world of fashion by visiting the plethora of boutiques there. The place is riddled with fashion designers and celebrities alike all year round. In Cannes, you can partake in a range of water sports or sunbathe at the beaches in complete solitude and privacy.</p>
			<p>Besides Cannes, the places at the French Rivera that should be on your yacht charter itinerary include Monaco, Nice, Antibes, and Villefranche-sur-Mer. There, you can unwind and relax, explore the rich French heritage, enjoy luxurious cuisines, pay a visit to the museums, and lastly, enjoy spectacular views and sunsets.</p>
			<p>Needless to say, summer in the world's most luxurious yacht destinations will be one to remember. It is the perfect destination for anyone since it offers so much to beach bums, history buffs, fashionistas, foodies, and party people!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>french-riviera</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>French Riviera, France</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>British Virgin Islands</country>
		<image>British-Virgin-Islands</image>	
		<place>British Virgin Islands</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>This British overseas territory is located towards the east of Puerto Rico in the Caribbean and is has been titled Nature's Little Secrets.</p>
			<p>The British Virgin Islands are easily one of the best and most ideal sailing destinations in the Caribbean, and they call for a yacht charter trip!</p>
			<p>With breezy winds and warm weather all year round, these islands are a paradise on earth featuring sunny skies, secluded bays, expansive landscape, and a number of hidden coves. Another reason why the British Virgin Islands warrant a luxury private yacht charter is the fact that these islands are exclusive and untouched as they don't have a direct air service from the North American mainland or the UK.</p>
			<p>As soon as you enter the islands on your yacht, you will notice clear blue waters, pristine beaches, and endless opportunities to indulge in some of your favorite water activities and sports.</p>
			<p>These islands are a yachter's true delight as they sprawl across the Atlantic Ocean and the Caribbean Sea. What's amazing about the islands is they are very eco-conscious and are heavily focused on green energy, so you will actually be able to see and notice how clean and clear the air is in the British Virgin Islands.</p>
			<p>From exotic, remote locations to a massive culinary scene to exciting water sports to unmatchable splendor, the British Virgin Islands have a little something to explore for every individual out there. And there's no better way to do that than on a private yacht cruising through the gorgeous islands!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>british-virgin-islands</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>British Virgin Islands</criteria>
	</location>
	
	<location>
		<city>Corsica</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>France</country>
		<image>Corsica</image>	
		<place>Corsica</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<P>After Sicily, Sardinia, and Cyprus comes Corsica. It is the fourth largest island in the Mediterranean and a popular holiday destination among travelers from all over the world.</P>
			<P>This idyllic island, South East of mainland France is also famous for yachting and for all the right reasons, too. With its emerald tree-lined shores, huge mountainous landscapes, and sun-kissed picturesque backdrops, Corsica is truly a sight to behold.</P>
			<P>The best and the most ideal time to go on a yacht charter to Corsica is the month of May until the starting few days of June. The air is filled with a pleasant fragrance, and everything is in full bloom during this time.</P>
			<P>To make the most of your yachting trip on this island and explore its beauty and splendor in full, it is best to leave from Sardinia. This Italian island is like the perfect gateway to Corsica and is literally in the heart of the Mediterranean Sea. As you sail towards Corsica, you will come across vast areas of untouched nature, elegant coastal towns, and stunning beaches.</P>
			<P>Once you reach Corsica, head towards Cap Course, a long peninsula sitting on clear blue waters towards the island's northern end.</P>
			<P>Calanques de Piana is the next must-visit spot, which is like a world heritage site waiting to dazzle you on Corsica's west coast.</P>
			<P>A Corsica yacht charter is an absolute must-have experience that will truly blow you away and probably leave you craving for more!</P>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>corsica</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Corsica, France</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Turkey</country>
		<image>Turkey</image>	
		<place>Turkey</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Yachting in Turkey is nothing short of a memorable, wonderful experience. With a fusion of historical ruins and a buzzing modern life, Turkey is your ultimate yachting paradise that is full of Mediterranean beauty.</p>
			<p>When you embark on a yacht charter in Turkey, one of the best places to start from is Pamukkale, a town that is home to beautifully warm waters that quietly flow down on nearby hillsides across shiny white-tiered terraces.</p>
			<p>With gorgeous mosques, mysterious ruins, and magnificent architecture, there's no denying the fact that Turkey is one of the most stunning countries truly blessed by Mother Nature.</p>
			<p>The coast of Turkey is scattered with quiet and secluded bays and coves where you can take a break from the hustle bustle of life and unwind for as long as you want. As you sail along the coast, you can even stop for some fun-filled water activities like snorkeling, swimming, and sunbathing, among many others.</p>
			<p>Some of the must-visit spots on your Turkey yacht charter include Butterfly Valley Beach, an exotic cove laced with sun-kissed golden sand, Cold Water Bay, with its freshwater springs, and AsiKoyu, a relatively smaller bay that is very famous among scuba diving enthusiasts, due to the abundance of majestic sea life found here.</p>
			<p>Needless to say, whichever route you take on your yacht in Turkey, you will be blown away at each and every stop!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>turkey</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Turkey</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Corfu</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Greece</country>
		<image>Corfu</image>	
		<place>Corfu</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Known for its exciting culinary scene that features fresh, local, delicious ingredients, Corfu is a beautiful Greek Island on the northwest coast in the Ionian Sea.</p>
			<p>With sun-kissed sandy beaches, pleasant, mild climate, unparalleled natural beauty, and stunning villages, Corfu has been titled 'the emerald queen of the Greek Islands.'</p>
			<p>The magnificent beaches on this island are simply reason enough to make it your next getaway, but you know what would make it even better? Chartering a yacht through Corfu and exploring the plethora of islands with anchorages and marinas, its dazzling sunshine, and the many splendid views that you will come across on the way.</p>
			<p>When yachting through Corfu, you should ideally begin by exploring the North Ionian, where the Paxi islands bring you clear beaches, excellent snorkeling spots, and some of the most stunning cliffs ever. Then, there are the fishing villages of Sagiada and Petriti, followed by picturesque beaches along the coast of Corfu.</p>
			<p>If you've never been to Corfu, perhaps, you could plan your next trip or vacation there and explore the North Ionian Islands that are brimming with charming and lovely harbors featuring picture-perfect anchorages that have such crystal clear waters.</p>
			<p>What's not to love about that?</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>corfu</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Corfu, Greece</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Monaco</city>
		<state>French Riviera</state>
		<country>France</country>
		<image>Monaco</image>	
		<place>Monaco</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>One might wonder what the world's second-smallest country could possibly even have to offer.</p>
			<p>Well, the answer is &lt;em&gt;everything.&lt;/em&gt;</p>
			<p>Resting peacefully and quietly on the French Riviera, the tiny principality of Monaco, also referred to as the 'sparkling jewel of the French Riviera,' warrants a visit on a yacht.</p>
			<p>As you cruise along the French Riviera, you will get a chance to explore the richness, beauty, and sheer elegance that this beautiful country has to offer. Like many people, you might find yourself thinking that a day is enough to explore this place, but the chances are that once you begin going around on your yacht, you will want to stay for longer and take in every inch of its beauty and splendor.</p>
			<p>The coast of the French Riviera is literally brimming with jaw-dropping views and picturesque sights, the kind that makes you wish for time to stop.</p>
			<p>There's no better way to enjoy your trip to Monaco to the fullest than chartering a yacht and discovering the hidden gems as you cruise around the country.</p>
			<p>A Monaco yacht charter will give you a wonderful opportunity to explore a spectacular fusion of pure luxury, exhilarating nightlife, fine dining, lit casinos, and stunning architecture.</p>
			<p>Don't forget to stroll along Port Hercule to see all the exotic yachts, and also visit The Prince Palace in the old town. If you have a thing for yachts and would be interested in touring the most impressive yachts in the world, attend the annual Monaco Yacht Show held during September and prepare to be blown away!		</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>monaco</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Monaco, French Riviera, France</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Seychelles</country>
		<image>Seychelles</image>	
		<place>Seychelles</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>An archipelago of 115 coral and granite islands off East Africa, rising from the tranquil waters of the Indian Ocean, Seychelles is the ultimate hub of unparalleled beauty. Each island is brimming with natural splendor, including thick and dense forests, smooth rock formations, serene blue-green waters as well as national parks that are fully alive thanks to the thousands of exotic and incredible animal species.</p>
			<p>With so much more to offer, Seychelles presents a one of a kind opportunity for you to explore massive cruising grounds on uninhabited islands that will give you your much-needed privacy and relaxation. A luxury yacht charter vacation to Seychelles means being able to feel your feet on white, soft and powdery sun-kissed beaches where palm-fringed hills, clear topaz seas and granite boulders create an idyllic, picture-worthy scenery that is likely going to blow you away.</p>
			<p>Seychelles has to be on your list for a charter vacation with either friends or family because it truly is like paradise on earth with its white sandy beaches lined with coconut palms sitting against a picturesque backdrop of absolutely beauty and wilderness.</p>
			<p>It also has a year-round charter season and an abundance of natural harbors, so there's no reason why you shouldn't take a yacht charter to Seychelles on your next getaway.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>seychelles</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Seychelles</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Italy</country>
		<image>Italy</image>	
		<place>Italy</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Italy is an utterly beautiful yacht charter destination where some of the most famous spots for a yacht charter include Amalfi Coast, The Gulf of Naples, Sicily, and the Aeolian Islands, where each of them has a unique, fascinating history, cuisine, and culture to offer.</p>
			<p>The Amalfi Coast has to be one of the most globally-desired yachting spots in Italy, owing to its pristine beaches, vibrant waters, spectacular cliffs, and stunning coastline.</p>
			<p>An Amalfi Coast yacht charter will give you a wonderful opportunity to explore Italy like never before and make you want to never leave this place!</p>
			<p>Then comes Sardinia, an Italian island that is found right in the heart of the Mediterranean Sea. With its emerald green waters, dazzling beaches, sheltered coves, and pink granite coastline, Sardinia offers you a real taste of Italy.</p>
			<p>You might also want to take your yacht to Naples, the third-largest pulsating seaside city in Italy that has Mount Vesuvius in the background.</p>
			<p>Wherever you sail, one thing is for sure - a luxury yacht charter in Italy will be the most exotic, incredible, and mind-blowing experience of your life!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>italy</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Italy</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Tahiti</country>
		<image>Tahiti</image>	
		<place>Tahiti</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>A great jewel of the South Pacific, with natural beauty waiting to be explored and waters yet to be discovered. Tahiti is a luxurious South Pacific island that lies halfway between California and Australia.</p>
			<p>One of the ideal ways to explore this island and its surrounding splendor is none other than a luxury yacht charter vacation where you will also get to capture its romance and beauty in real-time. Tahiti surely isn't your average vacation spot, but it's a true paradise surrounded by surging rivers, gushing waterfalls, ribbons of coral reefs and multiple layers of rainforests.</p>
			<p>This French archipelago is home to numerous hidden gems of nature, including exotic animal life, winding trails, and massive lakes resting peacefully behind thick greenery and foliage.</p>
			<p>A must-visit destination in Tahiti is none other than Plage Lafayette, a truly stunning beach in the northern part of the island that is surrounded by gigantic aggressive mountains from one side. These mountains open up and allow you to look out into an endless sea.</p>
			<p>There's no surprise as to why Tahiti has long become such a popular hub for private yacht charters, and as your Tahiti yacht charter cruises across the untamed beauty of this majestic island, it will forever capture your heart.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>tahiti</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Tahiti</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Malaysia</country>
		<image>Malaysia</image>	
		<place>Malaysia</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Known as the 'jewel in the crown of South East Asia,' Malaysia is truly all that and more.</p>
			<p>Malaysia's northeast coast is home to some of the most enchanting islands that provide the perfect yacht charter cruising ground.</p>
			<p>Among the many exotic islands in the archipelago are Langkawi and Penang, which most people have probably already visited before, but a yacht charter will provide an unparalleled experience in itself.</p>
			<p>A yachting charter vacation presents travelers and tourists with a wonderful opportunity to explore the number of bewitching islands off the coasts of Malaysia. With peaceful and laid-back scenery, clear blue waters and expansive blue skies, Malaysia offers an outstanding natural landscape that will truly blow you away.</p>
			<p>All these islands are full of spectacular caves, limestone hills and tranquil lakes, the beauty of which can fully be explored only on a yacht charter.</p>
			<p>The east coast of Malaysia is home to Tioman, a budding sailing area and the islands that surround it. You will find absolutely stunning and out of this world coral reefs that make it one of the most popular diving spots in the country.</p>
			<p>So, for your next vacation, take a yacht charter in Malaysia and get to feel and know how it's like to explore unchartered waters!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>malaysia</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Malaysia</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>Florida</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Florida</image>	
		<place>Florida</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Internationally known as the 'sunshine state,' Florida is so much more than Walt Disney and exhilarating theme parks. It's also your next go-to yachting destination, considering how the state of Florida is home to Miami and Fort Lauderdale, two of the most vibrant and rich yachting hubs in the whole world, let alone in all of Florida!</p>
			<p>These hubs are the ideal gateway for tourists and travelers to explore all the main Florida Keys along with what all they have to offer, earning itself the title of 'Yachting Capital of the World.'</p>
			<p>Featuring a melting pot of cultures and magnificent natural beauty, Florida is one of the most picturesque backdrops you need for your luxury yacht charter vacation.</p>
			<p>When cruising through Florida, Fort Lauderdale, Key West, West Palm Beach, and Miami are your go-to spots if you happen to be seeking plentiful marine life, secluded pristine beaches, and the most exquisite natural backdrops doused in the dazzling sunshine.</p>
			<p>On Florida's southern tip lies Everglades National Park, a region of tropical wetlands that is home to sawgrass marshes, coastal mangroves and hundreds of animal species living in the Pine Flatwoods. This park has unparalleled natural beauty, the kind that makes your eyes go round and your jaw drop with wonder.</p>
			<p>You might have already been to Florida before, but a yacht charter is going to be a whole different experience, one that will make you want to cruise endlessly.</p>		
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>florida</link2>
		<areas>Miami, Fort Lauderdale, Clearwater, Hollywood, Tampa, Miami Beach, St. Petersburg, Sarasota, Destin, Key Largo, Jupiter, Naples, Daytona Beach, Plantation, Cape Coral, Panama City, Delray Beach, Boca Raton, Holiday, Jacksonville, Deerfield Beach, Sunny Isles Beach, Riviera Beach, Denia Beach, Aventura, Merritt Beach, Islamorada, Pompano Beach, Marco Island, Fernandina Beach, Sebastian, Leesburg, Madiera Beach, Palm Beach Gardens, Bradenton, Niceville,  Key Biscayne, Sebring, St. Augustine, Nokomis, Tarpon Springs, Cudjoe Key, Lighthouse Point, Brooksville, Palm Beach, The Florida Keys, Key Biscayne, Coral Gables, Clearwater Beach, West Palm Beach, Orlando, Pensacola, Gulf Breeze, Madeira Beach, Ruskin, Indian Rocks Beach, New Port Richey, Cocoa Beach, Palm Beach Shores, Palm Bay, Harbour Beach, Port St. Lucie, North Palm Beach, Boynton Beach, Crescent City, New Smyrna Beach, Hallandale Beach, Dania Beach, Miami Shores, Hialeah, Homestead, Hypoluxo, North Bay Village, Key West, Biscayne Bay, Tampa Bay, Fort Myers, Bal Harbour, Bushnell, Miami Bay, Fort Pierce, Hallandale, Saint Augustine, Fort Myers Beach, St Lucie River (Stuart), Lake Mary, Merritt Island, Umatilla, and Sanibel Island.</areas>
		<criteria>Florida, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>US Virgin Islands</country>
		<image>US-Virgin-Islands</image>	
		<place>Us Virgin Islands</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Known as one of the most exotic and picturesque cruising grounds, the US Virgin Islands truly calls for a private luxury yacht charter vacation.</p>
			<p>A Caribbean crewed charter is the ideal way to explore these gorgeous islands surrounded by crystalline waters that are so serene and peaceful.</p>
			<p>There are many factors that make the Virgin Islands a sailor’s and a yachter’s ultimate delight that include quiet and tranquil palm-fringed anchorages, pristine white beaches, and spectacular views along the way.</p>
			<p>The US Virgin Islands are one of those year-round cruising destinations with excellent weather and beautiful views no matter what time of the year you go yachting to the islands. A luxury charter yacht adventure in the Caribbean is a great chance for you to discover and explore the three unique gems that include St Croix, St Thomas, and St John. These are the three main islands in the region, each of which has something different and amazing to offer to you.</p>
			<p>For instance, St Thomas Island is all about buzzing nightlife and a vibrant form of entertainment, whereas St John brings you a whole other form of serenity and peace amid its unspoiled beauty and secluded location.</p>
			<p>Needless to say, a yacht charter in the Virgin Islands will truly blow you away!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>us-virgin-islands</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>US Virgin Islands</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Milos</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Greece</country>
		<image>Milos</image>	
		<place>Milos</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Known as the ‘Island of Colors,’ Milos is one of Greece’s most beautiful treasures. If you have visited the country before, you know that it is nothing short of gorgeous. But this volcanic island of the country is just something else.</p>
			<p>With mesmerizing shorelines, private beaches and bays, and fascinating rock formations, it’s safe to say that there is no place like Milos. The sheer variety of things you will witness while chartering your yacht through the island will be unmatchable and unforgettable.</p>
			<p>With as many as seventy beaches to visit and a myriad of other attractions, Milos is an island getaway that you will need to spend several weeks at to discover fully. Chartering a yacht there will help you explore places that are off-limits by foot or car, for example, the Milos Viper and the Kleftiko beach.</p>
			<p>Not just that, but Mother Nature has truly blessed the island as you can visit places like Sarakiniko beach, which quite literally resembles the surface of the moon. Safe to say, you will find the best spots in Milos for your Instagram shots!</p>
			<p>Milos holds a plethora of history dating back to the Neolithic period, and that can be noted from the various rock and volcanic formations. But that’s not all; there are several other must-see places when on a yacht charter through Milos that you simply cannot miss, such as the Ancient Theater of Milos, Kimolos Island, Philakopi, Plaka, Arkudos Rocks, and so much more.</p>
			<p>The coast of Milos is scattered with multiple hidden beaches and bays that you can only explore by sea. Just tie up and discover these forgotten and seldom explored corners of this ancient island.</p>
			<p>Needless to say, whichever corner of the island you go to, you will have an unforgettable time, witness stunning views, and come across multiple photo ops!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>milos</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Milos, Greece</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Nantucket</city>
		<state>Massachusetts</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Nantucket</image>	
		<place>Nantucket</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Translated as the ‘Far Away Island,’ Nantucket is truly one of the most beautiful attractions in Cape Cod and one that must be chartered through a yacht.</p>
			<p>When you step off your yacht onto its sandy beach, you will feel yourself transported when you witness the cobbled streets, cedar-shingled buildings, 19th-century homes, and historic lighthouses. Though Nantucket is a small island, its natural beauty and history have been preserved, which keeps travelers wanting to keep coming back.</p>
			<p>That’s not all though, the compact size of the island provides a more intimate community life, which you cannot find anywhere. This is also in part thanks to the friendly atmosphere that riddles the entire place.</p>
			<p>The chic island is also scattered with pristine beaches, museums, trendy art galleries, one-of-a-kind boutiques, and Michelin star restaurants. All in all, it is truly the perfect luxurious getaway when on a yacht.</p>
			<p>Nantucket is one of the most popular and attractive destinations for yacht charterers for a good reason. The natural beauty and myriad of relaxing activities ensure the perfect escape from the hustle and bustle of city life to simply unwind.</p>
			<p>As you start your yacht chartering experience from the historic Boston harbor, you can also choose to spend some downtime at the stunning destination Cape Cod. Moreover, the summers would be the best time to visit the beautiful island of Nantucket.</p>
			<p>There is so much you can do on the island, including cycling through the town, sport fishing in the bays, swimming on the beach, and so much more.</p>
			<p>Needless to say that you will be returning from Nantucket with a golden tan, thanks to the various outdoor activities and unforgettable experiences!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>nantucket</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Nantucket, Massachusetts, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Cuba</country>
		<image>Cuba</image>	
		<place>Cuba</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Cuba isn’t just another island in the Caribbean – it is, actually, a whole different, one-of-a-kind experience.</p>
			<p>Numerous archipelagos surround this country, and there’s no denying the fact that nature has blessed the land with beautiful waves crashing against it from the Caribbean.</p>
			<p>A Cuba yacht charter will bring your dream vacation to reality as you cruise against the colorful architecture, agricultural valleys, and stunning atolls that feature plentiful marine life, clear waters, and gorgeous white stretches of land.</p>
			<p>Cuba is one of the most popular destinations among charters, yacht owners, and sailors alike.</p>
			<p>Did you know that Christopher Columbus discovered the island of Cuba in 1492? And upon discovering it, he said, “This is the most beautiful land one has ever seen.”</p>
			<p>Find the perfect catamaran or monohull and spends hours of relaxation and enjoyment amid the picturesque nature.</p>
			<p>The Cuban coast is home to many natural wonders and hidden gems that will steal your breath away and might even make you never want to leave the island!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>cuba</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Cuba</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Indonesia</country>
		<image>Indonesia</image>	
		<place>Indonesia</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>It probably doesn’t come as a surprise that Indonesia is a must-visit yacht charter destination for your next vacation or getaway. Even if you’ve already been there, an Indonesian luxury yacht charter will be unlike any other travel experience.</p>
			<p>This is the largest island country in the world, and you must have heard of its alluring natural beauty and splendor, massive volcanic islands, fields and forests brimming with greenery and nature, and its astounding cliffs.</p>
			<p>This blossoming and booming island country calls for that perfect yacht charter destination to explore its thousands of islands, bringing you a myriad of unique traditions and cultures.</p>
			<p>Needless to say, Indonesia is a real yachting paradise and every sailor’s dream. Among its countless majestic islands is Bali, which most of us have seen before, if not in person, then in pictures for sure!</p>
			<p>Bali is one of the ideal spots in Indonesia to kick-start your yacht charter, after which you can go on to explore Komodo National Park, Lombok, and the secluded areas of the Banda Sea.</p>
			<p>Another must-visit region is Jakarta, which is notably the heartbeat of Indonesia. Some of the most famous landmarks in Jakarta include the Monumen Selamat Datang, Monas, the National Museum, Merdeka Palace, Istiqlal Mosque, and Jakarta Cathedral.</p>
			<p>When cruising on a yacht charter in Indonesia, you can’t help but notice the spectacular beaches lining Indonesia’s coastline, where you can just relax, take pictures or play in the water to your heart’s content.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>indonesia</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Indonesia</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>China</country>
		<image>China</image>	
		<place>China</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>You might have never thought of a luxury private yacht charter in China, but as it turns out, this beautiful country in East Asia has become a hugely popular destination for charter. It brings you an exotic fusion of stunning beaches, bright and lit cities, stunning landscapes, and of course, a unique culinary affair.</p>
			<p>Some of the best and must-visit destinations in China are none other than Shanghai, Sanya and Shenzhen, where you can explore the gorgeous waters surrounded by picturesque views of nature.</p>
			<p>China is home to an incredible 14,500km of coastline that allows charter guests to soak in everything that the coastline has to offer right from their yacht.</p>
			<p>A charter in China calls for some major highlights that include Wuzhizhou Island, a butterfly-shaped island that is home to as many as 2700 different types of plants, Shanghai’s The Bund promenade where the modern skyscrapers of Lujiazui in the Pudong District will simply blow you away, and the coast of Shekou where you can cruise along, experience the magical sunset, and enjoy breathtaking views of Shenzhen’s skyline.</p>
			<p>China is undoubtedly where all the magic and adventure starts, and a private luxury yacht charter is indeed the best way to experience it all.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>china</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>China</criteria>
	</location>
	
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Belize</country>
		<image>Belize</image>	
		<place>Belize</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Located in Central America and peacefully resting between its thick jungles and the beautiful clear waters of the Caribbean Sea, one can’t have enough reasons to visit Belize.</p>
			<p>This Caribbean country is a natural, laid-back paradise on earth with many hidden gems that are yet to be explored. It’s also less crowded and unspoiled as compared to other regions of the Caribbean, making it a must-visit destination on a luxury yacht charter.</p>
			<p>If you are looking to go for an exciting vacation amid the most alluring natural beauty, you must sign up for a Belize cruising vacation. This country is best known for its unparalleled natural beauty, protected waters that offer super chartering, and world-class scuba diving and snorkeling.</p>
			<p>Some of the must-visit spots in Belize include Laughing Bird Cay that offers the best snorkeling and bird watching, the moorings at Cocoa Plum Cay’s Thatch Cay Resort where, if you get lucky, you will be able to see a number of exotic wildlife creatures such as brocket deer, coatimundi, and spider monkeys.</p>
			<p>Needless to say, wherever you go and cruise, you will find many exciting things to do and wonderful scenic views to explore from your luxury yacht charter.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>belize</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Belize</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Cannes</city>
		<state>French Riviera</state>
		<country>France</country>
		<image>Cannes</image>	
		<place>Cannes</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Cannes is a stunning Mediterranean hotspot that has quite a unique look and feel of opulence attached to it. The city is synonymous with luxury living, given it’s often brimming with celebrities. This city presents the perfect Mediterranean retreat to anyone looking to take a break.</p>
			<p>With fully-equipped yacht harbors, spectacular beaches, and a plethora of fine-dining restaurants, Cannes is your ideal go-to yachting destination for a quiet, peaceful, and serene yachting vacation.</p>
			<p>If not anything else, Cannes Film Festival is reason enough to go on a private luxury yacht charter. Did you know this international film festival kick-starts the summer yachting season in this city where travelers from all over the world gather here in the Mediterranean?</p>
			<p>Cannes is also the perfect starting point to explore the countryside of the south of France and its surrounding areas.</p>
			<p>With an untouched love of the arts, ever refined culture, and exquisite tastes, a yachting vacation in Cannes will ultimately bring you the best of both worlds!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>cannes</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Cannes, French Riviera, France</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Ibiza</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Spain</country>
		<image>Ibiza</image>	
		<place>Ibiza</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>One of the famous Balearic Islands, Ibiza is a must-visit island for luxury yacht charters and is a true paradise for superyachts.</p>
			<p>This Spanish island is located off the eastern coast of Spain in the Mediterranean Sea and is best known for its exhilarating nightlife. When you are in Ibiza, the music has no chance of stopping!</p>
			<p>If you are looking for the most enjoyable, fun-filled, and electric time of your life, a luxury private yacht charter is definitely the best way to go about it.</p>
			<p>The magnificent beaches and coastlines, along with the never-ending party scenes in Ibiza, will literally breathe new life into you, and you will have such an amazing time cruising on this majestic island. Once you have had a proper dose of Ibiza’s pulsating nightlife, head over to two of its most beautiful and idyllic beaches called Cala Salada and Cala d’Hort. These golden, sun-kissed beaches boast the clearest and the bluest waters that gently hit the sand and retreat. Snorkeling, sunbathing, swimming, and sailing are four of the most popular and loved activities done on these beaches that will keep you busy all day long.</p>
			<p>If you want something more peaceful and secluded, there’s a private island in Ibiza called S’Espalmador that pulls in yachts for a relaxing, quiet time.</p>
			<p>As the nightlife in Ibiza continues to excite you, the natural beauty and splendor will just blow you away.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>ibiza</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Ibiza, Spain</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Grenada</country>
		<image>Grenada</image>	
		<place>Grenada</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Popularly dubbed as the ‘Spice Isle,’ Grenada is one of the most stunning Caribbean destinations for a luxury yacht charter. It is located in the West Indies in the Caribbean Sea, and it’s truly about the natural beauty that will blow you away.</p>
			<p>Grenada has everything that you would want in a yacht-worthy destination, from beautiful idyllic beaches lined with swaying coconut palms to picturesque views that provide utmost relaxation.</p>
			<p>Grenada is the ideal place to start your cruise, given how it’s a gateway to the massive cruising grounds of the Grenadines.</p>
			<p>When you are on a Grenada yacht charter, you will get to explore the many amazing beaches that make up its coastline which also includes 1.9 mile-long Grand Anse Beach in St. George Paris, one of the world’s greatest beaches.</p>
			<p>Among many other things, Grenada is home to the most magnificent kind of marine life, and while cruising, you will probably be able to spot a variety of little fish, turtles, dolphins, and rays.</p>
			<p>From swimming the corals to relaxing and unwinding on a sun-kissed sandy beach to going on a hike through its rainforests, a Grenada yacht charter will open up many possibilities for you to have fun and an excellent vacation!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>grenada</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Grenada</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Australia</country>
		<image>Australia</image>	
		<place>Australia</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Australia boasts the most diverse coastline in the world and also the best snorkeling and diving. The biggest highlight on a cruising vacation in Australia is the Great Barrier Reef that is known as the largest living structure on earth. It is also the world’s largest reef system ever. It is home to as many as 9000 different species of marine life, including dolphins, sharks, whales, turtles, stingrays, and many others.</p>
			<p>Another must-visit spot is Fraser Island that you can explore on a jeep safari. You also get to swim in incredible dune lakes, visit the majestic rainforests and relax on the sandy beaches doused in the dazzling sunshine.</p>
			<p>If you are a thrill-seeker, you must visit the Gold Coast, which has some of the most exhilarating theme parks, followed by an unbeatable nightlife.</p>
			<p>When cruising in Australia, Sydney definitely calls for a visit on your luxury yacht charter. This city has endless opportunities for fun and enjoyment and is home to the best culinary delights, national parks, and architectural styles, among many other things.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>australia</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Australia</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Crete</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Greece</country>
		<image>Crete</image>	
		<place>Crete</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Looking for the ultimate escape for your next yacht charter?</p>
			<p>The Greek island of Crete offers a welcoming and ever so sweet escape with its bustling nightlife, semi-private beaches, endless sunshine, and wonderful weather all year round. But that’s not all; the island boasts unbelievably scenic coastal lines and hidden treasures worth exploring.</p>
			<p>One of the most populated islands in Greece, Crete is filled with amazing spots that beg to be explored. Needless to say, one trip to this massive island is not enough. From the scrumptious food, ancient Greek history dating back to centuries, and naturally beautiful mountains and beaches, Crete will leave you wanting more.</p>
			<p>Chartering your yacht is one of the best ways to explore this eclectic island as you get to enjoy the semi-private beach life, bask in the glorious Greek sunshine, and soak in all the scenic views that the island has to offer. The island of Crete is also a popular hiking spot, with the Samaria Gorge being a major tourist attraction.</p>
			<p>On your yachting vacation in Crete, one of the must-visit places, includes the bustling capital of Heraklion. It is riddled with beautiful Venetian architecture, fine dining restaurants, and cute cafes. Making a trip even for a day here will be worthwhile. Moreover, you must also visit the charming little village of Elounda and witness its charming harbor, picturesque cafes, and quaint streets. If you are in the mood for water sports, you can try your hand at snorkeling in Elounda.</p>
			<p>Crete eludes energy and relaxation simultaneously, which is why it is one of the most popular tourist destinations. There is so much to explore as you traverse through its clear waters, including gorgeous towns and villages.</p>
			<p>Experience the rich Greek culture as you charter your yacht through this southernmost tip of Greece and have an undeniably amazing time.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>crete</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Crete, Greece</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>French West Indies</state>
		<country>France</country>
		<image>French-West-Indies</image>	
		<place>French West Indies</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>If you are looking for a distinctively unique yacht charter experience, French West Indies will be your perfect destination!</p>
			<p>This wonderful part of the Caribbean is made up of the gorgeous islands of Martinique, Dominica, Guadeloupe, and Isle de Saints, all of which offer a uniquely exclusive experience. As the name suggests, it also boasts a distinctive French culture that is worth visiting and exploring.</p>
			<p>As you charter your yacht through the warm blue Caribbean waters, you can choose to stay offshore, enjoy their delightful beaches, or go into the quaint towns that offer a fantastic cultural mix, scrumptious dishes, and the best island life. The best thing to do while you are there is to island-hop and explore what each offers.</p>
			<p>Not to mention the fact that this island is warm throughout the year; this is why it is filled with tourists all the time, especially during the festive seasons.</p>
			<p>One of the must-visit places in the French West Indies is the La Soufrière, which is the highest peak on the island and happens to be an active volcano. Since it is inactive for most of the year, you can go up to the sides of the volcano if you are feeling adventurous. Moreover, if you are looking for a bit more adventure, you must visit the two islands of Guadeloupe that offer opportunities for jungle trekking and swimming through rocky ravines.</p>
			<p>French West Indies offers tourists a plethora of activities; from sailing to snorkeling and hiking, it will definitely keep adults and children entertained 24/7. On your luxury vacation to these Caribbean islands, don’t forget to add the islands of Dominica and Martinique to your itinerary.</p>
			<p>Needless to say, there is no vacation much like the one you can have on your yacht charter through French West Indies!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>french-west-indies</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>French West Indies, France</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Malta</country>
		<image>Malta</image>	
		<place>Malta</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>If you’re looking for a worry-free yachting location, Malta is definitely a top contender for that. An optimal easily accessible location in the central Mediterranean housing one of the world’s most scenic natural harbors, Malta is also renowned for its highly developed docks and repair facilities.</p>
			<p>Seated just below Italy, this Mediterranean archipelago boasts a rich and long cultural history dating back to the time of the Romans with a range of beautiful prehistoric architectural phenomenon. One can find beautiful anchoring spots in the country’s numerous beaches and docks located in the northern and western shorelines, and with more research one can also find hidden gems across the coastline that offer a more secluded attraction.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>malta</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Malta</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Windward Islands</country>
		<image>Windward-Islands</image>	
		<place>Windward Islands</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Also known as the Islands of Barlovento, Windward Islands presents the perfect luxury yacht charter</p>
			<p>destination in the Caribbean for anyone looking for a peaceful, laid-back kind of vacation.</p>
			<p>With stunning views, untouched sun-kissed beaches, and dramatic vistas, the Windward Islands has</p>
			<p>more than 600 spectacular beaches for you to explore on your yacht charter. A majority of these islands</p>
			<p>have secluded anchorages and beautiful palm-fringed beaches on the shoreline, along with many plush</p>
			<p>tropical rainforests.</p>
			<p>If you are a true nature enthusiast, you will find the Windward Islands perfectly according to your liking</p>
			<p>with many opportunities for hiking across the jungle-clad waterfalls or zipping through the dense forest</p>
			<p>canopies.</p>
			<p>One of the biggest highlights of the Windward Islands is Barbados, a spectacular island that has it all.</p>
			<p>From brilliant turquoise bays to interiors dotted with lush gardens to powdery sands, this island truly</p>
			<p>deserves a yacht charter vacation.</p>
			<p>If you are looking to have that ideal vacation where you get to see majestic sights and also relax at the same time, Windward Islands certainly won’t disappoint you!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>windward-islands</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Windward Islands</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Red Sea</country>
		<image>Red-Sea</image>	
		<place>Red Sea</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>The Red Sea is one of the four seas named after color terms, which include the Yellow Sea, Black Sea and the White Sea. A yacht charter is the ideal way to explore some of the most stunning coastal treasures hiding away within the Red Sea.</p>
			<p>The Red Sea offers unique and incredible opportunities for all yachters to experience be it cruising across Hurghada yachting haven or the Sharm El Sheik for a spectacular diving session.</p>
			<p>The east coast of the sea in particular is like paradise on earth with its untouched and unexplored pristine wilderness. It offers the ultimate private escape that most of us need from the hustle and bustle of daily life where you will find an explosion of bays, islands, and coves.</p>
			<p>One of the best things about the Red Sea as a yachting destination is that the east coast has literally no crowds and its reefs are largely untouched. The warm waters here are the perfect home to marine life and feature excellent visibility so gear yourself for little glimpses of heaven below right from your private yacht charter!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>red-sea</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Red Sea</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Miami</city>
		<state>Florida</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Miami</image>	
		<place>Miami</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>This Florida city is a buzzing destination for tourists from all over the world and chances are that you’ve already been here before.</p>
			<p>But, if you haven’t had the chance to explore Miami on a luxury charter, it’s time for you to plan a yachting trip to this gorgeous city!</p>
			<p>Pulsating, tantalizing and exotic are three words that best describe this city that literally comes to life at night and stays up all night long.</p>
			<p>With its blue Biscayne Bay views and colorful skyline set against the vast skies, one can’t have enough reasons to visit this stunning city.</p>
			<p>A Miami yacht charter trip is certainly incomplete without exploring the shockingly blue waters that lay alongside its beautiful white beaches.</p>
			<p>A great place to start cruising in Miami is the Historic Virginia Key Beach which is close to downtown Miami that opens up multiple opportunities for you to explore the city to the fullest!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>miami</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Miami, Florida, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Martinique</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>France</country>
		<image>Martinique</image>	
		<place>Martinique</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>This rugged Caribbean island is best described as the “one place that has it all.”</p>
			<p>With breathtaking natural beauty, pulsating culture and traditions, exciting hiking trails and a plethora of exhilarating water sports that you can possibly imagine, Martinique has so much to offer you and more.</p>
			<p>The cafes and restaurants in Martinique offer a true representation of the French gastronomy and culinary flair, and that’s just one bite of the large slice of wonders that this island has in store for you.</p>
			<p>It is also known as the Island of Flowers and calls for a luxury private charter vacation that will simply leave you in awe.</p>
			<p>A Martinique yacht charter is the one and only way to really explore and take in everything about this French-Caribbean paradise. If you are a hiking enthusiast, the plethora of guided trails and rainforests are your ideal exploration avenues followed by the breathtaking views of the peaks of Carbet and Mont Pelée.</p>
			<p>While on the yacht charter, you will find yourself cruising against a backdrop of dazzling shorelines, lush tropical rainforests and vast blue skies.</p>
			<p>So, if you get a chance to go on a yacht charter vacation, make sure Martinique is on the list!	</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>martinique</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Martinique, France</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Costa Smeralda</city>
		<state>Sardinia</state>
		<country>Italy</country>
		<image>Costa-Smeralda</image>	
		<place>Costa Smeralda</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Looking for the perfect mix between contemporary chic, architectural history, and natural beauty?</p>
			<p>While places like Venice and Rome are swarmed with tourists, this coastal destination is not. Yet, it is one of the top places to visit if you are vacationing on a yacht. Located in Northern Sardinia in Italy, Costa Smeralda is truly a feast for the eyes.</p>
			<p>The emerald waters and sandy beaches will be enough to convince you of its beauty. But the beautiful backdrop of mountainous terrain here will certainly leave you in awe. For a luxury yacht charter vacation, there is no better place than this vacation destination off the coast of Italy.</p>
			<p>Costa Smeralda also boasts an eclectic mix of designer boutiques, chic cafes, exclusive clubs, and one-of-a-kind bars. Take your fine dining experience to the next level by visiting the world-class restaurants at this fantastic Italian gem. But that’s not all; here, you can get arguably the best lobster in the world. So don’t forget to relish in the savory and delicious seafood this place has to offer.</p>
			<p>On your yacht charter through this area of the breathtakingly beautiful Mediterranean island of Sardinia, don’t forget to visit the capital of Cagliari to admire the medieval castles, churches, and architectural landmarks, before stopping on the pebbled streets for a sip of coffee.</p>
			<p>The clear waters and white beaches at Costa Smeralda will constantly allure you and will be the ideal feat for any sailor. While there, you must also visit the surrounding destinations. For example, don’t forget to visit Porto Pollo for kite surfing, snorkeling, and a bunch of other incredible underwater experiences. Other than that, destinations like Portisco, Villasimius, and Cala Di Volpe should also be on your list of places to visit.</p>
			<p>Needless to say, Costa Smeralda is a place like no other and one that begs to be visited on a yacht!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>costa-smeralda</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Costa Smeralda, Sardinia, Italy</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Dominica</country>
		<image>Dominica</image>	
		<place>Dominica</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Looking for a yacht charter experience that lets you explore nature to its fullest? Then look no further than the Caribbean island of Dominica!</p>
			<p>Known as the ‘Nature Isle of the Caribbean,’ this island comes unmatched by all others. There’s a reason why this ever so attractive island has been designated as a UNESCO world heritage site.</p>
			<p>With no direct international flights taking you to this eccentric island, the best way to get here is by water, giving you one more reason to charter this island with a yacht. You can catch a short cruise from Guadeloupe and Martinique, and then take your yacht to this beautiful island.</p>
			<p>Dominica is filled with natural hot springs, tropical rainforests, sandy beaches, and clear waters. Though not a quintessential luxury yacht vacation destination, this island is perfect for adventurers who want to charter unexplored natural reserves.</p>
			<p>One of the best things to do is hike on the challenging but rewarding trails the island offers, so you can enjoy breathtaking views from the top. After this, you can also opt to soak under the natural waterfalls or steaming hot natural springs to calm your nerves and rest.</p>
			<p>The island of Dominica is filled with natural reserves and produce, so you can expect to indulge in unique and world-class organic rums, beers, coffees, and much more. While you are there, you can also experience the Dominican culture and spend time with the warm and inviting locals.</p>
			<p>Though it is a contrast to a luxury yacht charter vacation, visiting Dominica will be an experience like no other. You will get ultimate privacy, enjoy local cuisines, spend time with the locals, and best of all, experience natural beauty and views that will surpass all others you will ever see in the world.</p>
			<p>So, are you ready for a once-in-a-lifetime adventure with your yacht charter vacation to Dominica?</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>dominica</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Dominica</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Greece</country>
		<image>Greece</image>	
		<place>Greece</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>There are probably no surprises as to why Greece is a top yachting destination in the world. This country in southeastern Europe is dotted with thousands of gorgeous islands that are scattered throughout the Aegean and the Ionian Sea.</p>
			<p>Greece has long been referred to as a ‘mariner’s paradise’ since forever and for all the right reasons too. A private luxury yacht charter to Greece will take you over its wine-dark seas which are a sight to behold on their own.</p>
			<p>There’s so much to see and explore in this part of southern Europe such as the natural beauty and splendor of its deserted isles to the stunning beaches drowning in the dazzling sunshine and magnificent islands like Mykonos that seem to be thriving with a cosmopolitan nightlife.</p>
			<p>Further down, you get to explore the tavernas of Athens on your private luxury yacht to the beach bars in Crete, the largest island in Greece. If you fancy a relaxing night stopover, you can cruise towards Santorini and spend the night on an archaeological exploration and stay up to witness a mesmerizing sunset from the upper deck.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>greece</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Greece</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Norway</country>
		<image>Norway</image>	
		<place>Norway</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Looking for dramatic scenery and views on your next yacht charter vacation? Then you must consider Norway!</p>
			<p>Known as the Island of Vikings, Norway is a destination that will leave you in awe of its vast seas, gorgeous waterfalls, unique mountains, and beautiful glaciers. But that’s not all. You can also visit the cosmopolitan cities to experience the modern lifestyles of the locals while sipping on hot coffee.</p>
			<p>There are endless things to do when you charter your yacht through the country. From exploring the wilderness of Svalbard, where polar bears outnumber people, to experiencing the Northern Lights while staying in the igloos, it is obvious that you will have an incredible time, to say the least.</p>
			<p>You must begin chartering your yacht through the west coast of Norway, where you can stop by at the quaint fishing villages, unexplored bays, and elaborate summer homes. This coastline is also dotted with multiple hiking trails that you can travel to. When you want to rest your aching muscles, you can also soak in the several waterfalls lined at the coastline in Norway.</p>
			<p>While you are there, don’t forget to visit the Norwegian Fjords that are nestled between remarkable mountains. The charming port city of Bergen is also a must-visit while on your yacht vacation in Norway. This UNESCO world heritage site will also let you explore mystical peaks and breathtaking valleys like no other in the region.</p>
			<p>Conclude your memorable vacation at the capital of Norway, the bustling city of Oslo. Here, you can experience fine dining unlike any other in Europe, explore the lively bars, and learn more about Norwegian history at their museums.</p>
			<p>Needless to say, a yacht charter experience through this Scandinavian country will leave you breathless from the start to the finish of your journey!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>norway</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Norway</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Singapore</country>
		<image>Singapore</image>	
		<place>Singapore</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>The island city-state is a must-visit destination for a private yacht charter experience!</p>
			<p>It is the perfect mix of colonial history, unique cuisine, interesting culture, buzzing nightlife, and so much more. For this reason, it draws millions of tourists each year from all over the world. There are so many things to do on this island that it will keep you busy and thoroughly enjoyed throughout your time there.</p>
			<p>You can visit Universal Studios for some adventure, go to the world-renowned bird parks, visit the breathtaking temples, shop on the mainland, or simply cruise through the blue waters that surround the entire city. All in all, there are endless things to do when you are in Singapore.</p>
			<p>Since the nightlife here is unparalleled, it begs to be experienced by tourists. There are dozens of bars, restaurants, pubs, and clubs here, and each one offers a good time.</p>
			<p>The breathtaking region of Singapore is a mix of modernity, history, and culture. It is one of the cleanest and most efficient cities in the world, which is why it hosts so many tourists all year round. One of the best ways to visit it is by taking a yacht there and visiting the surrounding islands.</p>
			<p>With a plethora of things to do, Singapore is surely an enchanting city that will make the best holiday for anyone!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>singapore</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Singapore</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>San Francisco</city>
		<state>California</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>San-Francisco</image>	
		<place>San Francisco</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<P>If you are looking for a unique short getaway, then you must visit San Francisco bay!</P>
			<P>There’s no better way to explore it than with a private yacht charter across the beautiful blue ocean. Whether a local or a visitor, you will definitely not regret going on this unique and ever so relaxing experience.</P>
			<P>Having been the subject of numerous songs and movies, the city is an eclectic mix of culture, adventure, and relaxation. From hiking in the several trails to dining at the beautiful vineyards, or going into the city for a taste of culture and unique cuisine, there will simply not be a dull moment on your yacht charter through the San Francisco bay.</P>
			<P>Your vacation will be incomplete though if you don’t cruise underneath the vast Golden Gate bridge that will leave you in awe of its glory. You can also stop by at the Golden Gate Park for a relaxing break, and visit the museum there.</P>
			<P>Other sightseeing spots and destinations that are not to be missed include the Alcatraz prison, hiking at the trails at Land’s End lookout, and of course, visiting Lombard Street to see the world’s most crooked street.</P>
			<P>Experience the fantastic and mouthwatering seafood at Fisherman’s Wharf where you can dock your yacht. This is not to be missed if you are a seafood fan because it is considered to be one of the best seafood in the world.</P>
			<P>The unique history of San Francisco lends itself to be a must-visit destination for all. Not to mention the delicious cuisine in the city, the beautiful and cool breeze at the bay, clear waters, diverse culture, and so much more.</P>
			<P>Needless to say, there will definitely be something for everyone on this yacht charter experience to the San Francisco bay!</P>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>san-francisco</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>San Francisco, California, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>New Zealand</country>
		<image>New-Zealand</image>	
		<place>New Zealand</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<P>Explore the unexplored hidden treasures as you charter your yacht through the wonderful waters of New Zealand!</P>
			<P>The vibrant and beautiful country is filled with abundant opportunities for adventure, relaxation, and exploration. With lush forests, warm and sandy beaches, semi-tropical lakes, dormant volcanoes, and gorgeous mountains, there is definitely something for everyone in this unique island country. And there is no better way to discover all of these than with a private yacht charter.</P>
			<P>However, that’s not all; when you charter your yacht through the cobalt blue ocean, you can stop by at the wonderful towns of the country. Here, you can immerse yourself in the history, culture, and fantastic cuisine that New Zealand has to offer. The coastline of the country is considered to be one of the best sailing destinations as it is dotted with bays, fjords, and harbors.</P>
			<P>On your yacht charter through the country, you must visit the Bay of Island that provides stunning landscapes and scenery. The marine life is incredible there, so don’t forget to take a dip in the water or go scuba diving.</P>
			<P>Moreover, New Zealand’s largest city, Auckland, should also not be missed. It has two harbors to facilitate the hundreds of boats and yachts that visit the city. Here, you can immerse yourself in water sports or other adventures like bungee jumping, and get a taste of the city life and massive skyscrapers. There are a plethora of things you can do in Auckland; from shopping at the unique designer stores to gambling the night away, or visiting the world-renowned zoos.</P>
			<P>For some privacy and a taste of the yacht life, you can also go to the second largest island in the Gulf of New Zealand, called the Waiheke Island. Other islands that should be on your itinerary include the North and South Islands that include innumerable destinations to visit and things to do.</P>
			<P>Needless to say, there are just too many things to do and explore in the enchanting island country of New Zealand!</P>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>new-zealand</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>New Zealand</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>Ionian Islands</state>
		<country>Greece</country>
		<image>Ionian-Islands</image>	
		<place>Ionian Islands</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<P>The Ionian Islands are the most popular group of islands on the west coast of Greece in the Ionian Sea and they comprise of seven beautiful islands that include: Zakynthos, Ithaca, Corfu, Kefalonia, Lefkada, Paxi (or Paxos), and Kythira.</P>
			<P>Each island has something unique and extraordinary to offer to its yacht charter visitors, for instance, Corfu, the largest Ionian Island is the most tourist-friendly of them all, and the island of Zante offers the best experience of traditional culture.</P>
			<P>There are many things that set the Ionian Islands apart from other yacht charter destinations such as beautiful olive trees, Venetian castles, and churches, pine forests all the way down to the water’s edge and so much more.</P>
			<P>The islands are literally carpeted with olive trees, vineyards, and pines that set a fantastic backdrop and background for the stunning sandy white beaches and sparkling blue waters.</P>
			<P>On a private luxury yacht charter to the Ionian Islands, you will be able to seek out waterfalls, explore the mountain villages and monasteries, scenic views, hiking trails and so much more!</P>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>ionian-islands</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Ionian Islands, Greece</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Sardinia</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Italy</country>
		<image>Sardinia</image>	
		<place>Sardinia</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>This is the second-largest and highly exotic island in the Western Mediterranean. Sardinia is a popular vacation destination among yacht owners and yachting enthusiasts mainly owing to the 1,100 miles of rugged Mediterranean coastline that’s always waiting to be explored.</p>
			<p>This charming Italian island is home to vast untouched gems of nature, idyllic beaches, rich cultures, beautiful coastal towns and so much more.</p>
			<p>The exquisite 55km coastline of Costa Smeralda in northern Sardinia is filled with white sandy beaches, which will be one of the many highlights of your yacht charter trip.</p>
			<p>More than that, Sardinia has a timeless kind of atmosphere that literally feels out of time, making it an ideal place to unwind and relax while you cruise away on your private yacht charter.</p>
			<p>One of Sardinia’s biggest draws is its miles and miles of beaches with shimmering blue seas and massive granite boulders.</p>
			<p>The island is also said to be a hiker’s dream so if you are a true adventurous vacationer, you will find great many trail options such as the wild blue trail and blue miner’s trail.</p>
			<p>A private yacht charter to Sardinia is truly worth it and will stay with you for a long time!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>sardinia</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Sardinia, Italy</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Canary Islands</country>
		<image>Canary-Islands</image>	
		<place>Canary Islands</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>The Canary Islands are one of the most popular and sought-after European vacation destinations, located off the coast of northwestern Africa.</p>
			<p>If you are looking to take to the seas, Canary Islands make an ideal private yacht charter destination with unspoiled nature, scenic views, and pleasant favorable winds. These islands have so much to offer including beautiful beach-hugging resorts, massive landscapes, great volcanoes, sandy coves, and pine forests, to name a few.</p>
			<p>When traveling to and from the Canary Islands on a private yacht charter, you will be able to discover so many hidden wonderful gems on the islands ranging from sheltered marinas, spectacular beaches, and lush greenery.</p>
			<p>One of the many reasons why people travel to the Canary Islands is for peace, relaxation, and unwinding, be it dipping their feet in the blue waters, feeling the sun on their skin, or just taking in the natural beauty of it all.</p>
			<p>The bustling and exciting nightlife of Tenerife and the beaches of Gran Canaria will simply add the cherry to your trip!</p>
			<p>A private luxury yacht charter is indeed one of the best ways to explore the gorgeous Canary Islands, and also take some Instagram-worthy photos for your social media feed!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>canary-islands</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Canary Islands</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>Turquoise Coast</state>
		<country>Turkey</country>
		<image>Turquoise-Coast</image>	
		<place>Turquoise Coast</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>With luminous blue waves and some of the most extraordinary beaches in the world, Turkey’s Turquoise Coast is an absolutely stunning cruising ground for yacht charters.</p>
			<p>Imagine cruising over crystal clear blue seas overlooked by lush green mountains and then finding yourself taking a stroll along a beautiful sandy beach after walking through historic, ancient ruins – sounds heavenly, doesn’t it?</p>
			<p>That’s what the Turquoise Coast has to offer to its visitors, and so much more than that.</p>
			<p>When cruising over this coast in Turkey, two of the must-visit places without question have to be Antalya and Fethiye.</p>
			<p>Fethiye is such a great city that has a long harbor and is full of color, liveliness, cafes, restaurants, and impressive tombs such as the Lycian Rock Tombs that you should definitely visit. Antalya, as most already know, is the hub of stunning beaches and has long earned the reputation of being Turkey’s most sought-after and frequently visited summer resort town.</p>
			<p>A private luxury yacht charter to Turkey’s Turquoise Coast will give you such an amazing opportunity to explore it to the fullest and if u get lucky, you might even stumble across some hidden gems that haven’t been explored before!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>turquoise-coast</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Turquoise Coast, Turkey</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Saint Martin</country>
		<image>Saint-Martin</image>	
		<place>Saint Martin</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Located in the Caribbean Sea and a part of the Leeward Islands, Saint Martin is one of the most popular sailing destinations among people from all over the world. It offers the best of both worlds given how it’s ruled by the Netherlands and France, thereby bringing you a mix of two different cultures at the same time.</p>
			<p>Three of the must-visit islands on Saint Martin are St Barths, Anguilla, and Saba where you can expect to be welcomed by incredible natural beauty, amazing waterfront restaurants, sun-kissed beaches, clear blue waters, and just too many stunning sights to behold.</p>
			<p>The island Saba in particular deserves a visit if you are a water-sports enthusiast because it is often described as a snorkeler’s and a diver’s paradise.</p>
			<p>Did you know that Saint Martin is home to a total of thirty-seven white, powdery sand beaches with turquoise waters that will simply blow you away?</p>
			<p>And what better way to explore the beaches than a private luxury yacht charter to Saint Martin and its surrounding islands!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>saint-martin</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Saint Martin</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Boston</city>
		<state>Massachusetts</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Boston</image>	
		<place>Boston</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>You might have already been to Boston, but if you haven’t discovered it on your own private yacht, you are definitely missing out on a lot.</p>
			<p>From an exciting nightlife to fishing to sightseeing to cultural immersion, you get to experience all of it and more through your yachting experience.</p>
			<p>Begin your private yacht journey by heading north out of Boston Harbor towards Marblehead Harbor, which is best known for its yachting races and regattas. If you are looking for a fun-filled overnight stay, you can spend the night at the Harbor Light Inn that is located in the historic downtown Marblehead.</p>
			<p>When going on a private yacht charter in Boston, you must go cruise along the Charles River which is nothing short of a breathtaking sight that you get to witness from the riverbanks. As you cruise along the river, you will witness spectacular skyline views of Harvard, MIT, Cambridge and so much more. </p>
			<p>You can also go island hopping in Boston where the Boston Harbor is home to 34 beautiful islands that give the visitors, tourists, and locals to escape the city and venture here and there. Cruise towards Long Wharf and head out to Georges Island or Spectacle Island for an amazing time.</p>
			<p>A private luxury yacht charter in Boston is indeed one of the best ways to explore the city and discover some of its hidden gems that you haven’t been able to see before!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>boston</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Boston, Massachusetts, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>France</country>
		<image>France</image>	
		<place>France</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>With changing landscapes brimming with natural bounties, a plethora of historic European sites, towering coastal cliffs, and rivers gushing throughout the country, France is a sight to behold in all its beauty and splendor.</p>
			<p>Among many things, France is best known for the French Rivera, also called Cote d’Azur, which is the place where coastal culture meets the beautiful vibrant blue waters.</p>
			<p>Be it exploring the art and architecture in cities like Nice to feasting on incredible delicacies inspired by Italy such as homemade cheese and wine, a private luxury yacht charter in France will bring you all that and more.</p>
			<p>You can even head towards its perfectly manicured city beaches and socializing or mingle with the locals there. If you just want to relax and take in all its beauty, you can find your own secluded and serene piece of paradise after exploring its gorgeous coastline.</p>
			<p>The French Alps are another example of heaven on earth as they stand tall in all its beauty and majesty. The snow-covered peaks offer a fantastic opportunity for skiing and snowboarding as you go over the heavy yet spectacular blankets of snow.</p>
			<p>A private luxury yacht charter in France brings you an immeasurable experience of a lifetime with its cities flowing with wine and its lush valleys full of rivers. From quaint coastal regions to the rolling hills to warm blue waters, a charter holiday in France is the best way to explore nature’s infinite bounty and wonder.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>france</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>France</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>Maine</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Maine</image>	
		<place>Maine</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<P>Located in the New England region of the United States, Maine is the ultimate place to visit for delicious seafood and stunning stretches of coastline, among many other things.</P>
			<P>This northeastern-most state in the U.S is also known as ‘Pine Tree State’ locally because it is home to an abundance of forest areas and parks. But, more than that, it has breathtaking natural beauty and scenery which is why a private luxury yacht charter is an ideal way to explore this beautiful state.</P>
			<P>The coast of Maine is completely dotted with lighthouses that reveal unbeatable views and scenery from behind.</P>
			<P>With 3500 miles of spectacular coastline, a plethora of islands, and about 6000 ponds and lakes, there are more than enough reasons to go on a yacht charter in Maine.</P>
			<P>Some of the most famous island activities in Maine include deep-sea fishing, sailing, and kayaking. If there’s an adventure-enthusiast residing inside of you, you might want to head off to Casco Bay to brave its cool waters and swim off its amazing private beaches.</P>
			<P>If you are a keen bird watcher, there’s something for you as well – you get to see stunning eagles and ospreys that glide along the island sea level, which is such a great treat in itself.</P>
			<P>Another thing you will find in abundance in Maine is mesmerizing cascading waterfalls that will simply just blow you away because they are that stunning.</P>
			<P>Truth be told, Maine is one of the most fascinating hidden gems of America that continues to attract visitors from all corners of the globe. Whether you are an adventurer, a nature lover, or just someone looking to unwind and relax amid natural beauty, a private yacht charter to Maine is a wonderful option for you!</P>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>maine</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Maine, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>New Caledonia</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>France</country>
		<image>New-Caledonia</image>	
		<place>New Caledonia</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>A French territory comprising of beautiful islands, New Caledonia has become to be one of the most ideal yachting spots in the southwest Pacific Ocean.</p>
			<p>It is blessed with stunning coastlines, lush vegetation, vibrant scenic views, golden savannahs and so much more that make it such a yacht-worthy destination.</p>
			<p>New Caledonia takes great pride in its huge coral reef system as well as the fact that it has the most amount of sheltered water than any other Pacific island. It truly is one of the most magical destinations in the whole world and is meant to be explored on a luxury private yacht charter.</p>
			<p>It is best to begin your cruising journey from Nouméa, the province that is located on the southwest coast of the main island of Grande Terre. It is a buzzing cosmopolitan city featuring a colorful waterfront that is dotted with cafés, bars, restaurants, and nightclubs.</p>
			<p>If you want to get the best and the most incredible views of the islands, visit the Amédée lighthouse. This metal lighthouse was built in the 1860s and is also the world’s tallest lighthouse. It offers spectacular panoramic views of the island given its amazing height.</p>
			<p>New Caledonia is home to many small islands like Lifou Island, Mouli Island, and Tiga Island, just to name a few. These stunning islands guarantee pristine sand beaches, breathtaking blue waters, and color-infused sunsets that will blow you away.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>new-caledonia</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>New Caledonia, France</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Tonga</country>
		<image>Tonga</image>	
		<place>Tonga</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>If you are looking to step back in time in your search for serenity, peace, and comfort, Tonga is your best shot.</p>
			<p>Tonga is a country located in the South Pacific Ocean and it is home to more than 170 beautiful South Pacific islands.</p>
			<p>Vava’u is one of the most popular island groups in the country and it’s also quite sought-after among tourists, sailors, and yacht enthusiasts. It not only presents a nice, compact, and scenic cruising area but also brings you colorful reefs, remote idyllic islands, stunning lagoons, and sun-kissed sandy white beaches that are lined with rustling palm trees.</p>
			<p>When cruising in Tonga, one relaxed day is followed by another even better day so you can explore it at your own pace. The water here is warm and clear, thereby presenting excellent underwater visibility. This is one of the biggest reasons why this country is such a dream come true for snorkeling enthusiasts – the clear waters let you see an abundance of colorful fish and other sea creatures along with spectacular sights of coral.</p>
			<p>Another must-visit group of islands is Ha’apai and it is just gorgeous. This island is ideal for relaxing, unwinding, and just taking in every bit of nature that it has to offer to you.</p>
			<p>Needless to say, a private yacht charter in Tonga will mark as one of the most memorable travel experiences of your life.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>tonga</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Tonga</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Dubai</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>United Arab Emirates</country>
		<image>Dubai</image>	
		<place>Dubai</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Experience the luxurious lifestyle as you cruise through the blue waters surrounded by looming skyscrapers with your private yacht in the wonderful city of Dubai!</p>
			<p>But that’s not all. When you visit Dubai, there are a plethora of things to experience there. From marveling at the manmade island with palm trees dotting the coastline, to visiting the spice and gold souks, and exploring the world’s biggest shopping festival.</p>
			<p>Dubai is quickly becoming a hotspot in the Middle East for luxury yacht charter experiences because of its cool waters, warm beaches, beautiful sunsets, unique culture, and a myriad of activities. While you are there, you can even indulge in the luxury lifestyle by staying in the most top-notch hotels and eating from world-class restaurants.</p>
			<p>As you charter your yacht through the city, you can also stop by and engage in fantastic water adventures from scuba diving, jet-skiing, and more. When you sail through the waters on your private yacht, don’t forget to sunbathe at the Palm Jumeirah, visit the aquarium in the Atlantis, adore the beautiful and intricate grand mosque, and experience the Emirati culture in the desert.</p>
			<p>The best time to visit the city on your yacht is during the winters when there is minimal heat. During the day the weather is perfect for dipping in the water, while at night, it is moderately cool, which will allow you to enjoy a romantic and calm evening.</p>
			<p>Dubai is the perfect vacation destination for people of all ages because it offers them so many spectacular and unforgettable experiences. And there is certainly no better way to indulge in the VIP lifestyle in Dubai than through a yacht charter through the city.</p>
			<p>So, if you are dreaming of your next yacht charter vacation, then Dubai should be at the top of your list!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>dubai</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Dubai, United Arab Emirates</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Maldives</country>
		<image>Maldives</image>	
		<place>Maldives</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>An island that has an abundance of things to see, do and explore, The Maldives is one of the top locations for a yacht charter experience!</p>
			<p>When you charter your yacht through The Maldives, you can witness the world’s most beautiful beaches, blue lagoons, and a plethora of coral reefs. In fact, it is also the best way to explore the thousand coral islands and the 26 ring-shaped atolls the country offers since they have harbors and anchorages at every spot.</p>
			<p>Located in the Southwest of Sri Lanka and India, The Maldives is situated at the heart of the vast Indian Ocean. It is filled with stunning destinations that are not to be missed; some of these include the Ghuli island, the inhabited island of Bodi Kaashi Hura, the Lily Beach, Guraidhoo Island, and the Banana Reef.</p>
			<p>While you are there, you can plan your itinerary and do anything from snorkeling, relaxing at private and secluded spots on various islands and bays, fishing, to even going shopping at the local markets. The natural beauty of The Maldives is breathtaking, which is why it is nothing short of a paradise. To top it off, it offers activities for just about anyone.</p>
			<p>The Maldives is perfect for anyone, whether you are looking for a post-card vacation with family or an endlessly romantic honeymoon with your partner. Get the very best out of this tropical island by booking a luxury private yacht charter and making unforgettable memories.</p>
			<p>Needless to say, if you’re looking for a luxurious and relaxing yacht charter experience, then you must look no further than The Maldives!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>maldives</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Maldives</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Vancouver</city>
		<state>British Columbia</state>
		<country>Canada</country>
		<image>Vancouver</image>	
		<place>Vancouver</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<P>There are a multitude of reasons why your next yacht charter experience should be through Vancouver Island.</P>
			<P>Located on the west of British Columbia, Vancouver is a city and seaport that offers you the ideal mixture between solitude, relaxation, and vibrant city life. The art, music, and food scene in the city is continually thriving, which drives thousands of tourists from all over the world to it. Not to mention the abundance of lush forests and mountains that make the city look like it’s right out of a postcard.</P>
			<P>Vancouver is nothing short of perfect, and the best way to enjoy it is through chartering your yacht through Vancouver Island. This island is situated 80 miles west of the main city and is quite secluded compared to the city. This place is a popular surfing destination for thrill-seekers.</P>
			<P>Individuals who are looking for a more relaxing time can opt to chill at the various lakes where they can even camp. Hiking up the lush forests and mountains is a must when you visit Vancouver Island and want to witness the stunning natural beauty.</P>
			<P>Since the city is surrounded by mountains, there are multiple outdoor adventures you can indulge in. for example, mountain biking, skiing, and camping. But that’s not all; Vancouver has grown into a stylish, diverse, and modern city. This is why you must not miss visiting the boutiques, galleries, museums, theaters, and much more there.</P>
			<P>With so much to see and do in both Vancouver Island and the city, the best way to make the most out of your experience is by chartering your yacht there.</P>
			<P>To witness impressive beauty, immerse yourself in diverse cultures, engage in thrill-seeking activities, and much more, book a private yacht charter through Vancouver!</P>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>vancouver</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Sri Lanka</country>
		<image>Sri-Lanka</image>	
		<place>Sri Lanka</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>If you are looking for an unforgettable experience amidst stunning views and unique culture, then the South Asian island of Sri Lanka is the perfect destination!</p>
			<p>From sandy beaches, lush rainforests, vast mountains, and fun metropolitan cities, Sri Lanka truly offers something for everyone. And the ideal way to make the best out of all of these is through a luxurious and private yacht charter experience. This is why the island is also considered the hub for yachts and superyachts.</p>
			<p>There are a plethora of things you can do while you charter your yacht through Sri Lanka. For example, you can immerse yourself in the wealth of culture by visiting the numerous temples scattered around the island. Moreover, visiting ancient and abandoned historic treasures, such as palaces from thousands of years ago, will be an experience like no other.</p>
			<p>You can also go into the dense jungles and be one with nature by soaking in the many waterfalls, hiking up the mountains, and much more. While you’re there, you must also charter your yacht through the coral reefs to snorkel amongst the beautiful sea animals, or simply enjoy a relaxing time while fishing in the sea.</p>
			<p>Some things that are not to be missed while you visit Sri Lanka are the ancient ruins at Sigiriya and the gorgeous Hikkaduwa beach. You must also visit the several rice fields scattered on the island, as well as the modern city of Colombo.</p>
			<p>The culinary scene at Sri Lanka is not to be missed either, so while you are there, don’t forget to try their special coconut curry, rice pancakes, samosas, and a variety of seafood.</p>
			<p>For an experience like no other, book a yacht charter experience on the diverse terrain of Sri Lanka today!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>sri-lanka</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Sri Lanka</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Iceland</country>
		<image>Iceland</image>	
		<place>Iceland</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Iceland might be the most thinly populated country in Europe, but that doesn’t take away the fact that it’s one of the most beautiful and must-visit destinations in the whole world.</p>
			<p>When it comes to striking landscapes, dramatic scenery, and mesmerizing views of nature, it doesn’t get better than what you will see in Iceland!</p>
			<p>Almost 80% of the country is uninhabited, which means there are areas of vast wilderness here that are home to giant volcanic peaks, gorgeous fjords, lofty glaciers, and sprawling mountain ranges.</p>
			<p>As you cruise along Iceland’s coastline on your private yacht charter, you will get to explore all of that beauty and so much more.</p>
			<p>From picturesque fishing villages on the country’s west coast to discovering historical landmarks, you might actually be surprised at how much Iceland has to offer to you.</p>
			<p>Iceland is best described as a Northern paradise where mountains meet the ice, creating spectacular views of nature that are likely to leave anyone spellbound and blown away. Make sure to visit Reykjavik, which is Iceland’s capital and largest city. It is home to centuries of history, a bustling arts scene, and colorful houses.</p>
			<p>Glittering glaciers, dramatic black rocks, and cascading waterfalls are just a few of the many wonders of nature that you will explore and witness in beautiful Iceland.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>iceland</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Iceland</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Japan</country>
		<image>Japan</image>	
		<place>Japan</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Whether it’s exploring Japan’s rich culture and history, indulging in the very diverse and fascinating Japanese cuisine, or taking a relaxing dip in an Onsen hot spring, a private luxury yacht charter in Japan promises an adventurous journey full of fun, relaxation, and exploration.</p>
			<p>While Japan may not be the first destination to come to mind when you think of a fun cruising vacation with your family or friends, it definitely calls out to yachters and sailors out there.</p>
			<p>A Japan private luxury yacht charter will take you to through the country’s bustling cities that are brimming with a unique cosmopolitan vibe, vibrant energy, natural wonders like national parks and volcanoes, and fascinating historic sites. You will also find yourself feasting your eyes on gorgeous scenery and picturesque views amidst cherry blossom trees that are just too breathtaking.</p>
			<p>Make sure to visit Miyajima Island on your luxury yacht charter to Japan which is a small island in Hiroshima Bay, western Japan. The island is most famous and known for its giant torii gate, which has been ranked as one of Japan’s three best sights and views. The gate seems to be floating on the water during high tide, which is such a breathtaking, picture-worthy sight.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>japan</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Japan</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Lelepa</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Vanuatu</country>
		<image>Lelepa</image>	
		<place>Lelepa</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>The fact that Lelepa is located in Vanuatu is reason enough to plan a private yacht charter destination to this gorgeous island. Vanuatu is known as one of the South Pacific’s most beautiful natural gems with breathtaking untouched waters and stunning landscapes.</p>
			<p>The island is home to more than 160 acres of palm-fringed beaches and tropical rainforests that are simply picture-perfect. You will also find tropical reefs nearby filled with a variety of amazing fish, and it’s so easy to reach as well. Once you go there, you will feel like you are swimming inside an aquarium.</p>
			<p>Lelepa is a largely unexplored and undiscovered ideal yachting destination that you must visit on a private yacht charter. The chances are that you will fall in love with it and might want to go back again!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>lelepa</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Lelepa, Vanuatu</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Rhodes</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Greece</country>
		<image>Rhodes</image>	
		<place>Rhodes</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Greece presents the perfect summertime yachting vacation on a private luxury yacht charter that takes you through its majestic gorgeous islands.</p>
			<p>One of these is Rhodes, which is the largest of the Dodecanese islands of Greece, with a wonderful combination of exciting activities, relaxation spots, and many memorable experiences.</p>
			<p>Like most other Greek Islands, Rhodes is also home to long, stunning stretches of beaches and 300 days of golden sunshine. But, it has so much more to offer that you must explore on your private luxury yacht charter.</p>
			<p>Rhodes Island brings you such a rich and fascinating history that that goes as far back as a thousand years. It also has an abundance of natural beauties such as the Valley of Butterflies, the Marine Aquarium, Seven Springs, Mountain Akramitis, and so many others.</p>
			<p>You will also love the exciting and buzzing nightlife on the island, where nightclubs and bars offer hours-long entertainment for every person out there.</p>
			<p>A yachting journey to the gorgeous Rhodes island will not only help you uncover the hidden gems of the Greek Islands but also feast your eyes on spectacular views that will probably stay with you forever.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>rhodes</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Rhodes, Greece</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>Panama Canal</state>
		<country>Panama</country>
		<image>Panama-Canal</image>	
		<place>Panama Canal</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>With calm blue waters and excellent views of lush terrain, Panama Canal is another exquisite destination that you must explore on a private luxury yacht charter.</p>
			<p>This lock-type canal cuts across the Isthmus of Panama and connects the Atlantic Ocean with the Pacific Ocean.</p>
			<p>Panama Canal is known as one of the most stunning and fascinating human-made wonders that brings an opportunity for adventures by the shore as well as on land. From kayaking in Nicoya Bay at Puntarenas, Costa Rica, to getting in touch with the indigenous culture at the Museum of Oaxaca Art in Huatulco, Mexico, there’s so much to do and see here.</p>
			<p>From your yacht, you will get such clear and amazing views of Soberania National Park, which is a 55,000-acre area of protected rainforest. It is home to a number of beautiful species mammals, birds, and reptiles. If you get lucky, you might be able to catch a glimpse of a white-faced capuchin monkey or even an orange-chinned parakeet!</p>
			<p>While sailing away on your yacht, make sure to visit the islands surrounding Lake Gatun. It’s such a wonderful body of water featuring lush forests and colorful birds.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>panama-canal</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Panama Canal, Panama</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Newport</city>
		<state>Rhode Island</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Newport</image>	
		<place>Newport</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Looking for a low-key but luxurious destination for your next yacht charter experience? Perhaps Rhode Island might appeal to you.</p>
			<p>A State in New England, Rhode Island is known for its stunning white sandy beaches, quaint little towns, and coastal cities. The best way to explore this state is through a luxury yacht charter experience starting from Newport.</p>
			<p>Newport is a massively popular yacht destination, and you’ll find the harbor filled with yachts all year round. It is also where many sailing regattas take place as well.</p>
			<p>On a yacht charter vacation in Rhode Island, you should definitely stick to the coastal city of Newport. There is something for everyone there, from strolling along the Cliff Walk to exploring the many lively pubs dotting the city. That’s not all; if you are yacht enthusiasts, then you must also visit the Herreshoff Museum, where you will enjoy the history of classic sailing and yachts.</p>
			<p>While you’re there, you will probably never get bored since there is some form of entertainment all the time such as cultural events, live music performances, jazz and folk festivals, sailing events, and so much more. The coastal city is constantly buzzing with people, making it a lively place all year round.</p>
			<p>From the food to the people and the overall ambiance of Newport, it’s safe to say the State of Rhode Island will be the perfect retreat for your yacht charter experience with your friends, family, or partner!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>newport</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Newport, Rhode Island, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Whitsunday Islands</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Australia</country>
		<image>Whitsunday-Islands</image>	
		<place>Whitsunday Islands</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<P>If you seek the gateway to paradise, then look no further than the stunning Whitsunday Islands of Australia!</P>
			<P>Tucked away in the heart of the blue waters of the Great Barrier Reef, these islands lie on the Northeast coast of Queensland. Though most of these islands are uninhabited, the eight main islands offer plenty of resorts and sandbars.</P>
			<P>And nearly all of them contain a plethora of rainforests, hiking trails, white sandy beaches, and breathtaking views all over. So, there will definitely be something for anyone on this yacht charter experience.</P>
			<P>Water sports, such as diving excursions, snorkeling, and rafting, are the most popular activities to do on a yacht charter to these islands. At Blue Pearl Bay, you must experience snorkeling and whale watching. Additionally, you should also dock your yacht at Bauer Bay, where you should travel to the stop for stunning 360 degrees views of all the islands.</P>
			<P>The natural charm of the biggest island there, called the Whitsunday Islands, is endless, and the range of activities is never-ending. Here, Whitehaven Beach, which happens to be one of the best beaches in the world, is not to be missed either, as the blue waters and pristine white sands will leave you in awe.</P>
			<P>As you hike through the rainforests on these islands, expect to come across a multitude of wildlife. Enjoy the nature and panoramic views of flora and fauna before rejoining civilization at the many resorts on the islands.</P>
			<P>The best way to explore the stunning Whitsunday islands is through a yacht charter experience because it will be unlike any other. For breathtaking views and nature at its best, this destination should definitely be on your list!</P>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>whitsunday-islands</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Whitsunday Islands, Australia</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>Chesapeake Bay</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Chesapeake-Bay</image>	
		<place>Chesapeake Bay</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>If tranquility is what you’re seeking on your next yacht charter experience, then look no further than the peaceful Chesapeake Bay!</p>
			<p>Stretching over 6 states: Maryland, New York, Pennsylvania, Delaware, Virginia and West Virginia, plus the District of Columbia, it is home to many famous writers and sailors who gush about this Bay endlessly. Besides the tranquility and stunning views, Chesapeake Bay also offers an intriguing history dating back to colonial and civil war times.</p>
			<p>The Bay is dotted with several islands, villages, and towns that beg to be explored. Stopping at each of them may not be entirely possible in one trip, but you must explore at least some of them. Some of these places include the quaint waterfront fishing town of Rock Hall, where hiking, fishing, bird watching, and visiting the farmers market are a must.</p>
			<p>A must-visit is the Baltimore Inner Harbor, where you can dock your yacht and step off to the pier, where you can find live music performances and festivals if you are lucky. Most of the people who visit Chesapeake Bay also pay a visit to the Chester River and Whitehall bay.</p>
			<p>One of the most popular yachting centers where people on yacht charters stop by is at St. Michaels. Here, you can learn more about the history and visit the historic buildings on Mulberry street to get a taste of pre-civil war life.</p>
			<p>Overall, Chesapeake Bay is the ideal yacht vacation spot for people who want to explore non-traditional yacht charter spots. Nevertheless, it will still be an unforgettable and ever so relaxing experience that will immerse you in nature, history, and tranquility!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>chesapeake-bay</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Chesapeake Bay, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Scotland</country>
		<image>Scotland</image>	
		<place>Scotland</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>A unique destination for a yacht charter experience, Scotland will definitely make for a quaint and unforgettable time.</p>
			<p>The country is famous for its beautiful scenery, tranquil sailing spots, unique history, delicious food, and good-humored people, so what more could you ask for?</p>
			<p>Western Scotland boasts a dramatic coastline that begs to be explored by yacht charters. Here, you can sail off to uninhabited places or explore unforgettable destinations. Some of these include Viking battlefields, ruined castles, local pubs, whiskey distilleries, and fishing villages. Hence, there will be something for everyone here. If you are an avid history geek, then this destination will appeal to you even more.</p>
			<p>But that’s not all; the coastal areas of Scotland are brimming with stunning natural spots like bays and islands, as well as a plethora of wildlife. If you’re lucky, you can witness dolphins, seals, porpoises, and plenty of wild birds.</p>
			<p>In the coastal areas of Western Scotland, you can also find many diving spots where you can find a host of gorgeous marine life. The white sandy beaches are incomparable to any other. Lastly, depending on the area and sailing conditions, you may also find yourself watching sharks swimming in the sea.</p>
			<p>Scotland is definitely a treat for the eyes. From castles and historic buildings to the wildlife and natural vistas, it is truly a destination unlike any other. Moreover, compared to the rest in the UK, this country happens to be the top destination with the best seafood, so don’t forget to indulge in the local seafood cuisine while you are there.</p>
			<p>Needless to say, if you want a yacht charter vacation that is filled with adventure, history, and tranquility, then Scotland is the best place to go!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>scotland</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Scotland</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Bermuda</country>
		<image>Bermuda</image>	
		<place>Bermuda</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>A little oasis of paradise, Bermuda should definitely be at the top of places to visit on your next luxury yacht charter.</p>
			<p>Bermuda is often mistaken as being part of the Caribbean when it’s not. In fact, it is hundreds of miles away from there. Bermuda is a British island territory that is not that far from the East coast of America. You can easily reach this stunning destination via a two-hour flight from there.</p>
			<p>With gorgeous azure waters, secluded limestone coves, coral pink sandy beaches, Bermuda will surely be a feast for the eyes and soul. It is free of modern technology, high-rise buildings, and neon signs. Instead, it has stunning natural scenery and spots that make it a true haven of tranquility.</p>
			<p>Bermuda comprises 181 islands and islets, most of which are uninhabited but still worth exploring. The sparkling waters of the island-nation are the perfect place to dive into and witness the breathtaking marine life. Here, there is also a plethora of water sports and related activities.</p>
			<p>The pastel-colored houses and quaint towns are reminiscent of the colonial times and make for the perfect exploration by foot. While you’re there, you must immerse yourself in the unique culture of Bermuda that is the perfect fusion of British and African heritage. You can do this by indulging in the delicious local cuisine, musical events, and blending with the locals.</p>
			<p>The beautiful harbor city of Hamilton should also be on your itinerary when you visit Bermuda, where opportunities for shopping, museums, and galleries are aplenty. Other highlights also include the Royal Naval Dockyard and the Crystal Caves.</p>
			<p>Needless to say, this yacht charter experience to Bermuda will be a once-in-a-lifetime one that is perfect for a family retreat, couples vacation, or an enjoyable time with friends!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>bermuda</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Bermuda</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Boracay</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Philippines</country>
		<image>Boracay</image>	
		<place>Boracay</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>This resort island located in the Western Visayas region of the Philippines is another unexplored yacht destination that is home to some of the best hotels and spectacular beaches in the Philippines.</p>
			<p>More than that, you will also experience exciting nightlife scenes, an excellent variety of dining options, and some of the most stimulating watersports!</p>
			<p>Among many other reasons, Boracay’s pristine, picture-perfect beaches are what make this island visit-worthy. Some of its most popular beaches include the world-famous White Beach, Diniwid Beach, and Bulabog Beach, to name a few.</p>
			<p>If you are a windsurfing enthusiast, you will absolutely love Boracay because it has the most ideal weather conditions for windsurfing; reliable winds and warm and clear waters.</p>
			<p>While cruising on this gorgeous island, you will witness some of the most mesmerizing sunsets, especially on the White Beach. It’s simply a magical view where you definitely need to keep your camera ready to be able to capture the most stunning sunset ever!</p>
			<p>A private yacht charter in Boracay is an absolutely must-have experience and will also last a long, long time with you!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>boracay</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Boracay, Philippines</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>Italian Coast</state>
		<country>Italy</country>
		<image>Italian-Coast</image>	
		<place>Italian Coast</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>There aren’t enough reasons to love the Italian coast. From picture-perfect beaches to stunning cliffs to gorgeous hills, the coast has so much beauty and splendor to offer.</p>
			<p>A private yacht charter to the Italian coast is ideal for all travel enthusiasts who love to indulge in exciting water activities such as jet-skiing, snorkeling, and swimming. While you are at it, make sure to explore the undiscovered pristine beaches, after which you can binge on delicious seafood and splurge on shopping.</p>
			<p>When cruising along the Italian coast, a must-visit spot is Portofino, a beautiful fishing village located on the Italian Riviera coastline. It is best known for offering ‘relaxed luxury’ owing to its stellar restaurants and upscale boutiques.</p>
			<p>Sorrento is another popular seaside town that offers somewhat dramatic and spectacular views over the Bay. If you happen to visit it during the springtime, you’ll be able to experience an amazing opportunity of seeing the town painted radiant colors of orange blossoms and jasmine.</p>
			<p>A private luxury yacht charter along the Italian coast will truly leave you bedazzled and will be a trip of a lifetime!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>italian-coast</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Italian Coast, Italy</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Cooper Island</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>British Virgin Islands</country>
		<image>Cooper-Island</image>	
		<place>Cooper Island</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Previously known as Bergen Island, Cooper Island is a stunning, small island of the British Virgin Islands in the Caribbean. It’s the perfect spot for yacht charters to stop over and explore its ultimate beauty and scenic views.</p>
			<p>While you are on your luxury charter yacht vacation, you must stop at Cooper Island Beach Club for either lunch or an overnight stay.</p>
			<p>You also get to explore 12 acres of pristine and breathtaking nature reserve here on Cooper Island, where you will be able to spot giant land crabs, majestic seabirds, and ancient Bermuda cedar trees. The island is perfect for a picnic or a day trip, owing to its shallow-water beaches nature trails.</p>
			<p>Once you are done with that, climb the wildlife observation tower, which will give you a chance to see a spectacular sweeping panorama of the island.</p>
			<p>Towards the southwestern side of Cooper Island, you will come across a site that was mainly created for divers with breathtaking underwater scenery. It is also close to a reef wall that features some of the most vibrant colored corals.</p>
			<p>If you’ve never been to Cooper Island, you might want to plan a yacht charter vacation here the next time you think about going on a trip!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>cooper-island</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Cooper Island, British Virgin Islands</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>The Cook Islands</country>
		<image>The-Cook-Islands</image>	
		<place>The Cook Islands</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>With diverse marine life, crystal-clear waters, and a great connection to Polynesian culture, The Cook Islands have long attracted travelers and tourists from all over the world.</p>
			<p>Located in the South Pacific Ocean between French Polynesia and American Samoa, north-east of New Zealand, the Cook Islands are like that cherry on the top that makes everything better. This stunning destination is made of 15 idyllic islands that are best explored by a private luxury yacht charter.</p>
			<p>There are many reasons to visit the Cook Islands, one of which is its luxe lagoons. These lagoons are home to such deep blue waters that make it really hard for one to be able to distinguish between them and the blue skies! This is further enhanced by the islands’ pure white sand featuring a beach hammock to two.</p>
			<p>A must-visit spot on the Cook Islands is Aitutaki which is its second-largest island. It is home to rainforest-laced shores where you can drive around to your heart’s content.</p>
			<p>A yacht charter on the Cooks Islands might not be on the top of your travel list, but once you do go there, then you will be able to truly explore its beauty and splendor.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>the-cook-islands</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>The Cook Islands</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Bora Bora</country>
		<image>Leeward-Islands</image>	
		<place>Bora Bora</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Often described as an ‘unspoiled paradise,’ Bora Bora is one of the most magical destinations in the world that you must explore on a luxury yacht charter. It’s a small South Pacific island located in French Polynesia northwest of Tahiti.</p>
			<p>The unique geography of this island is among a few hundred reasons why it warrants a visit from every person at least once in their lifetime.</p>
			<p>Bora Bora is known for its volcanic past, the evidence of which is found in Mt Otemanu, a dramatic peak surrounded by a series of little islands and a large turquoise lagoon.</p>
			<p>The crystal-clear waters and pristine beaches further add to the beauty of Bora Bora, given the fact that it is void of any sky-rise hotels and large crowds.</p>
			<p>Among all these things, the one feature of this island that makes it a must-visit yacht destination is that its lagoon actually has more than fifty shades of blue! If you circle the lagoon on your yacht, you will be able to see some of the most breathtaking shades of turquoise and blue that you’ve probably never seen before!</p>
			<p>If you want to have a truly magical yachting experience, Bora Bora should definitely top your list!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>bora-bora</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Bora Bora</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Ireland</country>
		<image>Ireland</image>	
		<place>Ireland</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
		    <p>Ireland is not exactly thought of as a pristine destination for a yacht charter experience, but that is far from the truth.</p>
		  	<p>To experience the true spirit of Ireland, you must explore her seas. Though some of the sea passages may be slightly challenging, the breathtaking views of the mountains, the cool air, and the warm blue water certainly make up for it. If you are looking for an unforgettable experience in the sea, you must consider Ireland as your top destination.</p>
			<p>There’s a reason why this beautiful island country is called the Emerald Isle. Thanks to its luscious green landscapes, rolling hills, and a plethora of medieval castles, you will definitely be tempted to dock your yacht and explore all its offerings offshore.</p>
			<p>Begin your luxury private yacht charter from Cork in the South of Ireland, where you can witness the awe-inspiring castles dating back to medieval centuries. This is the most famous coastline in Ireland as it has multiple stops and numerous things to see and do. After that, you can travel all the way to the southwest and dock your yacht at the Kinsale harbor. Here, you will find yourself in castle haven.</p>
			<p>The Irish weather can be challenging at times, so we recommend you visit during the warmer months with more light.</p>
			<p>There is so much to do in Ireland, but perhaps the best one is to visit the wine distilleries. You can also go to the local pubs and sample some world-famous Guinness, have a laugh with the friendly locals, and enjoy a song or two. Your trip to Island will surely be incomplete without a visit to the pub.</p>
			<p>All in all, chartering your private yacht through Ireland will leave you with an unforgettable experience and memories to last a lifetime!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>ireland</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Ireland</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Ross Sea</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Antarctica</country>
		<image>Ross-Sea</image>	
		<place>Ross Sea</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Sailing on a yacht through Antarctica is undoubtedly a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity. When you visit the white continent, you get the chance to witness a myriad of things that will leave you in awe. Some of these include sharks, whales, penguins, and much more. The snow-capped mountains will be a treat for the eyes, and visiting pristine locations seldom seen by humans will give you a peek into the history of the world.</p>
			<p>The most spectacular destination for your Antarctic yacht charter is the Ross Sea. It is located on the opposite side of the southernmost end of the continent. The deep bay was the starting point of heroic expeditions by man dating back to centuries when they wanted to visit the South Pole. You can start your yacht charter from South America, preferably the Chilean coast, and then travel north.</p>
			<p>A yacht charter through the Ross Sea will take you to stunning mountains, fjords, and sites that will leave you mesmerized. Here, you can experience the epitome of relaxation as you disconnect from the world and watch the clear and still waters reflect the sun. You can choose to stay within the warmth of your yacht or spend a few nights on the huts built at the foot of the mountains.</p>
			<p>While you are there, you must also visit Deception Island. It is an abandoned whaling station and WWII base that gives an eerie and chilling beauty. Here, the water is much warmer, so you can even decide to take the ‘Polar Plunge’ if you’re brave enough to do so.</p>
			<p>Needless to say, a trip to the Ross Sea on your yacht charter will be an iconic experience that will leave you with innumerable memories!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>ross-sea</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Ross Sea, Antarctica</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Madagascar</country>
		<image>Madagascar</image>	
		<place>Madagascar</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Home to a bounty of fantastical creatures, Madagascar is a naturally and culturally rich destination perfect for yacht charters.</p>
			<p>Located in the Indian Ocean, off the coast of Mozambique, Madagascar is a stunning destination with a plethora of flora and fauna, unique wildlife, and hidden gems. If you are searching for private beaches, hidden treasures, world-class diving spots, and incredible adventures, you’ll find them all in this Island country.</p>
			<p>Since the island was isolated for over 70 million years, it hosts a multitude of unique creatures and absolutely stunning nature reserves. On your yacht charter trip, you can expect to have encounters with wildlife. In fact, you might even get a chance to see the world-famous inhabitant of this island, called the lemur. Aside from that, you can get a glimpse of colorful chameleons, cat-like fossa, insects, turtles, and a range of reptiles.</p>
			<p>Madagascar offers everything from fantastic beaches to forests, mountains, and waterfalls. This place is perfect for history buffs, beach bums, and adventure seekers. There’s really something for everyone in Madagascar.</p>
			<p>A range of activities awaits you as you charter your yacht through Madagascar. From diving, mountain hiking, kite-surfing, to rock climbing, and much more. The island is a melting pot for culture and history, which you can uncover as you explore the land and meet with the locals.</p>
			<p>Moreover, don’t forget to unwind at the pristine beaches and experience unparalleled diving at the Mitsio Island in Madagascar. Here, you can even snorkel in the coral-rich marine reserves. Similarly, you can also go wreck diving or spot a humpback whale at Ile-Saint Marie.</p>
			<p>With a plethora of activities in your itinerary and much to see, yacht charters through Madagascar will immerse you in an experience like no other!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>madagascar</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Madagascar</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Borneo</city>
		<state>Kota Kinabalu</state>
		<country>Malaysia</country>
		<image>Borneo</image>	
		<place>Borneo</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Are you looking for an unmatched adventure through lush rainforests and crystal clear waters? Do you want to see nature reserves and wildlife unlike any other? Then look no further than Borneo!</p>
			<p>An island shared by Malaysia, Brunei, and Indonesia, Borneo, was not open to public tourism due to safety concerns up until recently. Now, it seems like a popular destination as we see people all over the world heading to the island via private yachts. This is because it is home to incredible rainforests, one-of-a-kind wildlife, and ancient spots dating back centuries.</p>
			<p>Since it was predominantly isolated by humans, it is rich with a multitude of various wildlife. Some of the most famous include orangutans, hammerhead sharks, pigmy elephants, proboscis monkeys, and clouded leopards. Consider taking a boat safari through the waters to get a peek at this wildlife.</p>
			<p>Moreover, offshore, you can also visit Mount Kinabalu, where you can hike up to the island’s highest peak and get 360 degrees mesmerizing views of the land. But if you want to experience jungles and forests that are completely pristine and give you the perfect dose of nature, then head over to Danum Valley.</p>
			<p>While you’re there, you can dive and snorkel and explore the stunning underwater treasures the island offers. The Baracuda Point is packed with turtles. Or, you can go to Layang-Layang for a chance to spot the infamous and unique hammerhead sharks.</p>
			<p>So, if nature and wildlife are what you crave, then you must charter your private yacht through Borneo ASAP!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>borneo</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Borneo, Kota Kinabalu, Malaysia</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Seattle</city>
		<state>Washington</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Seattle</image>	
		<place>Seattle</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Seattle is not exactly thought of as a sailing destination, but nevertheless, it certainly should be. If you’re looking for a low-key adventure and want to witness nature at its finest, then you must consider a private yacht charter through Seattle!</p>
			<p>The Washington state itself is described as having pristine waterways, beautiful oceans, and untouched natural landscapes. And Seattle is known for its fantastic skyline, secluded beaches, and lush forests, so why would you not consider it for a yacht charter experience?</p>
			<p>Not only that, but when you charter your yacht here, you begin your journey from Seattle and travel all the way to the San Juan Archipelago, where you will have plenty of secluded islands to explore and unwind at. The scenic views here are unbeatable; as you sail through the deep ocean blue waters and relax at the beaches, you can marvel at the gorgeous snow-capped mountains in the backdrop. The beauty of the Pacific Northwest will definitely blow you away!</p>
			<p>You can begin your yacht charter experience from Seattle, where you can get a taste of the modern city life, then sail through the waters and take stops along the way to explore San Juan, Lake Washington, Puget Sound, and more. If you are feeling adventurous, you can even travel upwards to explore the Gulf Islands, the Sunshine Coast, and the Desolation Sound, all of which are located in Canada.</p>
			<p>You can do tons of things on a yacht charter experience in Seattle, from exploring untouched islands and forests to sailing along the coastline or the deep waters. You might even get a chance to witness up close the unique marine life the city’s waters offer, such as whales, porpoises, sea birds, and otters.</p>
			<p>Needless to say, a yacht charter through Seattle will be an unforgettable getaway, whether you’re with friends or family!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>seattle</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Seattle, Washington, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Catalina Island</city>
		<state>California</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Catalina-Island</image>	
		<place>Catalina Island</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>If you are in search of a fantastic vacation with the whole family, Catalina Island should be at the top of your list.</p>
			<p>Just 20 miles off the coast of Los Angeles, this beautiful island is a haven for boat life as it offers natural harbors, stunning views, and unique wildlife. On this island, you can find tons of exciting activities and adventures for all ages.</p>
			<p>Some of these activities include zip-lining, hiking, diving, parasailing, kayaking, and paddleboarding. You can also take things easy and enjoy a relaxing day at the island, unwinding at the pristine beaches, soaking in the island life, and going shopping. Indeed, both the laid-back individuals and the adventurers will be pleased on a yacht charter through this gorgeous enclave.</p>
			<p>Sometimes, what you need is a vacation that whisks you away from the everyday monotonous life and takes you away for an experience that provides an eclectic mix of adventure and relaxation. A yacht charter experience in Catalina Island helps you do just that. You can enjoy a relaxing sail to the island, where you can dock your yacht, hop off, and immerse yourself in the island.</p>
			<p>Not to mention, when you sail through the waters, you might even get the chance to witness whales and leopard sharks swimming. Onshore, when you hike in the forests, you might come across bald eagles and grey foxes. All in all, since the wildlife has been preserved on this island, you can see its finest here.</p>
			<p>Besides viewing the wildlife and engaging in water sports, you can hike up on the jagged mountains to get a view of the island and watch the fantastic sunrise. You can also visit some of the island’s many attractions, including its botanical garden.</p>
			<p>All in all, a Catalina Island yacht charter experience could be all you need to break away from daily life and have an amazing time with your family!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>catalina-island</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Catalina Island, California, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Maui</city>
		<state>Hawaii</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Maui</image>	
		<place>Maui</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>The name Maui comes from the legend of Hawaiiloa, the navigator credited with discovery of the Hawaiian Islands. He named the island after his son, who was named for the demigod Maui. </p>
			<p>There are endless reasons why Maui is the perfect tourist destination for practically anyone. Still, we’re here to talk about why you need to book a yacht charter experience through this gorgeous island ASAP!</p>
			<p>Hawaii itself holds various gorgeous islands that beg to be explored, whether via sailing or on foot. And there are tons of things you can see and do there. Since it is located right in the middle of the Pacific, you get the chance even to spot a whale or two.</p>
			<p>Maui, in particular, is an excellent destination because of its majestic forests and hiking spots, as well as huge waves for surfing. But that’s not all, the pristine beaches, tumbling waterfalls, and quaint towns will be everything you need and more to have an unforgettable time, whether with family or friends.</p>
			<p>Some of the things you can do on the second largest Hawaiian island include snorkeling in the clear waters with the ocean life, try your hand at surfing at Ho’okipa beach, or simply go ocean kayaking. For all the adrenalin junkies, you can consider a skydiving experience in Maui. The food in Maui is incomparable to anywhere else. Don’t forget to try all the local dishes while you’re there, including Poi, Poke, Chicken Long rice, and much more.</p>
			<p>You can also traverse through the calm waters from Maui towards Lanai and Molokai, areas which are popular due to an abundance of whale watching opportunities. Molokai is also known for its friendly locals and laid-back nature, where you can simply unwind and relax.</p>
			<p>Needless to say, visiting this island through a yacht charter will be no less of a paradise!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>maui</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Maui, Hawaii, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Bar Harbor</city>
		<state>Maine</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Bar-Harbor</image>	
		<place>Bar Harbor</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>A haven for all nature lovers, Bar Harbor, is the best destination for a fantastic yacht charter experience!</p>
			<p>The seaside town on Mount Desert Island in Maine is filled with nature reserves and beautiful landmarks, including glaciers carved lakes, valleys, and snow-capped mountain peaks. This place offers a stunning landscape and views that will leave your mouth agape. Since it serves as a gateway to the famous Acadia National Park, it gives you access to gorgeous cliffs and mountains.</p>
			<p>If you are an outdoor lover, you will have a blast at Bar Harbor. When you visit in the summers, you get the chance to bike and hike across the tall mountains. After you climb up the hills, expect to see breathtaking views of the Atlantic Ocean and the Porcupine Islands. Or, if that is too much of an effort, then you can simply take a horse carriage and explore the cobbled stone streets reminiscent of the old town. That, too, will be an enchanting experience.</p>
			<p>When you visit Bar Harbor, don’t leave without trying their world-famous lobsters. Their sea is riddled with them, and the town is known for the delicious delicacies based around them. If you are feeling adventurous, you must also try their lobster ice cream.</p>
			<p>This town, located along Maine’s Frenchman Bay, also gives you access to fantastic beaches. You can even book a tour of the ocean to spot a few whales. All in all, Bar Harbor is the perfect destination for a chilled-out and low-key yacht vacation with your family.</p>
			<p>Needless to say, Bar Harbor gives you an unforgettable experience. While it offers something for everyone, it is absolutely the perfect place for nature lovers, adventurers, and of course, lobster fanatics!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>bar-harbor</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Bar Harbor, Maine, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>St. Barts</country>
		<image>St.-Barts</image>	
		<place>St. Barts</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>One of the most popular yacht charter destinations is undoubtedly St. Barts. The Caribbean Island is a stunning destination that will leave all visitors wanting more.</p>
			<p>St. Barts, or St. Barthelemy, is a place where all the famous celebrities, movie stars, and designers come to unwind and relax. So, why not enjoy a bit of luxury with them?</p>
			<p>There is undoubtedly something for everyone there, from pristine beaches, fishing villages, and high-end restaurants to stunning historical landmarks, beautiful hills, and marine parks. The French-speaking island will offer you a unique cuisine that is undeniably delicious and a glamorous yet relaxing atmosphere unlike any other.</p>
			<p>Everything about this Caribbean Island oozes beauty and style. The sea is riddled with yachts all year round, which serves as a testament to the fact that it is the perfect destination for yacht charters. Moreover, you also get access to one of the best diving spots in the world here. Scuba diving is a popular activity here that gives you a chance to swim in the crystal clear blue waters with a plethora of marine life.</p>
			<p>We think that the best time to visit St. Barts is during the New Year when you can also witness a fireworks display that lights up the sky unlike you have ever seen before. While you are there, you might even get access to the hottest yacht parties. From natural reserves, a taste of history, some French culture and cuisine, and stylish destinations, what more could you want from your next vacation?</p>
			<p>If glitz and glam and a simultaneous relaxing time are what you are searching for in your next yacht charter vacation, then look no further than St. Barts. It will undoubtedly give you precisely that and more when you book a yacht today!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>st.-barts</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>St. Barts</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Copenhagen</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Denmark</country>
		<image>Copenhagen</image>	
		<place>Copenhagen</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Considering a contemporary vacation that offers an eclectic mix of modern architecture and renaissance times entertainment? Then there is no better place than Copenhagen!</p>
			<p>The Danish capital has recently witnessed a surge in tourists as more and more people are discovering the beautiful hidden treasures, myriad entertainment options, modern cuisine, and so much more. And we believe that the best way to make the most of all of this is through a yacht charter experience through the city.</p>
			<p>The entire city is completely eco-friendly and boasts clean energy. It is modern, stunning, and absolutely tourist-friendly. You can dock your yacht at the harbor, where you can even take a dip in the water since it is swimmable. Then you can rent yourself a bike and explore the streets of this city. Whichever bar or restaurant in Copenhagen you go to, you are guaranteed to have a fantastic experience since most of them have Michelin stars.</p>
			<p>You can moor your superyacht near the Royal Playhouse at the heart of the city. From there, you can explore all the operas and concert halls that have been recently built but are reminiscent of the renaissance times. For a touch of history, don’t forget to explore attractions like the 19th-century amusement park Tivoli Gardens and the 17th century Rosenborg Castles, where you can witness the stunning crown jewels.</p>
			<p>From world-renowned restaurants, fun theme parks, and ancient castles and landmarks, Copenhagen will offer one thing or the other to tourists. Whatever you choose to do, we’re sure that you will have a wonderful time.</p>
			<p>Book a yacht today and explore the Danish capital with your loved ones for an experience like no other!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>copenhagen</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Copenhagen, Denmark</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Qatar</country>
		<image>Qatar</image>	
		<place>Qatar</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>A country that is slowly rising in popularity amongst tourists is undoubtedly Qatar, and the reason why is clear as day.</p>
			<p>With a vast coastline, modern and luxurious feel, and the ideal blend of Arabian history and culture that spills into its food and lifestyle, there’s no doubt that Qatar is one of the best destinations for a vacation, and especially for a yacht charter experience. The coastline is riddled with idyllic beaches that are perfect for unwinding and lounging.</p>
			<p>The capital city of the country, Doha, is the perfect mix between culture and modernity. Here you can experience the quintessential Arabic culture while living in style by exploring world-renowned shopping malls and fine dining in their world-class restaurants. Sail in the steady and serene waters of the country onboard your luxurious yacht and soak in the sunshine that happens to be all year round.</p>
			<p>In Qatar, there is a wide range of things to do. From visiting art galleries, marveling at the architecture, shopping, to so much more. If you want to learn more about Islamic history and Arabic culture, visit the famous Islamic Museum. Moreover, to immerse yourself in Qatari culture and taste authentic Arabic cuisine, then you must go to Katara, where you can even buy a wide range of souvenirs to take back. Besides that, kayaking, surfing, and sailing are all popular activities in the country.</p>
			<p>A visit to Qatar is surely incomplete if you don’t take a day trip to the desert. This experience will definitely be unlike any other, as you traverse through sandy roads and meet with the locals.</p>
			<p>So, book a yacht charter to Qatar today for a unique mix of culture, adventure, relaxation, and incredible food!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>qatar</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Qatar</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Mauritius</country>
		<image>Mauritius</image>	
		<place>Mauritius</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<P>Discover the absolutely breathtaking island nation of Mauritius by cruising along its blue waters on a luxury yacht!</P>
			<P>Here you can experience absolute thrill and adventure by immersing yourself in nature, wildlife, and unique natural sites Mauritius has to offer. And the best part is that it is still a rising tourist destination, so it’s never too crowded either.</P>
			<P>Mauritius is slowly rising in popularity due to its recent influx of tourists and growing population. The history and culture of the island nation are unparalleled and can best be experienced through the unique cuisine and dishes it offers. The exotic dining experience is a must when you go to this island nation.</P>
			<P>When you charter your yacht through Mauritius, you get to explore all the islands there, including St. Brandon, Rodrigues, and Agalega Islands. You will also find the world’s largest coral reefs in Mauritius’ coastline, which is home to a wide variety of sea life, including sharks, sea turtles, whales, and more. Besides that, you also have an array of entertainment options here, especially if you visit the more populated islands.</P>
			<P>You can enjoy some other popular activities through a yacht charter experience in Mauritius, including helicopter tours, skydiving, sailing, and kayaking. If you have kids, you should also visit their botanical gardens and plantation areas. To learn more about the history of the island nation, don’t forget to visit their museums.</P>
			<P>Mauritius has plenty to offer to any kind of traveler, whether you are seeking a honeymoon or family vacation, a laidback time, or an unforgettable adventure. And the best way to make the most of your trip there is to book a luxury chart charter experience!</P>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>mauritius</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Mauritius</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Mumbai</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>India</country>
		<image>Mumbai</image>	
		<place>Mumbai</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Looking for a low-key luxurious yacht charter experience with friends and family? Then the perfect destination would be Mumbai!</p>
			<P>Discover the old city of Bombay as you charter your yacht through its peaceful waters. Here, you can find yourself lost in its fantastic and massive range of history and culture. The city is brimming with a unique culture influenced by centuries-old religion and traditions unlike any you have seen before. Not to mention, there is also so much to do when you charter your yacht through Mumbai.</P>
			<P>Whether you are seeking a romantic getaway, a family vacation, or a fun time with friends, Mumbai will definitely offer you an unforgettable experience and give you memories that you will treasure for years to come.</P>
			<P>Revel in the beauty and tranquility of the Arabian Sea on your luxurious yacht as you cruise along its coastline. The sea undoubtedly offers something captivating and peaceful that constantly draws you towards it. Whether you choose to spend a few hours or an entire day in the ocean, expect to be mesmerized by its beauty.</P>
			<P>Don’t forget to dock your yacht explore the hustle and bustle of the country’s vivid city. This is where infamous Bollywood came alive, so expect to watch movies, dances, and live song performances everywhere you go. Of course, this city is also where the beautiful Taj Mahal lies, which is also one of the Seven Wonders of the World. It is definitely a must-see for every tourist.</P>
			<P>The Indian cuisine is known worldwide for its unique taste and blends of spices. In Mumbai, you can try the quintessential Indian food and dishes that will undoubtedly leave your taste buds wanting more.</P>
			<P>Needless to say, with a wide variety of entertainment options and activities, as well as the unique cuisine, a yacht charter to Mumbai will be an unforgettable experience!</P>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>mumbai</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Mumbai, India</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Seward</city>
		<state>Alaska</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Seward</image>
		<place>Seward</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Located on Alaska's Resurrection Bay, it is named for William H. Seward, who as U.S. Secretary of State in 1867 orchestrated the United States' purchase of Alaska from the Russian Empire. </p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>seward</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Seward, Alaska, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Juneau</city>
		<state>Alaska</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Juneau</image>
		<place>Juneau</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Juneau became the capital of Alaska in 1906, and was named after Joe Juneau, a gold prospector from Quebec.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>juneau</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Juneau, Alaska, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Anchorage</city>
		<state>Alaska</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Anchorage</image>
		<place>Anchorage</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Anchorage is Alaska's most populous city, and the fourth largest by area in the USA. It contains around 40% of the state's population.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>anchorage</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Anchorage, Alaska, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>Arizona</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Arizona</image>
		<place>Arizona</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Arizona became a state in 1912, and was the last state to join the Union other except for Hawaii and Alaska. Indian reservations make up around 25% of the state. It has 27 Native American tribes (the largest is Navajo Nation.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>arizona</link2>
		<areas>Lake Havasu City, Peoria, Phoenix, Morristown, Sun City, Mesa, Page, Gilbert, Surprise, Bullhead City, Mohave Valley, Chandler, Queen Creek, Kingman, Willow Beach, Tempe, Vail, Sierra Vista, Wickenburg, Marana, Lake Pleasant, Lake Havasu, Lake Saguaro, Lake Mead, Peoria, Bartlett Lake, Parker, Glendale, and Apache Lake.</areas>
		<criteria>Arizona, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Phoenix</city>
		<state>Arizona</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Phoenix</image>
		<place>Phoenix</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Phoenix is the only state capital with a population greater than 1 million, and is the 5th most populous city in the United States.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>phoenix</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Phoenix, Arizona, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>California</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>California</image>
		<place>California</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>The California Gold Rush in1848 led to a huge amount of immigration and a massive economic boom. California is now the US state with the largest population.  If it were a country, it would have the 5th largest economy in the world.  </p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>california</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>California, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Monterey Bay</city>
		<state>California</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Monterey-Bay</image>
		<place>Monterey Bay</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Located off the coast of cities such as Santa Cruz, Carmel and Monterey. The Monterey Canyon, located in its center, is one of the largest underwater canyons in the world at 249 miles long.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>monterey-bay</link2>
		<areas>San Francisco, Newport Beach, Santa Barbara, Marina del Rey, Oxnard, Los Angeles, Sacramento, Folsom, San Diego, Long Beach, Discovery Bay, Oakland, Santa Rosa, Huntington Beach, Hilmar, Tahoe City, Rancho Cucamonga, Angels Camp, La Grange, Castro Valley, Marin County, Irvine, Riverside, Richmond, Menifee, San Mateo, Glendale, Sausalito, Mission Viejo, Oceanside, Rio Linda, Oakley, Bakersfield, Wildomar, Torrance, Alameda, National City, Dollar Point, Ione, South Lake Tahoe, Redondo Beach, Stockton, Murrieta, Dana Point, Berkeley, Vacaville, Copperopolis, Monrovia, Concord, Modesto, Canyon Lake, San Joe, Truckee, Fresno, Antioch, Roseville, Bethel Island, Peteluma, Santa Cruz, Castaic, Spring Valley, El Dorado Hills, Bass Lake, Bradley, Cerritos, Emeryville, Placerville, Rocklin, Pamona, Big Bear Lake, Yuba City, Shasta Lake, Catalina, Lake Tahoe, Napa Valley, Wishon, Millerton Lake, Coronado, Lake Tulloch, Folsom Lake, Fontana, Donner Lake (Truckee), Benicia, Santa Catalina Island, Redding, Corona, Sanger, Carson, Castaic Lake, San Joaquin River, Novato, Lake Elsinore, Pine Flat Lake, Silverwood Lake, San Juan Capistrano, Don Pedro Reservoir, Lake Mead, Lake Pyramid (Castaic), Lake Piru, Lake Paris, Redwood National Park, Culver City, Lake Paris (Riverside), Seal Beach, Chula Vista, Camanche Lake, Hawthorne, Melones Lake, Vaellejo, Moreno Valley, Lewiston, Kernville, Janesville, Morro Bay, Palmdale, Douglas City, Lake Shasta, San Dimas, Lake Berryessa, Blue Lake, Laguna Hills, Winters, Simi Valley, Fairfield, Walnut Creek, Redwood City, Monterey, San Jose, San Bernardino, North Highlands, and Lake McClure (La Grange).</areas>
		<criteria>Monterey Bay, California, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>South Lake Tahoe</city>
		<state>California</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>South-Lake-Tahoe</image>
		<place>South Lake Tahoe</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Part of the city is located on the California-Nevada state  It has chilly, snowy winters and warm summers with cool nights.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>south-lake-tahoe</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>South Lake Tahoe, California, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>San Diego</city>
		<state>California</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>San-Diego</image>
		<place>San Diego</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>San Diego is located on the Mexican border and is Spanish for 'Saint Didacus'. It has the 8th largest population in the USA. Its deepwater port is home to the West Coast's only major submarine and shipbuilding yards.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>san-diego</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>San Diego, California, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Sacramento</city>
		<state>California</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Sacramento</image>
		<place>Sacramento</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Sacramento is the state capital and home of the governor. It hardly ever snows in Sacramento and from May - August each year is the sunniest location on the planet.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>sacramento</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Sacramento, California, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Newport Beach</city>
		<state>California</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Newport-Beach</image>
		<place>Newport Beach</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>The beaches of Newport Beach first became popular in 1905 when the Pacific Electric Railway started bringing tourists there. It is known for surfing, bodyboarding, bodysurfing, fishing, sailing, rowing, kayaking, and paddleboarding, and is home to the largest sailboat race on the world (the Newport to Ensenada International Yacht Race).</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>newport-beach</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Newport Beach, California, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Los Angeles</city>
		<state>California</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Los-Angeles</image>
		<place>Los Angeles</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Los Angeles is the second largest city in the USA (New York is the first), and home to Hollywood and much of the entertainment industry. It has one of the busiest container ports in the world, and has the third largest economy of any city in the world.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>los-angeles</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Los Angeles, California, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Long Beach</city>
		<state>California</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Long-Beach</image>
		<place>Long Beach</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>This waterfront town in Southern California is a popular tourist spot and also has one of the world's largest shipping ports.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>long-beach</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Long Beach, California, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Orlando</city>
		<state>Florida</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Orlando</image>
		<place>Orlando</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Due to nearby Disneyland, which was opened in 1971, Orlando is one of the most-visited cities in the world. Walt Disney chose this location over Miami and Tampa because it was safer from hurricanes.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>orlando</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Orlando, Florida, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Marco Island</city>
		<state>Florida</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Marco-Island</image>
		<place>Marco-Island</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Located near Naples Florida,it is the largest of the Ten Thousand Islands. With great beaches and resorts, it is a popular tourist destination.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>marco-island</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Marco Island, Florida, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Fort Lauderdale</city>
		<state>Florida</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Fort-Lauderdale</image>
		<place>Fort Lauderdale</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Fort Lauderdale is known as the Yachting Capital of the World, and is also a famous Spring Break destination for college students. It was named after forts built by the US during the Second Seminole War. </p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>fort-lauderdale</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Fort Lauderdale, Florida, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Clearwater Beach</city>
		<state>Florida</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Clearwater-Beach</image>
		<place>Clearwater Beach</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Its white sandy beaches have been ranked among the best in the USA. Each night at the main pier there are free shows by street performers and musical acts, and the Clearwater Marine Aquarium is home to Winter, the bottlenose dolphin featured in the movie Dolphin Tale.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>clearwater-beach</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Clearwater Beach, Florida, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Homosassa</city>
		<state>Florida</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Homosassa</image>
		<place>Homosassa</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Located on the Homosassa River, the name is is derived from a Seminole Indian name meaning either "river of fishes" or "pepper ridge."</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>homosassa</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Homosassa, Florida, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Everglades</city>
		<state>Florida</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Everglades</image>
		<place>Everglades</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Everglades National Park in South Florida was established in 1947 and is made up of 1.5 million acres of wilderness in South Florida. It is home to over 200,000 alligators.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>everglades</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Everglades, Florida, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Madeira Beach</city>
		<state>Florida</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Madeira-Beach</image>
		<place>Madeira Beach</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Madeira-BeacLocated near the city of St. Petersburg, it is named after the Portuguese island of Madeira and often referred to by the locals as Mad Beach.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>madeira-beach</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Madeira Beach, Florida, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Tampa Bay</city>
		<state>Florida</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Tampa-Bay</image>
		<place>Tampa Bay</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Originally named Spirito Santo, it became known as Tampa Bay soon after the US bought Florida from Spain in 1821. The name Spirito Santo seems to have disappeared from maps of the region in favor of "Tampa Bay" (sometimes divided into Tampa and Hillsboro Bays) soon after the US established Fort Brooke at the mouth of the Hillsborough River in 1824. Tampa Bay has been designated an 'Estuary of National Significance' by the EPA, with 2 refuges: Pinellas National Wildlife Refuge and the refuge on Egmont Key. </p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>tampa-bay</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Tampa Bay, Florida, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Fort Myers Beach</city>
		<state>Florida</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Fort-Myers-Beach</image>
		<place>Fort Myers Beach</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Seven miles of white sandy beach, made up of Estero Island and San Carlos.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>fort-myers-beach</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Fort Myers Beach, Florida, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Key West</city>
		<state>Florida</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Key-West</image>
		<place>Key West</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>The city of Key West is around 4 miles in size, and is closer to Havana, Cuba than it is to Miami. It has a tropical savanna climate </p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>key-west</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Key West, Florida, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>Georgia</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Georgia</image>
		<place>Georgia</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Georgia is named after King George II of Great Britain. Atlanta, Georgia's capital, has become a mini version of Hollywood, with TV shows such as Stranger Things, The Walking Dead, and The Vampire Diaries filmed there. It is also a popular filming location for movies, such as Forrest Gump, Sully, Baby Driver, The Hunger Games: Catching Fire, Captain America: Civil War, Black Panther, and Birds of Prey,</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>georgia</link2>
		<areas>Lavonia, Fitzgerald, Bishop, Statesboro, Covington, Bainbridge, Waleska, Sylvester, Gainesville, Morganton, Dawsonville, Cumming, Griffin, Acworth, Flowery Branch, Lagrange, Buford, Reed Creek, Milledgaville, Hoschton, St. Simons Island, Midway, Mableton, Dalton, Fair Play, Cartersville, Douglasville, St. Marys, Dallas, Eatonton, Oakwood, Atlanta, Lake Lanier (Gainesville), Lake Murray, Lake Hartwell, Lake Allatoona, Lake Wateree, Lake Sinclair, Lavonia, Anderson, Jonesboro, Rutledge, Savannah, Gainesville (Lake Lanier), and Dawsonville (Lake Lanier).</areas>
		<criteria>Georgia, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Savannah</city>
		<state>Georgia</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Savannah</image>
		<place>Savannah</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Founded in 1733, it is the oldest state in Georgia.  During the American Revolution and Civil War, it was an important strategic port.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>savannah</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Savannah, Georgia, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>Hawaii</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Hawaii</image>
		<place>Hawaii</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Hawaii was a US territory before it became the 50th (and last) US state. It is the only US state outside North America, the only state that is an archipelago, and the only state in the tropics.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>hawaii</link2>
		<areas>Honolulu (Oahu), Lahaina (Maui), Kapolei, Waialua, Kaneohe, Waianae, Kailua-Kona, Kauai, Lahaina, Waikiki, Big Island, Kewalo Harbour, Maui, Molokai, Lanai, Halwiwa, North Kona, Ko’Olina, Glacier Bay (Kapaa), Kaanapali Beach, Puako, Waianae (Oahu), Kihei (Maui), Kealakekua, and Captain Cook.</areas>
		<criteria>Hawaii, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Honolulu</city>
		<state>Hawaii</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Honolulu</image>
		<place>Honolulu</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Honolulu means 'sheltered harbor' or 'calm port' in Hawaiian. It has been the capital of the Hawaiian Islands since 1845.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>honolulu</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Honolulu, Hawaii, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Lahaina</city>
		<state>Hawaii</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Lahaina</image>
		<place>Lahaina</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Lahaina, located in Maui, was the capital of the Kingdom of Hawaii from 1820 to 1845, when Honolulu then became the capital. In the 1800s, Lahaina had a huge whaling industry.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>lahaina</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Lahaina, Hawaii, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Oahu</city>
		<state>Hawaii</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Oahu</image>
		<place>Oahu</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Home to the state capital of Honolulu, and also Pearl Harbor, it is the most populated Hawaiian island.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>oahu</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Oahu, Hawaii, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Big Island</city>
		<state>Hawaii</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Big-Island</image>	
		<place>Big Island</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text><p>Volcanoes are a popular tourist attraction on the island of Hawaii, as it was built from five regular volcanoes plus 2 submarine volcanoes.</p></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>big-island</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Big Island, Hawaii, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Kona</city>
		<state>Hawaii</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Kona</image>	
		<place>Kona</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text><p>World-famous Kona coffee comes from the Kona District on the Big Island.</p></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>kona</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Kona, Hawaii, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Kauai</city>
		<state>Hawaii</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Kauai</image>	
		<place>Kauai</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text><p>The beautiful, lush scenery of this Hawaiian island has been featured in movies such as Jurassic Park, South Pacific, Lilo and Stitch, and the TV show Lost was filmed there.</p></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>kauai</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Kauai, Hawaii, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Hilo</city>
		<state>Hawaii</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Hilo</image>	
		<place>Hilo</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text><p>Hilo is the largest city on the Big Island in Hawaii. It is home to the Mauna Loa Macadamia Nut Corporation, one of the world's leading producers of macadamia nuts.</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>hilo</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Hilo, Hawaii, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Waikiki</city>
		<state>Hawaii</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Waikiki</image>	
		<place>Waikiki</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text><p>Home to Waikiki Beach, made famous in the early 1900s by surfing legend Duke Kahanamoku.</p></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>waikiki</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Waikiki, Hawaii, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>Illinois</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Illinois</image>	
		<place>Illinois</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text><p>Movie director John Hughes based hit films, such as Ferris Bueller's Day Off, Home Alone, and The Breakfast Club, in the Chicago area.</p></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>illinois</link2>
		<areas>Chicago, Antioch, Ingleside, Olympia Fields, Fox Lake, Wauconda, Loves Park, Taylorville, Bolingbrook, Oak Brook, Itasca, Normal, Johnsburg, Ottowa, Sullivan Township, Annawan, Algonquin, Burnham, Dahlgren, Morton, Lake Michigan, Chicago River, and Calumet River.</areas>
		<criteria>Illinois, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Chicago</city>
		<state>Illinois</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Chicago</image>	
		<place>Chicago</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text><p>O'Hare International Airport in Chicago is one of the world's ten busiest airports.</p></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>chicago</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Chicago, Illinois, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>Louisiana</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Louisiana</image>	
		<place>Louisiana</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text><p>In 1803, President Thomas Jefferson purchased the Louisiana territory from Napoleon Bonaparte for $15 million as part of his Westward expansion plan.</p></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>louisiana</link2>
		<areas>New Orleans, Madisonville, Slidell, Sulphur, Marrero, Kenner, Morgan City, Terrytown, Chalmette, Lafayette, Lake Pontchartrain, Breaux Bridge, Grand Isle, Dularge, Springfield, Venice, Myrtle Grove, Delacroix, Lafitte, and Hopedale.</areas>
		<criteria>Louisiana, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>New Orleans</city>
		<state>Louisiana</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>New-Orleans</image>	
		<place>New Orleans</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text><p>Famous for its Cajun music and jazz, Creole cuisine, Bourbon Street and French Quarter, and the annual Mardi Gras festival.</p> </text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>new-orleans</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>New Orleans, Louisiana, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>Maryland</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Maryland</image>	
		<place>Maryland</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text><p>Maryland was named after England's Queen Mary (Henrietta Maria), the wife of England's King Charles.</p></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>maryland</link2>
		<areas>Baltimore, Annapolis, Pasadena, Galesville, Chester, Edgewater, Solomons, Saint Michaels, and Pasadena (Chesapeake Bay).</areas>
		<criteria>Maryland, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Washington DC</city>
		<state>Maryland</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Washington-DC</image>	
		<place>Washington DC</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text><p>Washington DC is the capital city of the United States, and not a state or part of any state. It was named for President George Washington, and the 'Columbia' part is a female personification of the nation.</p></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>washington-dc</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Washington DC, Maryland, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>Massachusetts</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Massachusetts</image>	
		<place>Massachusetts</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>massachusetts</link2>
		<areas>Boston, Nantucket, Hyannis, Chatham, Plymouth, Quincy, Beverly, Provincetown, Falmouth, Marlbehead, Scituate, Hull, Barnstable, Tisbury, Yarmouth, New Bedford, Dennis, Martha's Vineyard, Newburyport, Fairhaven, Winthrop, Andover, Haverhill, Weston, Essex, Salem, Groveland, Hingham, Manchester-By-The-Sea, Southwick, Wales, Marblehead, Gloucester, Lynn, Revere, Osterville, Wellfleet, Truro, Bourne, Boston Harbor, and Cape Cod.</areas>
		<criteria>Massachusetts, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>New Jersey</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>New-Jersey</image>	
		<place>New Jersey</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>new-jersey</link2>
		<areas>Toms River, Lavallette, Ocean City, Berkeley Township, Princeton, Beach Haven, Point Pleasant, Ship Bottom, Brick Township, Somers Point, Lacey Township, Sea Bright, Union Beach, Brielle, Long Port, Highlands, Red Bank, Island Heights, Monmouth Beach, Galloway, Barnegat Township, Brigantine, Atlantic Highlands, Northfield, Jersey City, Alpine, Englewood Cliffs, Belmar, Keyport, Lanoka Harbor, Weehawken, Bordentown, Hoboken, Perth Amboy, Avalon, Atlantic City, Long Beach Island, Manasquan, Long Branch,  Rumson, Seaside Heights, Barnegat Bay, Point Pleasant Beach, Leonardo, and Englewood Cliffs (Hudson River).</areas>
		<criteria>New Jersey, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Cape May</city>
		<state>New Jersey</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Cape-May</image>	
		<place>Cape May</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>cape-may</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Cape May, New Jersey, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>New York City</city>
		<state>New York</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>New-York-City</image>	
		<place>New York City</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>new-york-city</link2>
		<areas>New York Harbor, Brooklyn, Port Washington, East Rockaway, New Rochelle, Queens, The Bronx, Staten Island, Long Island, Buffalo, Grand Island, New York City, NY Harbor, Jamaica Bay, Howard Beach, Hudson River, Long Island Sound, East Hampton, Sag Harbor, Montauk, Manhattan, Glen Cove, Mattituck (North Fork), Shelter Island, Port Chester, Jamesport, Southampton, Greenport, Hampton Bays, Patchogue, Sayville, Bay Shore, Northport, Bellport, Moriches, Huntington, Kingston, Mahopac, Peekskill, Nyack, Piermont, Freeport, Saugerties, and Green Point (Long Island).</areas>
		<criteria>New York City, New York, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>North Carolina</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>North-Carolina</image>	
		<place>North Carolina</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>north-carolina</link2>
		<areas>Wilmington, Atlantic Beach, Charlotte, Raleigh, Fayetteville, Mooresville, Chapel Hill, Wrightsville Beach, Washington, Monroe, Greensboro, Morehead City, New London, Hubert, Swan Quarter, Merritt, Nebo, Cornelius, Littleton, Southport, Lake Lure, Rocky Point, Huntersville, Shallotte, Sherrills Ford, Leland, Statesville, Wilson, Beaufort, Denver, Topton, Greenville, Newport, Wake Forest, New Bern, Sneads Ferry, Lake Norman of Catawba, Robbinsville, Semora, Lincolnton, Bah, High Point, Iron Station, Belmont, Jacksonville, Apex, Hertford, Elkin, Roxboro, Wanchese, Carolina Beach, Mount Gilead,  Holden Beach, Richfield, Durham, Kill Devil Hills, Hampstead, Bath, Mount Holly, Brogden, Lake Lanier, Hatteras, Falls Lake, Emerald Isle, Lake Norman, Mountain Island Lake, Lake Murray, Lake Wylie, Lake Keowee, Lake Hartwell, Aberdeen, Ayden, Clarks Hill Lake, Lake Hickory, Nags Head (Outer Banks), Manteo, Salisbury, Morehead, North Topsail Beach, Moyock, Lake Rhodhiss, Davidson, and Charlotte (Mountain Island Lake).</areas>
		<criteria>North Carolina, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Outer Banks</city>
		<state>North Carolina</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Outer-Banks</image>	
		<place>Outer Banks</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>outer-banks</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Outer Banks, North Carolina, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>Ohio</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Ohio</image>	
		<place>Ohio</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>ohio</link2>
		<areas>Columbus, Akron, Cincinnati, Toledo, Lewis Center, Port Clinton, Streetsboro, Thornville, Vermilion, Tallmadge, Conneaut, Batavia, North Royalton, Columbus (Alum Creek Lake), Cleveland, Jamestown, Mentor, Sheffield Lake, Lake Erie, Warren, Oak Harbor, Kellys Island, Ashtabula, Napoleon, Lakeside Marblehead, Grand River, Westlake, Rocky River, and Belleview (Lake Erie/Sandusky Bay).</areas>
		<criteria>Ohio, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Cincinnati</city>
		<state>Ohio</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Cincinnati</image>	
		<place>Cincinnati</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>cincinnati</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Cincinnati, Ohio, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>Oregon</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Oregon</image>	
		<place>Oregon</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>oregon</link2>
		<areas>Portland, Beaverton, Treasure Valley, Bend, Newport, St. Helens, Oakridge, Astoria, Elkton, Springfield, Maupin, Ashland, Keizer, McMinnville, Sisters, Columbia River, Willamette River, Tillamook Bay, Pacific City, Eugene, Cascade Locks, Hermistan, and Adrian.</areas>
		<criteria>Oregon, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Cascade Locks</city>
		<state>Oregon</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Cascade-Locks</image>	
		<place>Cascade Locks</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>cascade-locks</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Cascade Locks, Oregon, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Portland</city>
		<state>Oregon</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Portland</image>	
		<place>Portland</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>portland</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Portland, Oregon, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>Pennsylvania</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Pennsylvania</image>	
		<place>Pennsylvania</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>pennsylvania</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Pennsylvania, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Philadelphia</city>
		<state>Pennsylvania</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Philadelphia</image>	
		<place>Philadelphia</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>philadelphia</link2>
		<areas>Pittsburgh, Conneaut, Lakeville, McKeesport, Plum, Greentown, Blakeslee, Easton, Saylorsburg, Bird In Hand, Emmaus, Lake Erie, Paupack (Lake Wallenpaupack), Harveys Lake, Great Bend Township, Westfield, Hesston (Raystown Lake), Conneaut Lake, Philadelphia, and Erie.</areas>
		<criteria>Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>Rhode Island</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Rhode-Island</image>	
		<place>Rhode Island</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>rhode-island</link2>
		<areas>Newport, Narragansett, Portsmouth, Providence, Barrington, North Kingstown, Coventry, South Kingstown, Westerly, East Greenwich, Wickford, Jamestown, Cranston, Warwick, and Bristol.</areas>
		<criteria>Rhode Island, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>South Carolina</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>South-Carolina</image>	
		<place>South Carolina</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>south-carolina</link2>
		<areas>Myrtle Beach, Charleston, Hilton Head Island, Augusta, Lake Wylie, Anderson, Greensville, Tega Cay, Mount Pleasant, Ladson, Salem, Clover, Shallotte, Johns Island, Saint Helena Island, North, Goose Creek, McCormick, Rock Hill, Fair Play, Greer, Edgefield, Compobello, Monks Corner, Bluffton, Conway, Bishop, Camden, Townville, Somerville, Lavonia, Chapin, Lancaster, Columbia, Folly Beach, Lake Murray, North Myrtle Beach, Low Country, Lake Wando, Wylie, Mt. Pleasant, Lake Keowee, Lake Oconee, Lake Hartwell, Lake Wateree, Hooley Island, Lake Sinclair, Little River, Lake Jocassee, Six Mile, Lexington (Lake Murray), Appling, McIntyre, Edisto Island, Lake Russel, Anderson (Lake Hartwell), and Eutawville (Lake Marion).</areas>
		<criteria>South Carolina, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Charleston</city>
		<state>South Carolina</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Charleston</image>	
		<place>Charleston</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>charleston</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Charleston, South Carolina, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Hilton Head Island</city>
		<state>South Carolina</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Hilton-Head-Island</image>	
		<place>Hilton Head Island</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>hilton-head-island</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Hilton Head Island, South Carolina, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>Tennessee</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Tennessee</image>	
		<place>Tennessee</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>tennessee</link2>
		<areas>Nashville, Knoxville, Dandridge, Chattanooga, Hendersonville, Winchester, Harrison, New Tazewell, Mt. Juliet, Andersonville, Powell, Soddy-Daisy, Maynardville, Sharps Chapel, Robbinsville, Lebanon, Cleveland, Silver Point, Byrdstown, Hendersonville (Old Hickory Lake), Percy Priest Lake, Norris Lake, Dresden, Alpine, Guild, and Dandridge (Douglas Lake).</areas>
		<criteria>Tennessee, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Pigeon Forge</city>
		<state>Tennessee</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Pigeon-Forge</image>	
		<place>Pigeon Forge</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>pigeon-forge</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Pigeon Forge, Tennessee, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Nashville</city>
		<state>Tennessee</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Nashville</image>	
		<place>Nashville</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>nashville</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Nashville, Tennessee, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>Utah</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Utah</image>	
		<place>Utah</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>utah</link2>
		<areas>Salt Lake City, Provo, Lehi, Sandy, Midway, Alpine, Spanish Fork, Orem, Herriman, St. George, South Jordan, Willard Bay, Yuba Lake, Harriman, Midvale, Dutch John (Green River), Eagle Mountain, Pleasant Grove,and Hurricane.</areas>
		<criteria>Utah, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Moab</city>
		<state>Utah</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Moab</image>	
		<place>Moab</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>moab</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Moab, Utah, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>Virginia</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Virginia</image>	
		<place>Virginia</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>virginia</link2>
		<areas>Virginia Beach, Norfolk, Arlington, Alexandria, Chesapeake, Lynchburg, Woodbridge, Lorton, Fredericksville, Chantilly, Readville, Stafford, Bumpass, Mineral, White Post, Mechanicsville, Gloucester Point, Hampton, TappaHannock, Fort Belvior, Lake Gaston, Hartfield, and Yorktown.</areas>
		<criteria>Virginia, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Norfolk</city>
		<state>Virginia</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Norfolk</image>	
		<place>Norfolk</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>norfolk</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Norfolk, Virginia, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>Washington State</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Washington</image>	
		<place>Washington State</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>washington</link2>
		<areas>Seattle, Olympia, Tacoma, Bellingham, Everett, Kirkland, Renton, Kent, Anacortes, Mead, Bellevue, Davenport, Menatchee, Auburn, Friday Harbor, Gig Harbor, Burien, Chelan, Kennewick, Bonney Lake, Vancouver, Ridgefield, Spokane County, Liberty Lake, Lynnwood, Quincy, Seatac, LA Conner, Bremerton, Des Moines, Ruston, Edmonds, Bainbridge Islands, Spanaway, Eastsound, Kenmore, Everette, San Juan Island, Lake Washington, Lake Union, Puget Sound, Lake Sammamish, St. Helens, Lake Tapps, Conner, Mercy Island, Leschi, Olga, Lake Chelan, Columbia River, Snohomish, Longview, Puyallup, Orcas Island, Clarkston, Metchosin, Astoria, Toledo, Sequim, Port Townsend Bay, and Belfair.</areas>
		<criteria>Washington State, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>Wyoming</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Wyoming</image>	
		<place>Wyoming</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>wyoming</link2>
		<areas>Jackson, Cheyenne, and Casper.</areas>
		<criteria>Wyoming, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Jackson</city>
		<state>Wyoming</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Jackson</image>	
		<place>Jackson</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>jackson</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Jackson, Wyoming, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Puerto Vallarta</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Mexico</country>
		<image>Puerto-Vallarta</image>	
		<place>Puerto Vallarta</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>puerto-vallarta</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Puerto Vallarta, Mexico</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Naples</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Italy</country>
		<image>Naples</image>	
		<place>Naples</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>naples</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Naples, Italy</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Capri</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Italy</country>
		<image>Capri</image>	
		<place>Capri</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>capri</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Capri, Italy</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Positano</city>
		<state>Capri</state>
		<country>Italy</country>
		<image>Positano</image>	
		<place>Positano</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>positano</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Positano, Capri, Italy</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Durban</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>South Africa</country>
		<image>Durban</image>	
		<place>Durban</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>durban</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Durban, South Africa</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Amalfi Coast</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Italy</country>
		<image>Amalfi-Coast</image>	
		<place>Amalfi Coast</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>amalfi-coast</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Amalfi Coast, Italy</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Sorrento</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Italy</country>
		<image>Sorrento</image>	
		<place>Sorrento</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>sorrento</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Sorrento, Italy</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Salerno</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Italy</country>
		<image>Salerno</image>	
		<place>Salerno</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>salerno</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Salerno, Italy</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Ischia</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Italy</country>
		<image>Ischia</image>	
		<place>Ischia</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>ischia</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Ischia, Italy</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Riga</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Latvia</country>
		<image>Riga</image>	
		<place>Riga</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>riga</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Riga, Latvia</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Cabo San Lucas</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Mexico</country>
		<image>Cabo-San-Lucas</image>	
		<place>Cabo San Lucas</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>cabo-san-lucas</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Cabo San Lucas, Mexico</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Los Cabos</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Mexico</country>
		<image>Los-Cabos</image>	
		<place>Los Cabos</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>los-cabos</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Los Cabos, Mexico</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Sao Paulo</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Brazil</country>
		<image>Sao-Paulo</image>	
		<place>Sao Paulo</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>sao-paulo</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Sao Paulo, Brazil</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Santos and Guaruja</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Brazil</country>
		<image>Santos-and-Guaruja</image>	
		<place>Santos and Guaruja</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>santos-and-guaruja</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Santos and Guaruja, Brazil</criteria>
	</location>
	
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>St. Thomas</state>
		<country>US Virgin Islands</country>
		<image>St.-Thomas</image>	
		<place>St. Thomas</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>st.-thomas</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>St. Thomas, US Virgin Islands</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>Saint Thomas</state>
		<country>US Virgin Islands</country>
		<image>Saint-Thomas</image>	
		<place>Saint Thomas</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>saint-thomas</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Saint Thomas, US Virgin Islands</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Cancun</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Mexico</country>
		<image>Cancun</image>	
		<place>Cancun</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>cancun</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Cancun, Mexico</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Sydney</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Australia</country>
		<image>Sydney</image>	
		<place>Sydney</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>sydney</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Sydney, Australia</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Mu Ko Ang Thong</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Thailand</country>
		<image>Mu-Ko—Ang-Rhong</image>	
		<place>Mu Ko Ang Thong</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>mu-ko—ang-rhong</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Mu Ko Ang Thong, Thailand</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Algarve</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Portugal</country>
		<image>Algarve</image>	
		<place>Algarve</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>algarve</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Algarve, Portugal</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Split</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Croatia</country>
		<image>Split</image>	
		<place>Split</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>split</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Split, Croatia</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Vodice</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Croatia</country>
		<image>Vodice</image>	
		<place>Vodice</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>vodice</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Vodice, Croatia</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Kornati National Park</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Croatia</country>
		<image>Kornati-National-Park</image>	
		<place>Kornati National Park</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>kornati-national-park</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Kornati National Park, Croatia</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Niagara Falls</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>New York</country>
		<image>Niagara-Falls</image>	
		<place>Niagara Falls</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>niagara-falls</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Niagara Falls, New York</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Kyiv</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Ukraine</country>
		<image>Kyiv</image>	
		<place>Kyiv</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>kyiv</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Kyiv, Ukraine</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Kapisillit</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Greenland</country>
		<image>Kapisillit</image>	
		<place>Kapisillit</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>kapisillit</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Kapisillit, Greenland</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Adeje</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Canary Islands</country>
		<image>Adeje</image>	
		<place>Adeje</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>adeje</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Adeje, Canary Islands</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Tenerife</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Canary Islands</country>
		<image>Tenerife</image>	
		<place>Tenerife</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>tenerife</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Tenerife, Canary Islands</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Antigua</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Guatemala</country>
		<image>Antigua</image>	
		<place>Antigua</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
			<p>Magical, fascinating, breathtaking – these are just a few of the many words that best describe Antigua, one of the Leeward Islands in the Caribbean region.</p>
			<p>It is yet another exquisite crowning jewel of the Caribbean, and a private luxury yacht charter will help you explore the ultimate beauty of it.</p>
			<p>The shores of English and Falmouth Harbors in Antigua are brimming with history and are the best spots to begin your yacht charter journey on the island. Falmouth Harbor is a contemporary marina that presents the ideal starting point. From thereon, the island is your oyster, and you can go wherever you like, such as the Green Island, where the sparkling white sand beaches make the perfect spots for relaxation. You can also head over to Nonesuch Bay for some exciting and fun-filled watersports.</p>
			<p>The English harbor, on the other hand, is where Antigua best flaunts its maritime heritage, given how it was once also the most important Caribbean military base for Great Britain.</p>
			<p>Once you begin cruising through this gorgeous island with your yacht cutting through the beautiful blue waters, the natural beauty will leave you in great awe, giving you a chance to explore the fascinating intricacies of its shoreline.</p>
			<p>A private yacht charter in Antigua provides the ideal opportunity for you to witness the turquoise waters of the island gushing against the white sands and rocky coves, making it a true paradise holiday for all the dreamers out there!</p>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>antigua</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Antigua, Guatemala</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Playa del Carmen</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Mexico</country>
		<image>Playa-del-Carmen</image>	
		<place>Playa del Carmen</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text>
		</text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>playa-del-carmen</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Playa del Carmen, Mexico</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Barcelona</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Spain</country>
		<image>Barcelona</image>	
		<place>Barcelona</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>barcelona</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Barcelona, Spain</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Calgiari</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Italy</country>
		<image>Calgiari</image>	
		<place>Calgiari</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>calgiari</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Calgiari, Italy</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Fajardo</city>
		<state>Puerto Rico</state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>Fajardo</image>	
		<place>Fajardo</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>fajardo</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Fajardo, Puerto Rico, United States</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Willemstad</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Curacao</country>
		<image>Willemstad</image>	
		<place>Willemstad</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>willemstad</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Willemstad, Curacao</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Kassandra</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Greece</country>
		<image>Kassandra</image>	
		<place>Kassandra</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>kassandra</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Kassandra, Greece</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Chios</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Greece</country>
		<image>Chios</image>	
		<place>Chios</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>chios</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Chios, Greece</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Brussels</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Belgium</country>
		<image>Brussels</image>	
		<place>Brussels</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>brussels</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Brussels, Belgium</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Gent</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Belgium</country>
		<image>Gent</image>	
		<place>Gent</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>gent</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Gent, Belgium</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Reykjavik</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Iceland</country>
		<image>Reykjavik</image>	
		<place>Reykjavik</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>reykjavik</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Reykjavik, Iceland</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Nuuk</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Greenland</country>
		<image>Nuuk</image>	
		<place>Nuuk</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>nuuk</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Nuuk, Greenland</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Fuengirola</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Spain</country>
		<image>Fuengirola</image>	
		<place>Fuengirola</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>fuengirola</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Fuengirola, Spain</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Marsa Alam</city>
		<state>Red Sea</state>
		<country>Egypt</country>
		<image>Marsa-Alam</image>	
		<place>Marsa Alam</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>marsa-alam</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Marsa Alam, Red Sea, Egypt</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Nikiti</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Greece</country>
		<image>Nikiti</image>	
		<place>Nikiti</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>nikiti</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Nikiti, Greece</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Phuket</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Thailand</country>
		<image>Phuket</image>	
		<place>Phuket</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>phuket</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Phuket, Thailand</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Jokulsarlon Glacier Lagoon</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Iceland</country>
		<image>Jokulsarlon-Glacier-Lagoon</image>	
		<place>Jokulsarlon Glacier Lagoon</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>jokulsarlon-glacier-lagoon</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Jokulsarlon Glacier Lagoon, Iceland</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Bayahibe</city>
		<state>Cotubanama National Park</state>
		<country>Dominican Republic</country>
		<image>Bayahibe</image>	
		<place>Bayahibe</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>bayahibe</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Bayahibe, Cotubanama National Park, Dominican Republic</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Punta Cana</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Dominican Republic</country>
		<image>Punta-Cana</image>	
		<place>Punta Cana</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>punta-cana</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Punta Cana, Dominican Republic</criteria>
	</location>
	
	<location>
		<city>Venice</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Italy</country>
		<image>Venice</image>	
		<place>Venice</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>venice</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Venice, Italy</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Nice</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Italy</country>
		<image>Nice</image>	
		<place>Nice</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>nice</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Nice, Italy</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Beaulieu</city>
		<state>French Riviera</state>
		<country>Italy</country>
		<image>Beaulieu</image>	
		<place>Beaulieu</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>beaulieu</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Beaulieu, French Riviera, Italy</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Koh Samui</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Thailand</country>
		<image>Koh-Samui</image>	
		<place>Koh Samui</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>koh-samui</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Koh Samui, Thailand</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Ponta Delgada</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Portugal</country>
		<image>Ponta-Delgada</image>	
		<place>Ponta Delgada</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>ponta-delgada</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Ponta Delgada, Portugal</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Hurghada</city>
		<state>Red Sea</state>
		<country>Egypt</country>
		<image>Hurghada</image>	
		<place>Hurghada</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>hurghada</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Hurghada, Red Sea, Egypt</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Phi Phi</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Thailand</country>
		<image>Phi-Phi</image>	
		<place>Phi Phi</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>phi-phi</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Phi Phi, Thailand</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Bamboo Island</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Thailand</country>
		<image>Bamboo-Island</image>	
		<place>Bamboo Island</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>bamboo-island</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Bamboo Island, Thailand</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Riviera Maya</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Mexico</country>
		<image>Riviera-Maya</image>	
		<place>Riviera Maya</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>riviera-maya</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Riviera Maya, Mexico</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Kas</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Turkey</country>
		<image>Kas</image>	
		<place>Kas</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>kas</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Kas, Turkey</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Portofino</city>
		<state>Algarve</state>
		<country>Portugal</country>
		<image>Portofino</image>	
		<place>Portofino</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>portofino</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Portofino, Algarve, Portugal</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Tiran Island</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Egypt</country>
		<image>Tiran-Island</image>	
		<place>Tiran-Island</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>tiran-island</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Tiran Island, Egypt</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Ras Muhammad National Park</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Egypt</country>
		<image>Ras-Muhammad-National-Park</image>	
		<place>Ras Muhammad National Park</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>ras-muhammad-national-park</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Ras Muhammad National Park, Egypt</criteria>
	</location>
	

	<location>
		<city>Cagliari</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Italy</country>
		<image>Cagliari</image>	
		<place>Cagliari</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>cagliari</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Cagliari, Italy</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Puerto Aventuras</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Mexico</country>
		<image>Puerto-Aventuras</image>	
		<place>Puerto Aventuras</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>puerto-aventuras</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Puerto Aventuras, Mexico</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Athens</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Greece</country>
		<image>Athens</image>	
		<place>Athens</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>athens</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Athens, Greece</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Toronto</city>
		<state>Ontario</state>
		<country>Canada</country>
		<image>Toronto</image>	
		<place>Toronto</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>toronto</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Toronto, Ontario, Canada</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Dubrovnik</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Croatia</country>
		<image>Dubrovnik</image>	
		<place>Dubrovnik</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>dubrovnik</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Dubrovnik, Croatia</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Adamas</city>
		<state>Cyclades</state>
		<country>Greece</country>
		<image>Adamas</image>	
		<place>Adamas</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>adamas</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Adamas, Cyclades, Greece</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Cape Town</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>South Africa</country>
		<image>Cape-Town</image>	
		<place>Cape Town</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>cape-town</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Cape Town, South Africa</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Vancouver Island</city>
		<state>Telegraph Cave</state>
		<country>Canada</country>
		<image>Vancouver-Island</image>	
		<place>Vancouver Island</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>vancouver-island</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Vancouver Island, Telegraph Cave, Canada</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Queenstown</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>New Zealand</country>
		<image>Queenstown</image>	
		<place>Queenstown</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>queenstown</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Queenstown, New Zealand</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Zurich</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Switzerland</country>
		<image>Zurich</image>	
		<place>Zurich</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>zurich</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Zurich, Switzerland</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Geneva</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Switzerland</country>
		<image>Geneva</image>	
		<place>Geneva</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>geneva</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Geneva, Switzerland</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Interlaken</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Switzerland</country>
		<image>Interlaken</image>	
		<place>Interlaken</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>interlaken</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Interlaken, Switzerland</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Lindos</city>
		<state>Island of Rhodes</state>
		<country>Greece</country>
		<image>Lindos</image>	
		<place>Lindos</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>lindos</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Lindos, Island of Rhodes, Greece</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Kekova</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Turkey</country>
		<image>Kekova</image>	
		<place>Kekova</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>kekova</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Kekova, Turkey</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Trou dEau Douce</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Mauritius</country>
		<image>Trou-dEau-Douce</image>	
		<place>Trou dEau Douce</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>trou-deau-douce</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Trou dEau Douce, Mauritius</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Ile Aux Benitiers</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Mauritius</country>
		<image>Ile-Aux-Benitiers</image>	
		<place>Ile Aux Benitiers</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>ile-aux-benitiers</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Ile Aux Benitiers, Mauritius</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Cambrils</city>
		<state>Costa Dorada</state>
		<country>Spain</country>
		<image>Cambrils</image>	
		<place>Cambrils</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>cambrils</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Cambrils, Costa Dorada, Spain</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Quarteira</city>
		<state>Algarve</state>
		<country>Portugal</country>
		<image>Quarteira</image>	
		<place>Quarteira</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>quarteira</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Quarteira, Algarve, Portugal</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Mallorca</city>
		<state>Palma Bay</state>
		<country>Spain</country>
		<image>Mallorca</image>	
		<place>Mallorca</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>mallorca</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Mallorca, Palma Bay, Spain</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Alcudia</city>
		<state>Balearic Islands</state>
		<country>Spain</country>
		<image>Alcudia</image>	
		<place>Alcudia</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>alcudia</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Alcudia, Balearic Islands, Spain</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Bergen</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Norway</country>
		<image>Bergen</image>	
		<place>Bergen</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>bergen</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Bergen, Norway</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Haleiwa</city>
		<state>Oahu</state>
		<country>Hawaii</country>
		<image>Haleiwa</image>	
		<place>Haleiwa</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>haleiwa</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Haleiwa, Oahu, Hawaii</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Philipsburg</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>St. Martin</country>
		<image>Philipsburg</image>	
		<place>Philipsburg</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>philipsburg</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Philipsburg, St. Martin</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Fuerteventura</city>
		<state>Lobos Island</state>
		<country>Canary Islands</country>
		<image>Fuerteventura</image>	
		<place>Fuerteventura</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>fuerteventura</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Fuerteventura, Lobos Island, Canary Islands</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Naxos</city>
		<state>Cyclades</state>
		<country>Greece</country>
		<image>Naxos</image>	
		<place>Naxos</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>naxos</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Naxos, Cyclades, Greece</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Luxor</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Egypt</country>
		<image>Luxor</image>	
		<place>Luxor</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>luxor</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Luxor, Egypt</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Mykonos</city>
		<state>Cyclades</state>
		<country>Greece</country>
		<image>Mykonos</image>	
		<place>Mykonos</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>mykonos</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Mykonos, Cyclades, Greece</criteria>
	</location>
	
	<location>
		<city>Lisbon</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Portugal</country>
		<image>Lisbon</image>	
		<place>Lisbon</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>lisbon</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Lisbon, Portugal</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Nikiti</city>
		<state>Macedonia</state>
		<country>Greece</country>
		<image>Nikiti</image>	
		<place>Nikiti</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>nikiti</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Nikiti, Macedonia, Greece</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Oslo</city>
		<state>Bergen</state>
		<country>Norway</country>
		<image>Oslo</image>	
		<place>Oslo</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>oslo</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Oslo, Bergen, Norway</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Hvar</city>
		<state>Paklinski Islands</state>
		<country>Croatia</country>
		<image>Hvar</image>	
		<place>Hvar</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>hvar</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Hvar, Paklinski Islands, Croatia</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Andratx</city>
		<state>Balearic Islands</state>
		<country>Spain</country>
		<image>Andratx</image>	
		<place>Andratx</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>andratx</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Andratx, Balearic Islands, Spain</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Lake Como</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Italy</country>
		<image>Lake-Como</image>	
		<place>Lake Como</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>lake-como</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Lake Como, Italy</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Makrys Gialos</city>
		<state>Crete</state>
		<country>Greece</country>
		<image>Makrys-Gialos</image>	
		<place>Makrys Gialos</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>makrys-gialos</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Makrys Gialos, Crete, Greece</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Phnom Penh</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Cambodia</country>
		<image>Phnom-Penh</image>	
		<place>Phnom Penh</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>phnom-penh</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Phnom Penh, Cambodia</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Marseille</city>
		<state>Provence</state>
		<country>France</country>
		<image>Marseille</image>	
		<place>Marseille</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>marseille</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Marseille, Provence, France</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Puerto Plata</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Dominican Republic</country>
		<image>Puerto-Plata</image>	
		<place>Puerto Plata</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>puerto-plata</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Puerto Plata, Dominican Republic</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Muscat</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Oman</country>
		<image>Muscat</image>	
		<place>Muscat</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>muscat</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Muscat, Oman</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Koh Phi Phi</city>
		<state>Krabi</state>
		<country>Thailand</country>
		<image>Koh-Phi-Phi</image>	
		<place>Koh Phi Phi</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>koh-phi-phi</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Koh Phi Phi, Krabi, Thailand</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Zakinthos</city>
		<state>Ionian Islands</state>
		<country>Greece</country>
		<image>Zakinthos</image>	
		<place>Zakinthos</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>zakinthos</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Zakinthos, Ionian Islands, Greece</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Cinque Terre</city>
		<state>Tuscany</state>
		<country>Italy</country>
		<image>Cinque-Terre</image>	
		<place>Cinque Terre</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>cinque-terre</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Cinque Terre, Tuscany, Italy</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Lake Maggiore</city>
		<state>Piedmont</state>
		<country>Italy</country>
		<image>Lake-Maggiore</image>	
		<place>Lake Maggiore</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>lake-maggiore</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Lake Maggiore, Piedmont, Italy</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Bari</city>
		<state>Castellana Cave</state>
		<country>Italy</country>
		<image>Bari</image>	
		<place>Bari</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>bari</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Bari, Castellana Cave, Italy</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Victoria</city>
		<state>Vancouver Island</state>
		<country>Canada</country>
		<image>Victoria</image>	
		<place>Victoria</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>victoria</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Victoria, Vancouver Island, Canada</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Moscow</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Russia</country>
		<image>Moscow</image>	
		<place>Moscow</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>moscow</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Moscow, Russia</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Portimao</city>
		<state>Algarve</state>
		<country>Portugal</country>
		<image>Portimao</image>	
		<place>Portimao</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>portimao</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Portimao, Algarve, Portugal</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Amsterdam</city>
		<state>Holland</state>
		<country>Netherlands</country>
		<image>Amsterdam</image>	
		<place>Amsterdam</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>amsterdam</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Amsterdam, Holland, Netherlands</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Faro</city>
		<state>Algarve</state>
		<country>Portugal</country>
		<image>Faro</image>	
		<place>Faro</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>faro</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Faro, Algarve, Portugal</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Comino</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Malta</country>
		<image>Comino</image>	
		<place>Comino</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>comino</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Comino, Malta</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Port of Spain</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Trinidad and Tobago</country>
		<image>Port-of-Spain</image>	
		<place>Port of Spain</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>port-of-spain</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Port of Spain, Trinidad and Tobago</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>La Crucecita</city>
		<state>Oaxaca</state>
		<country>Mexico</country>
		<image>La-Crucecita</image>	
		<place>La Crucecita</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>la-crucecita</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>La Crucecita, Oxaca, Mexico</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Paris</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>France</country>
		<image>Paris</image>	
		<place>Paris</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>paris</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Paris, France</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Mazatlan</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Mexico</country>
		<image>Mazatlan</image>	
		<place>Mazatlan</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>mazatlan</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Mazatlan, Mexico</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Halkidiki</city>
		<state>Macedonia</state>
		<country>Greece</country>
		<image>Halkidiki</image>	
		<place>Halkidiki</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>halkidiki</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Halkidiki, Macedonia, Greece</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Bali</city>
		<state>Komodo Island</state>
		<country>Indonesia</country>
		<image>Bali</image>	
		<place>Bali</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>bali</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Bali, Komodo Island, Indonesia</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>St. Lucia</country>
		<image>St.-Lucia</image>	
		<place>St. Lucia</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>st.-lucia</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>St. Lucia</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Astypalea</city>
		<state>Dodecanese</state>
		<country>Greece</country>
		<image>Astypalea</image>	
		<place>Astypalea</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>astypalea</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Astypalea, Dodecanese, Greece</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Nydri</city>
		<state>Ionian Islands</state>
		<country>Greece</country>
		<image>Nydri</image>	
		<place>Nydri</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>nydri</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Nydri, Ionian Islands, Greece</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Hoi An</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Vietnam</country>
		<image>Hoi-An</image>	
		<place>Hoi An</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>hoi-an</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Hoi An, Vietnam</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Verona</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Italy</country>
		<image>Verona</image>	
		<place>Verona</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>verona</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Verona, Italy</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Sao Miguel Island</city>
		<state>Ponta Delgada</state>
		<country>Portugal</country>
		<image>Sao-Miguel-Island</image>	
		<place>Sao Miguel Island</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>sao-miguel-island</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Sao Miguel Island, Ponta Delgada, Portugal</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Beijing</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>China</country>
		<image>Beijing</image>	
		<place>Beijing</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>beijing</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Beijing, China</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Cairns</city>
		<state>Queensland</state>
		<country>Australia</country>
		<image>Cairns</image>	
		<place>Cairns</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>cairns</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Cairns, Queensland, Australia</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Curacao</country>
		<image>Curacao</image>	
		<place>Curacao</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>curacao</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Curacao</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Albufeira</city>
		<state>Algarve</state>
		<country>Portugal</country>
		<image>Albufeira</image>	
		<place>Albufeira</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>albufeira</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Albufeira, Algarve, Portugal</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>London</city>
		<state>United Kingdom</state>
		<country>England</country>
		<image>London</image>	
		<place>London</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>london</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>London, United Kingdom, England</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Cascais</city>
		<state>Lisbon</state>
		<country>Portugal</country>
		<image>Cascais</image>	
		<place>Cascais</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>cascais</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Cascais, Lisbon, Portugal</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Istanbul</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Turkey</country>
		<image>Istanbul</image>	
		<place>Istanbul</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>istanbul</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Istanbul, Turkey</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Kotor</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Montenegro</country>
		<image>Kotor</image>	
		<place>Kotor</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>kotor</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Kotor, Montenegro</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Khasab</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>United Arab Emirates</country>
		<image>Khasab</image>	
		<place>Khasab</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>khasab</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Khasab, United Arab Emirates</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Chalkidiki</city>
		<state>Macedonia</state>
		<country>Greece</country>
		<image>Chalkidiki</image>	
		<place>Chalkidiki</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>chalkidiki</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Chalkidiki, Macedonia, Greece</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Vilamoura</city>
		<state>Algarve</state>
		<country>Portugal</country>
		<image>Vilamoura</image>	
		<place>Vilamoura</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>vilamoura</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Vilamoura, Algarve, Portugal</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Ierapetra</city>
		<state>Crete</state>
		<country>Greece</country>
		<image>Ierapetra</image>	
		<place>Ierapetra</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>ierapetra</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Ierapetra, Crete, Greece</criteria>
	</location>
	
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>St. Maarten</country>
		<image>St.-Maarten</image>	
		<place>St. Maarten</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>st.-maarten</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>St. Maarten</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Vigo</city>
		<state>Galicia</state>
		<country>Spain</country>
		<image>Vigo</image>	
		<place>Vigo</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>vigo</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Vigo, Galicia, Spain</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Douro River</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Portugal</country>
		<image>Douro-River</image>	
		<place>Douro River</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>douro-river</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Douro River, Portugal</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Port Bunarina</city>
		<state>Pula</state>
		<country>Croatia</country>
		<image>Port-Bunarina</image>	
		<place>Port Bunarina</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>port-bunarina</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Port Bunarina, Pula, Croatia</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Bangalore</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>India</country>
		<image>Bangalore</image>	
		<place>Bangalore</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>bangalore</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Bangalore, India</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Basseterre</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Saint Kitts and Nevis</country>
		<image>Basseterre</image>	
		<place>Basseterre</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>basseterre</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Basseterre, Saint Kitts and Nevis</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Hamburg</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Germany</country>
		<image>Hamburg</image>	
		<place>Hamburg</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>hamburg</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Hamburg, Germany</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Bucharest</city>
		<state>Danube</state>
		<country>Romania</country>
		<image>Bucharest</image>	
		<place>Bucharest</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>bucharest</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Bucharest, Danube, Romania</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Cornwall</city>
		<state>United Kingdom</state>
		<country>England</country>
		<image>Cornwall</image>	
		<place>Cornwall</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>cornwall</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Cornwall, United Kingdom, England</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Oranjestad</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Aruba</country>
		<image>Oranjestad</image>	
		<place>Oranjestad</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>oranjestad</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Oranjestad, Aruba</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Noord</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Aruba</country>
		<image>Noord</image>	
		<place>Noord</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>noord</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Noord, Aruba</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Nassau</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Bahamas</country>
		<image>Nassau</image>	
		<place>Nassau</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>nassau</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Nassau, Bahamas</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Bridgetown</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Barbados</country>
		<image>Bridgetown</image>	
		<place>Bridgetown</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>bridgetown</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Bridgetown, Barbados</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Placencia</city>
		<state>Laughing Bird Caye National Park</state>
		<country>Belize</country>
		<image>Placencia</image>	
		<place>Placencia</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>placencia</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Placencia, Laughing Bird Caye National Park, Belize</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Playa Tamarindo</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Costa Rica</country>
		<image>Playa-Tamarindo</image>	
		<place>Playa Tamarindo</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>playa-tamarindo</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Playa Tamarindo, Costa Rica</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>Manuel Antonio National Park</state>
		<country>Costa Rica</country>
		<image>Manuel-Antonio-National-Park</image>	
		<place>Manuel Antonio National Park</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>manuel-antonio-national-park</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Manuel Antonio National Park, Costa Rica</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>San Jose</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Costa Rica</country>
		<image>San-Jose</image>	
		<place>San Jose</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>san-jose</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>San Jose, Costa Rica</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>La Fortuna</city>
		<state>Lake Arenal</state>
		<country>Costa Rica</country>
		<image>La-Fortuna</image>	
		<place>La Fortuna</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>la-fortuna</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>La Fortuna, Lake Arenal, Costa Rica</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>Montego Bay</state>
		<country>Jamaica</country>
		<image>Montego-Bay</image>	
		<place>Montego Bay</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>montego-bay</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Montego Bay, Jamaica</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Negril</city>
		<state>Montego Bay</state>
		<country>Jamaica</country>
		<image>Negril</image>	
		<place>Negril</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>negril</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Negril, Montego Bay, Jamaica</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Ocho Rios</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Jamaica</country>
		<image>Ocho-Rios</image>	
		<place>Ocho Rios</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>ocho-rios</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Ocho Rios, Jamaica</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Kingston</city>
		<state>Rio Grande</state>
		<country>Jamaica</country>
		<image>Kingston</image>	
		<place>Kingston</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>kingston</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Kingston, Rio Grande, Jamaica</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Panama City</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Panama</country>
		<image>Panama-City</image>	
		<place>Panama City</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>panama-city</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Panama City, Panama</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Soufriere</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>St. Lucia</country>
		<image>Soufriere</image>	
		<place>Soufriere</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>soufriere</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Soufriere, St. Lucia</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Tivua Island</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Fiji</country>
		<image>Tivua-Island</image>	
		<place>Tivua Island</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>tivua-island</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Tivua Island, Fiji</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Nadi</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Fiji</country>
		<image>Nadi</image>	
		<place>Nadi</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>nadi</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Nadi, Fiji</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Hong Kong</city>
		<state>Kowloon</state>
		<country>China</country>
		<image>Hong-Kong</image>	
		<place>Hong Kong</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>hong-kong</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Hong Kong, Kowloon, China</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Varanasi</city>
		<state>Uttar Pradesh</state>
		<country>India</country>
		<image>Varanasi</image>	
		<place>Varanasi</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>varanasi</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Varanasi, Uttar Pradesh, India</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Kochi</city>
		<state>Kerala</state>
		<country>India</country>
		<image>Kochi</image>	
		<place>Kochi</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>kochi</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Kochi, Kerala, India</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Panaji</city>
		<state>Goa</state>
		<country>India</country>
		<image>Panaji</image>	
		<place>Panaji</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>panaji</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Panaji, Goa, India</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Lake Pichola</city>
		<state>Rajasthan</state>
		<country>India</country>
		<image>Lake-Pichola</image>	
		<place>Lake Pichola</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>lake-pichola</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Lake Pichola, Rajasthan, India</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Chambal</city>
		<state>Agra</state>
		<country>India</country>
		<image>Chambal</image>	
		<place>Chambal</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>chambal</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Chambal, Agra, India</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Gili Islands</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Indonesia</country>
		<image>Gili-Islands</image>	
		<place>Gili Islands</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>gili-islands</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Gili Islands, Indonesia</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Langkawi</city>
		<state>Kedah</state>
		<country>Malaysia</country>
		<image>Langkawi</image>	
		<place>Langkawi</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>langkawi</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Langkawi, Kedah, Malaysia</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Kuala Lumpur</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Malaysia</country>
		<image>Kuala-Lumpur</image>	
		<place>Kuala Lumpur</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>kuala-lumpur</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Myanmar</country>
		<image>Myanmar</image>	
		<place>Myanmar</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>myanmar</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Myanmar</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Busan</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>South Korea</country>
		<image>Busan</image>	
		<place>Busan</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>busan</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Busan, South Korea</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Colombo</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Sri Lanka</country>
		<image>Colombo</image>	
		<place>Colombo</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>colombo</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Colombo, Sri Lanka</criteria>
	</location>
	
	<location>
		<city>El Calafate</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Argentina</country>
		<image>El Calafate</image>	
		<place>El Calafate</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>el calafate</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>El Calafate, Argentina</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state>Perito Moreno</state>
		<country>Argentina</country>
		<image>Perito-Moreno</image>	
		<place>Perito Moreno</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>perito-moreno</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Perito Moreno, Argentina</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Manaus</city>
		<state>Amazon River</state>
		<country>Brazil</country>
		<image>Manaus</image>	
		<place>Manaus</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>manaus</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Manaus, Amazon River, Brazil</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Rio de Janeiro</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Brazil</country>
		<image>Rio-de-Janeiro</image>	
		<place>Rio de Janeiro</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>rio-de-janeiro</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Rio de Janeiro, Brazil</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Paraty</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Brazil</country>
		<image>Paraty</image>	
		<place>Paraty</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>paraty</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Paraty, Brazil</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Puerto El Morro</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Ecuador</country>
		<image>Puerto-El-Morro</image>	
		<place>Puerto El Morro</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>puerto-el-morro</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Puerto El Morro, Ecuador</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Foz do Iguaçu</city>
		<state>Foz do Iguaçu</state>
		<country>Paraguay</country>
		<image>Foz-do-Iguaçu</image>	
		<place>Foz do Iguaçu</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>foz-do-iguaçu</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Foz do Iguaçu, Foz do Iguaçu, Paraguay</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Paracas</city>
		<state>Ballestas Islands</state>
		<country>Peru</country>
		<image>Paracas</image>	
		<place>Paracas</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>paracas</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Paracas, Ballestas Islands, Peru</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Iquitos</city>
		<state>Amazon River</state>
		<country>Peru</country>
		<image>Iquitos</image>	
		<place>Iquitos</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>iquitos</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Iquitos, Amazon River, Peru</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Lima</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Peru</country>
		<image>Lima</image>	
		<place>Lima</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>lima</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Lima, Peru</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Cusco</city>
		<state>Lake Titicaca</state>
		<country>Peru</country>
		<image>Cusco</image>	
		<place>Cusco</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>cusco</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Cusco, Lake Titicaca, Peru</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city>Grand Baie</city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Mauritius</country>
		<image>Grand-Baie</image>	
		<place>Grand Baie</place>	
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>	
		<link></link>
		<link2>grand-baie</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Grand Baie, Mauritius</criteria>
	</location>
	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Antarctica</country>
		<image>Antarctica</image>
		<place>Antarctica</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>antarctica</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Antarctica</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Argentina</country>
		<image>Argentina</image>
		<place>Argentina</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>argentina</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Argentina</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Aruba</country>
		<image>Aruba</image>
		<place>Aruba</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>aruba</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Aruba</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Barbados</country>
		<image>Barbados</image>
		<place>Barbados</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>barbados</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Barbados</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Belgium</country>
		<image>Belgium</image>
		<place>Belgium</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>belgium</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Belgium</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Brazil</country>
		<image>Brazil</image>
		<place>Brazil</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>brazil</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Brazil</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Cambodia</country>
		<image>Cambodia</image>
		<place>Cambodia</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>cambodia</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Cambodia</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Canada</country>
		<image>Canada</image>
		<place>Canada</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>canada</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Canada</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Denmark</country>
		<image>Denmark</image>
		<place>Denmark</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>denmark</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Denmark</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Dominican Republic</country>
		<image>Dominican-Republic</image>
		<place>Dominican Republic</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>dominican-republic</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Dominican Republic</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Ecuador</country>
		<image>Ecuador</image>
		<place>Ecuador</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>ecuador</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Ecuador</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Egypt</country>
		<image>Egypt</image>
		<place>Egypt</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>egypt</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Egypt</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>England</country>
		<image>England</image>
		<place>England</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>england</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>England</criteria>
	</location>


	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Germany</country>
		<image>Germany</image>
		<place>Germany</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>germany</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Germany</criteria>
	</location>


	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Greenland</country>
		<image>Greenland</image>
		<place>Greenland</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>greenland</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Greenland</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Guatemala</country>
		<image>Guatemala</image>
		<place>Guatemala</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>guatemala</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Guatemala</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>India</country>
		<image>India</image>
		<place>India</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>india</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>India</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Jamaica</country>
		<image>Jamaica</image>
		<place>Jamaica</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>jamaica</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Jamaica</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Latvia</country>
		<image>Latvia</image>
		<place>Latvia</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>latvia</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Latvia</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Mexico</country>
		<image>Mexico</image>
		<place>Mexico</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>mexico</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Mexico</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Montenegro</country>
		<image>Montenegro</image>
		<place>Montenegro</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>montenegro</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Montenegro</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Netherlands</country>
		<image>Netherlands</image>
		<place>Netherlands</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>netherlands</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Netherlands</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Oman</country>
		<image>Oman</image>
		<place>Oman</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>oman</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Oman</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Panama</country>
		<image>Panama</image>
		<place>Panama</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>panama</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Panama</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Paraguay</country>
		<image>Paraguay</image>
		<place>Paraguay</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>paraguay</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Paraguay</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Peru</country>
		<image>Peru</image>
		<place>Peru</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>peru</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Peru</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Philippines</country>
		<image>Philippines</image>
		<place>Philippines</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>philippines</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Philippines</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Portugal</country>
		<image>Portugal</image>
		<place>Portugal</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>portugal</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Portugal</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Romania</country>
		<image>Romania</image>
		<place>Romania</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>romania</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Romania</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Russia</country>
		<image>Russia</image>
		<place>Russia</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>russia</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Russia</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Saint Kitts and Nevis</country>
		<image>Saint-Kitts-and-Nevis</image>
		<place>Saint Kitts and Nevis</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>saint-kitts-and-nevis</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Saint Kitts and Nevis</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>South Africa</country>
		<image>South-Africa</image>
		<place>South Africa</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>south-africa</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>South Africa</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>South Korea</country>
		<image>South-Korea</image>
		<place>South Korea</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>south-korea</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>South Korea</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Spain</country>
		<image>Spain</image>
		<place>Spain</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>spain</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Spain</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>St. Martin</country>
		<image>St.-Martin</image>
		<place>St. Martin</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>st.-martin</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>St. Martin</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Switzerland</country>
		<image>Switzerland</image>
		<place>Switzerland</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>switzerland</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Switzerland</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Trinidad and Tobago</country>
		<image>Trinidad-and-Tobago</image>
		<place>Trinidad and Tobago</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>trinidad-and-tobago</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Trinidad and Tobago</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Ukraine</country>
		<image>Ukraine</image>
		<place>Ukraine</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>ukraine</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Ukraine</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>United Arab Emirates</country>
		<image>United-Arab-Emirates</image>
		<place>United Arab Emirates</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>united-arab-emirates</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>United Arab Emirates</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>United States</country>
		<image>United-States</image>
		<place>United States</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>united-states</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>United States</criteria>
	</location>

	<location>
		<city></city>
		<state></state>
		<country>Vietnam</country>
		<image>Vietnam</image>
		<place>Vietnam</place>
		<search>boat</search>
		<text></text>
		<link></link>
		<link2>vietnam</link2>
		<areas></areas>
		<criteria>Vietnam</criteria>
	</location>
</countries>